<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<eastendersOmnibus>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b007qmpq</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b007qmpq</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5082189274976367100.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>01/07/2007</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Dawn is finally able to escape May and Rob and is left holding the baby. A persistent Bradley eventually wins Stacey's heart and Stella's past starts to catch up with her.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Dawn is finally able to escape May and Rob and is left holding the baby. A persistent Bradley eventually wins Stacey's heart. Stella's past starts to catch up with her.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Dawn Swann; Dr May Wright; Rob Minter; Bradley Branning; Stacey Slater; Stella Crawford</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b007stw6</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b007stw6</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5084819083455904024.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>08/07/2007</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>As the Vic re-opens it looks like Pat may have got one over on Peggy by offering a service you just can't get in the Vic. Ian discovers Jane has been living a lie.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>As the Vic re-opens it looks like Pat may have got one over on Peggy by offering a service you just can't get in the Vic. Ian discovers Jane has been living a lie.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Dawn Swann; Dr May Wright; Rob Minter; Bradley Branning; Stacey Slater; Stella Crawford</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b007t27y</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b007t27y</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5087397352319500829.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>15/07/2007</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Max is determined to split up Stacey and Bradley, forcing her to make a difficult decision. Phil's doubts about marrying Stella surface until Ben's return cements all their futures.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Max is determined to split up Stacey and Bradley, forcing her to make a difficult decision. Phil's doubts about marrying Stella surface until Ben's return cements all their futures. Deano and Chelsea join forces to seek revenge on Sean.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Max Branning; Stacey Slater; Bradley Branning; Phil Mitchell; Stella Crawford; Ben Mitchell</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b007tqdj</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b007tqdj</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5089967890246158488.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>22/07/2007</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>After a failed attempt to run away, will Ben have the confidence to stop Phil and Stella's wedding? Jase Dyer arrives to claim his son and Yolande is shocked by an outburst from Jay.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>After a failed attempt to run away, will Ben have the confidence to stop Phil and Stella's wedding? Jase Dyer arrives to claim his son and Yolande is shocked by an outburst from Jay.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Stella Crawford; Phil Mitchell; Ben Mitchell; Peggy Mitchell; Jase Dyer; Yolande Trueman</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b007v9h4</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b007v9h4</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5092591256270557686.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>29/07/2007</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Stella's demise rocks the Mitchells' world, and Ian is beside himself with worry for Ben. Bert feels pushed out by Jase. Bobby creates havoc at the Beales'.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Stella's demise rocks the Mitchells' world, and Ian is beside himself with worry for Ben. Bert feels pushed out by Jase. Bobby creates havoc at the Beales.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Ian Beale; Ben Mitchell; Bert Atkins; Jay Brown</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b007vyqq</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b007vyqq</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5095188852491180510.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>05/08/2007</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Left in charge of the Vic, Ronnie and Roxy make an enemy of Ian Beale. An unexpected visitor forces Tanya to confront her past. Lucy heads for more trouble.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Left in charge of the Vic, Ronnie and Roxy make an enemy of Ian Beale. An unexpected visitor forces Tanya to confront her past. Lucy heads for more trouble.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Ronnie Mitchell; Roxy Mitchell; Ian Beale; Tanya Branning; Lucy Beale</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b007wjjv</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b007wjjv</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5097786448711803488.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>12/08/2007</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Patrick is attacked and Sean becomes the number one suspect. While Carly and Stacey protest his innocence, the rest of the Square have their doubts.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>The Square reels after Patrick is attacked, and a devastated Yolande can only wait to see if her husband will recover. Chelsea and Deano give witness statements and Sean becomes number one suspect. While Carly and Stacey protest his innocence, the rest of the Square have their doubts.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Patrick Trueman; Yolande Trueman; Chelsea Fox; Deano Wicks; Sean Slater; Carly Wicks</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b007x4yz</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b007x4yz</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5100377602481482580.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>19/08/2007</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Sean is charged with Patrick's attack and even Carly starts to doubt his innocence. Yolande tries to come to terms with the repercussions of the attack.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Sean is charged with Patrick's attack and even Carly starts to doubt his innocence. Yolande tries to come to terms with the repercussions of the attack. Lucy continues to pull the wool over Ian's eyes. Chelsea panics when Deano threatens to abandon her in support of his sister.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Sean Slater; Patrick Trueman; Carly Wicks; Yolande Trueman; Ian Beale; Lucy Beale</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b007xqyh</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b007xqyh</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5102955871349273478.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>26/08/2007</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Will Pat find her long lost sister, whom she thought was dead? Will Shirley help Heather win over Garry's affections as they follow him to Brighton?</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Heather and Shirley follow Garry to Brighton as Heather vies for his affections, while Garry struggles with his feelings for Dawn as he tries to help her form a bond with her daughter. Minty worries about Garry's reaction to his choice of girlfriend. Will Pat find her long lost sister?</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Heather Trott; Shirley Carter; Garry Hobbs; Dawn Swann; Minty Peterson; Pat Evans</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b007y9t9</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b007y9t9</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5105576660393265393.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>02/09/2007</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>A blast from Roxy's past puts Ronnie in a tight spot. Even with Sean behind bars, Deano discovers he's not untouchable. Phil goes AWOL and Ian wrestles with Lucy's future.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>A blast from Roxy's past puts Ronnie in a tight spot. Even with Sean behind bars, Deano discovers he's not untouchable. Ian wrestles with Lucy's future. Phil goes AWOL.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Roxy Mitchell; Ronnie Mitchell; Deano Wicks; Ian Beale; Lucy Beale</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b007yylr</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b007yylr</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5108178122084455100.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>09/09/2007</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Deano and Chelsea try to talk their way out of lying to the police. Peggy struggles to cope as Phil finally returns from Portugal, having started drinking again.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Deano and Chelsea try to talk their way out of lying to the police. Peggy struggles to cope as Phil finally returns from Portugal, having started drinking again. Lucy takes on Deano and Chelsea, but has she bitten off more than she can chew with Craig?</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Deano Wicks; Chelsea Fox; Peggy Mitchell; Phil Mitchell; Lucy Beale; Craig Dixon</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b007zmsx</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b007zmsx</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5110769275854133936.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>16/09/2007</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Sean is out of prison and after Deano and Chelsea. Peggy and Ben struggle to cope with Phil's drinking. Are Jase's true colours beginning to show?</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Sean is out of prison and after Deano and Chelsea. Peggy and Ben struggle to cope with Phil's drinking. Are Jase's true colours beginning to show?</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Sean Slater; Deano Wicks; Chelsea Fox; Peggy Mitchell; Ben Mitchell; Phil Mitchell; Jase Dyer</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b008075y</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b008075y</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5113369449055134314.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>23/09/2007</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Is Ian going mad, or is Cindy back from the grave? As Deano cracks under the pressure, Kevin tries to be a good dad. Will Phil be able to stay on the wagon?</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Is Ian losing his mind, or is Cindy back from the grave? As Deano cracks under the pressure, Kevin tries to be a good dad. Will Phil be able to stay on the wagon? And as Jase's secret is out, will he be able to keep his relationship together with Jay?</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Sean Slater; Deano Wicks; Chelsea Fox; Peggy Mitchell; Ben Mitchell; Phil Mitchell; Jase Dyer</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b0080smc</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b0080smc</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5115997969040288798.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>30/09/2007</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Speculation over Ian's disappearance spreads through the Square. Shirley considers desperate measures to pay the rent as Stacey's wedding plans continue to go awry.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Speculation over Ian's disappearance spreads through the Square. Shirley considers desperate measures to pay the rent as Stacey's wedding plans continue to go awry.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Sean Slater; Deano Wicks; Chelsea Fox; Peggy Mitchell; Ben Mitchell; Phil Mitchell; Jase Dyer</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b0081kj4</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b0081kj4</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5118567218476758074.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>07/10/2007</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Max goes against Stacey's wishes, but will he be able to handle the consequences? The Wicks family appear united in their preparation for Chelsea and Deano's sentencing.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Max goes against Stacey's wishes, but will he be able to handle the consequences? The Wicks family appears united in preparation for Chelsea and Deano's sentencing, but Deano has no intention of going to jail. Steven deflects the police investigation into Ian's disappearance while growing closer to the remaining Beale family, but what has he done to Ian?</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Sean Slater; Deano Wicks; Chelsea Fox; Peggy Mitchell; Ben Mitchell; Phil Mitchell; Jase Dyer</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b0082h5j</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b0082h5j</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5121181565069835620.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>14/10/2007</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Chelsea, Deano and family struggle to deal with their imprisonment. Shirley's intrigued by the man who knocked her down. Steven reveals what happened to Ian.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Chelsea, Deano and their family struggle to deal with their imprisonment. Shirley is intrigued by the man who knocked her down. Steven finally reveals what happened to Ian and a gunshot rings out into the night.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Sean Slater; Deano Wicks; Chelsea Fox; Peggy Mitchell; Ben Mitchell; Steven Beale; Jase Dyer</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b0084kph</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b0084kph</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5123776584310080888.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>21/10/2007</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Ian struggles to cope with the aftermath of Steven's plan. Ronnie and Roxy get excited about the future only for their plans to be devastated by an admission from Peggy.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Ian struggles to cope with the aftermath of Steven's plan. Ronnie and Roxy get excited about the future only for their plans to be devastated by an admission from Peggy. Meanwhile, Minty gives Hazel and Garry a scare and the Masood family's move onto the Square doesn't go according to plan.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Sean Slater; Deano Wicks; Chelsea Fox; Peggy Mitchell; Ben Mitchell; Steven Beale; Jase Dyer</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b0085b0m</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b0085b0m</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5126393507883535583.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>28/10/2007</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>As Stacey and Bradley's wedding day approaches, Max makes a last ditch attempt to win Stacey's love. The Mitchell women resort to desperate measures to keep Peggy's creditors at bay.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>As Stacey and Bradley's wedding day approaches, Max makes a last ditch attempt to win Stacey's love. The Mitchell women resort to desperate measures to keep Peggy's creditors at bay and maintain control of the Vic. Jase, rejected by his new friends and neighbours, is tempted to return to his dark past.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Stacey; Peggy Mitchell; Max; Bradley; Jase Dyer</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b0087f19</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b0087f19</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5128980796182648762.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>04/11/2007</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Jack Branning's arrival in Walford has unexpected consequences for Ronnie and Roxy. Stacey is devastated by Sean's discovery on the eve of her wedding. Jase decides to put Terry behind him.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Jack Branning's arrival in Walford has unexpected consequences for Ronnie and Roxy. Stacey is devastated by Sean's discovery on the eve of her wedding. Jase decides to put Terry behind him. The Masoods plan to welcome Syed back home.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Stacey; Jack; Roxy; Sean; Jase Dyer; Ronnie</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b0088x0g</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b0088x0g</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5131569372971949657.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>11/11/2007</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Ronnie gets the better of Jack to help Peggy out of debt, but jeopardises her own chances of running the club. Sean struggles to spend time with his mum after the wedding.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Ronnie gets the better of Jack to help Peggy out of debt, but jeopardises her own chances of running the club. Sean struggles to spend time with his mum after the wedding. Jase decides to face up to his violent past. Jane gets out of hospital, but her problems are far from over.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Peggy; Jack; Jane; Sean; Jase Dyer; Ronnie</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b0089xz6</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b0089xz6</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5134204335408048218.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>18/11/2007</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Steven returns to make amends with the Beales. An attack on the Vic has disastrous consequences for Jase.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Steven returns to make amends with the Beales. An attack on the Vic leads to disastrous consequences for Jase.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Steven; Ian; Jane; Jase; Sean; Peggy</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b008d356</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b008d356</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5136783892766027774.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>25/11/2007</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Back from honeymoon, Stacey and Bradley's plans to set up home are thrown into disarray. Steven is thrown a lifeline by Pat. Phil has plans for Kevin, but fears Darren will uncover the truth.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Back from honeymoon, Stacey and Bradley's plans to set up home are thrown into disarray. Steven is thrown a lifeline by Pat. Phil has plans for Kevin, but fears Darren will uncover the truth.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Stacey Branning; Bradley Branning; Steven Beale; Pat Evans; Phil Mitchell; Kevin Wicks; Darren Miller</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b008gzg1</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b008gzg1</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5139373758049682973.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>02/12/2007</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Kevin makes a huge decision for the sake of his family and Ronnie and Roxy prepare for the opening night of the club, but is Ronnie hiding something?</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Kevin makes a big decision for his family. Ronnie and Roxy prepare for the opening night of the club, but Ronnie seems to be hiding something. Pressure builds for Billy as he tries to provide for his family and Heather tries cheer up Shirley.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Kevin Wicks; Ronnie Mitchell; Roxy Mitchell; Billy Mitchell; Heather Trott; Shirley Carter</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b008h3qy</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b008h3qy</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5141963623324979850.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>09/12/2007</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Jack has a big revelation for the Mitchells, leaving them furious. Roxy struggles to recover from Ronnie's betrayal. Peggy is left to explain recent events to Phil.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Jack has a big revelation for the Mitchells, leaving them furious. Roxy struggles to recover from Ronnie's betrayal. Peggy is left to explain recent events to Phil. Stacey fights to stop Steven's devastating actions. Dawn prepares to put her heart on the line, but someone could be about to beat her to it.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Jack Branning; Phil Mitchell; Roxy Mitchell; Ronnie Mitchell; Peggy Mitchell; Stacey Branning; Steven Beale; Dawn Swann</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b008j3ck</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b008j3ck</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5144572815957301505.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>16/12/2007</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>An increasingly desperate Billy is forced to make a decision he will live to regret. Phil and Max join forces to deal with Jack once and for all.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>An increasingly desperate Billy is forced to make a decision he will live to regret. Phil and Max join forces to deal with Jack once and for all, while events take an unexpected turn for Tanya. Peggy is thrown by a shocking discovery. Bradley is concerned by Stacey's new friendship with Steven.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Billy Mitchell; Phil Mitchell; Jack Branning; Max Branning; Peggy Mitchell; Bradley Branning; Stacey Branning; Steven Beale</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b008l0r9</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b008l0r9</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5147163969726980524.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>23/12/2007</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Peggy can't decide whether or not to help Billy. Lauren makes a discovery that threatens to blow the Branning family apart. Will Ian finally forgive Steven?</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Peggy can't decide whether or not to help Billy. Lauren makes a discovery that threatens to blow the Branning family apart. Will Ian finally forgive Steven?</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Stacey Branning; Phil Mitchell; Jack Branning; Peggy Mitchell; Billy Mitchell; Max Branning</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b008l1nd</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b008l1nd</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5149756411986848693.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>30/12/2007</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>A revelation blows the Branning family apart as Tanya reels at Max's betrayal. Abi takes matters into her own hands. Bradley seeks revenge on Stacey.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>A revelation blows the Branning family apart. Tanya reels at Max's betrayal. Abi takes matters into her own hands. Bradley seeks revenge on Stacey. Kevin tries to do the right thing for his family.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Stacey Branning; Phil Mitchell; Jack Branning; Max Branning; Tanya Branning; Kevin Wicks</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b008plct</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b008plct</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5152332103878454816.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>06/01/2008</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>The Wicks family are looking forward to 2008 when disaster strikes. Phil sets out to reunite his family and will Abi's intervention lead to trouble for Tanya?</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>The Wicks family are looking forward to 2008 when disaster strikes. Phil sets out to reunite his family. Abi's intervention leads to trouble for Tanya.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Deano Wicks; Carly Wicks; Denise Wicks; Kevin Wicks; Tanya Branning; Heather Trott</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b008pt30</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b008pt30</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5154964489329981991.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>13/01/2008</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Tanya struggles to hold it together as Max plays dirty in order to protect the girls. Meanwhile, Ronnie struggles with her loyalties to the Mitchells and her feelings for Jack.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Tanya struggles to hold it together as Max plays dirty in order to protect the girls. Ronnie struggles with her loyalties to the Mitchells and her feelings for Jack. Darren plays a dangerous game in order to avenge Kevin's death. Shirley discovers the truth about Vinnie.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Tanya Branning; Max Branning; Ronnie Mitchell; Jack Branning; Darren Miller; Shirley Carter; Vinnie Monks</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b008s7cn</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b008s7cn</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5157563374040793418.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>20/01/2008</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Dawn finds herself with a difficult decision to make, while the Beales play host to an unwelcome guest. Jay falls under a dangerous influence, and Ronnie and Jack's fledgling romance flounders.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Dawn finds herself with a difficult decision to make. The Beales play host to an unwelcome surprise guest from Jane's past. Jay falls under a dangerous influence. Ronnie and Jack's fledgling romance flounders when Ronnie starts to harbour mistrust.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Dawn Swann; Jane Beale; Ian Beale; Christian Clarke; Jay Brown; Ronnie Mitchell; Jack Branning</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b008vr2n</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b008vr2n</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5160142931398773125.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>27/01/2008</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Ronnie digs into Jack's past, whilst Jay strives to impress the E20 crew. Christian ensures that Jane cops more than an eyeful on a trip down the club.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Ronnie digs into Jack's past. Jay strives to impress the E20 crew.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Ronnie Mitchell; Jack Branning; Jay Brown</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b008wtjr</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b008wtjr</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5160186740065192318.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>27/01/2008</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>As Ronnie digs into Jack's past, Jay's bid to run with the E20 crew leads him into danger. Roxy seeks Ronnie's forgiveness but discovers something far worse.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Jay's bid to run with the E20 crew leads him into danger. Roxy seeks Ronnie's forgiveness but discovers something far worse.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Jay Brown; Roxy Mitchell; Ronnie Mitchell</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b008x394</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b008x394</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5162737950639018504.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>03/02/2008</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Roxy tells Ronnie about Jack and Selina, and Dot makes a tough decision about Jim.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>The men of Walford are captivated by a new arrival on the square. Ronnie packs a punch when Roxy tells her about Jack and Selina. Minty's dreams are shattered when Hazel tells him he isn't going to be a daddy, and Dot makes the toughest decision about Jim.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Tanya Branning; Max Branning; Jay Brown; Ronnie Mitchell; Jack Branning; Shirley Carter</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b008yjbh</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b008yjbh</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5162803663638647290.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>03/02/2008</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>While Jack and Roxy try to pick up a broken Ronnie, a familiar face re-appears on the square. Minty's dreams are shattered when Hazel tells him he isn't going to be a daddy.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription></episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters></episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b008yvjp</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b008yvjp</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5165358739687234184.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>10/02/2008</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>A familiar face makes a shocking return to Walford. Meanwhile, Minty is devastated by Hazel's decision, Stacey fails to make a fresh start and Ian is forced to mix business with pleasure.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>A familiar face makes a shocking return to Walford. Minty is devastated by Hazel's decision. Stacey fails to make a fresh start. Ian is forced to mix business with pleasure.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Claire Bates; Minty Peterson; Hazel Hobbs; Stacey Branning; Ian Beale</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b0090bl4</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b0090bl4</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5167942162515780379.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>17/02/2008</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Stacey's collapse motivates her to fight for Bradley. Tanya girds herself for the first divorce hearing but Max isn't going to give in easily and Mo helps Charlie to look to the future.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Stacey's collapse motivates her to fight for Bradley. Tanya girds herself for the first divorce hearing, but Max won't give in easily. Mo helps Charlie to look to the future.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Stacey Branning; Mo Harris; Charlie Slater; Max Branning; Jack Branning; Shirley Carter</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00920zd</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00920zd</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5170556509104663531.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>24/02/2008</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>The Mitchells unite to deal with Jack's ploy to steal the Vic's business; Tanya throws a birthday party which ends disastrously; Clare sets her sights on Ian; and Jase and Jay find a new home.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>The Mitchells unite to deal with Jack's ploy to steal the Vic's business. Tanya throws a birthday party which ends disastrously. Clare sets her sights on Ian, while Jase and Jay find a new home.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Jack Branning; Tanya Branning; Clare Bates; Ian Beale; Jase Dyer; Jay Brown</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00936ch</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00936ch</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5173160547776230613.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>02/03/2008</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Will Ian fall prey to Clare's charms? Tanya plays a dangerous game with Max. With Jase away, Dawn takes charge of her new extended family. Charlie gets himself into hot water. [AD.S]</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Will Ian fall for Clare's charms? Tanya plays a dangerous game with Max. With Jase away, Dawn takes charge of her new extended family. Charlie gets himself into hot water when he gives into sweet temptation.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Ian Beale; Clare Bates; Tanya Branning; Max Branning; Dawn Swann; Charlie Slater</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b009gpcb</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b009gpcb</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5175714335334600128.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>09/03/2008</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Tanya's plan to fleece Max gets underway but is she raising suspicion? Steven and Stacey grow closer as he convinces her to pursue her dream.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Tanya's plan to fleece Max gets underway but is she raising suspicion? Steven and Stacey grow closer as he convinces her to pursue her dream. Shirley makes a disovery that sends her spiralling out of control.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Stacey Branning; Bradley Branning; Steven Beale; Pat Evans; Phil Mitchell; Kevin Wicks; Darren Miller</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b009pdcm</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b009pdcm</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5183500681541330004.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>30/03/2008</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>With the threat of Sean looming large, Tanya struggles to cope without Max. Meanwhile Roxy is dreading the prospect of turning 30, and Chelsea's behaviour alienates Libby.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>With the threat of Sean looming large, Tanya struggles to cope without Max. Meanwhile, Roxy is dreading the prospect of turning 30, Chelsea's behaviour alienates Libby and a sensitive Christian surprises Ian.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Sean Slater; Tanya Branning; Roxy Mitchell; Chelsea Fox; Libby Fox; Christian Clarke; Ian Beale</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b009s6rn</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b009s6rn</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5186090546820820475.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>06/04/2008</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>As the Square gathers for Frank's funeral, some faces from the past come to pay their last respects. Bianca is pushed to extremes trying to protect her kids.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>As the Square gathers for Frank's funeral, some faces from the past come to pay their last respects. Bianca is pushed to extremes trying to protect her kids, whilst Chelsea makes a big decision about her life which leads to an unexpected conclusion.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Bianca Jackson; Pat Evans; Peggy Mitchell; Ricky Butcher; Diane Butcher; Janine Butcher; Chelsea Fox; Libby Fox</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b009x0h2</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b009x0h2</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5188715201335408308.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>13/04/2008</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>A desperate Bianca returns to Walford leaving Pat with a dilemma. Phil takes Shirley to the hospital for her biopsy results, and a vengeful Sean has Gus in his sights.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>A desperate Bianca returns to Albert Square, leaving Pat with a dilemma. Ricky is forced to play along with Bianca's tall tales, but can they pull it off? Sean and Roxy arrange another risky rendevouz. Tanya gives Ronnie some advice about Jack.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Bianca Jackson; Pat Evans; Ricky Butcher; Sean Slater; Roxy Mitchell; Tanya Branning; Ronnie Mitchell; Jack Branning</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00b099p</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00b099p</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5191298624163954909.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>20/04/2008</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Steven attempts to take his relationship with Stacey further; Roxy is determined to win the Barmaid of the Year competition; and Jack's relationship with Ronnie goes downhill.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Steven attempts to take his relationship with Stacey further, but is he being true to himself? Roxy is determined to become barmaid of the year, but has some tough competition. Jack's relationship with Ronnie goes downhill after Penny's arrival.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Stacey Branning; Bradley Branning; Steven Beale; Pat Evans; Phil Mitchell; Kevin Wicks; Darren Miller</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00b9d22</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00b9d22</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5196475777742558012.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>04/05/2008</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Roxy struggles with her betrayal of Ronnie whilst Sean careers dangerously out of control. Ian's investigations lead to the truth about Steven; will Ian accept it?</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Roxy struggles with her betrayal of Ronnie whilst Sean careers dangerously out of control. Ian's investigations lead to the truth about Steven. Will Ian accept it?</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Stacey Branning; Bradley Branning; Steven Beale; Pat Evans; Phil Mitchell; Kevin Wicks; Darren Miller</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00bdmgw</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00bdmgw</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5199081104904313198.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>11/05/2008</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Steven is forced to take drastic measures to keep his secret hidden; Roxy's horrible day has a surprising twist; Bradley helps Clare in her hour of need; and Ricky sets his sights on Bianca.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Steven is forced to take drastic meaures to keep his secret hidden. Roxy's horrible day has a surprising twist, Bradley helps Clare in her hour of need and Ricky sets his sights on Bianca.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Steven Beale; Roxy Mitchell; Bradley Branning; Ricky Butcher; Bianca Jackson; Clare Bates; Stacey Branning; Pat Evans; Phil Mitchell; Kevin Wicks; Darren Miller</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00bv31p</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00bv31p</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5204268566404426649.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>25/05/2008</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Christian warns Roxy she won't be able to keep her secret from Sean and Jack. Chelsea is horrified by the arrival of an unexpected visitor and Heather's dreams are left in tatters.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Christian warns Roxy she won't be able to keep her secret from Sean and Jack. Chelsea is horrified by the arrival of an unexpected visitor and Heather's dreams are left in tatters.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Roxy Mitchell; Ronnie Mitchell; Zainab Masood; Shabnam Masood; Ian Beale; Jane Beale; Stacey Branning; Bradley Branning; Steven Beale; Pat Evans; Phil Mitchell; Kevin Wicks; Darren Miller</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00bydvy</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00bydvy</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5206894509409203177.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>01/06/2008</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Ronnie and Roxy are determined to leave Walford, but can Sean stop them? Tanya and Jack's relationship develops. Chelsea is on self-destruct mode as she attempts to deal with her father.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Ronnie and Roxy are determined to leave Walford, but can Sean stop them? Tanya and Jack's relationship develops and Chelsea's on self destruct as she attempts to deal with her father.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Roxy Mitchell; Ronnie Mitchell; Zainab Masood; Shabnam Masood; Ian Beale; Jane Beale; Stacey Branning; Bradley Branning; Steven Beale; Pat Evans; Phil Mitchell; Kevin Wicks; Darren Miller</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00c1cny</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00c1cny</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5209463758845643561.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>08/06/2008</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Chelsea goes further and further off the rails, will somebody be able to save her? Dawn suspects Jase is playing away, but the truth could be much worse; and can the Millers believe their luck?</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Chelsea goes further and further off the rails. Dawn suspects Jase could be playing away but the truth could be much worse, and can the Millers believe their luck?</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Jase Dyer; May Wright; Dawn Swann; Denise Wicks; Chelsea Fox; Lucas Johnson; Patrick Trueman; Yolande Trueman; Libby Fox; Clare Bates; Jack Branning; Tanya Branning; Lauren Branning</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00c3z3v</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00c3z3v</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5212066509027021530.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>15/06/2008</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>May returns to the Square to bid farewell to Summer. Jean meddles with Charlie's love life whilst Shirley finds herself at the helm of the Vic.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>May returns to the square to bid farewell to Summer. Jean meddles with Charlie's love life while Shirley finds herself at the helm of the Vic.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>May Wright; Jean Slater; Charlie Slater; Shirley Carter; Roxy Mitchell; Ronnie Mitchell; Zainab Masood; Shabnam Masood; Ian Beale; Jane Beale; Stacey Branning; Bradley Branning; Steven Beale; Pat Evans; Phil Mitchell; Kevin Wicks; Darren Miller</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00c7c8d</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00c7c8d</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5214658951286889389.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>22/06/2008</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>The 'Best of British' party takes a dramatic turn as May returns to the Square, with explosive consequences for the Millers. Tensions creep into Jack and Tanya's relationship.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>The Best of British party takes a dramatic turn as May returns to the Square, with explosive consequences for the Millers. Tensions creep into Jack and Tanya's relationship as Abi's pining for her dad gets worse. Ian tries to stop Lucy from making a big mistake.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>May Wright; Darren Miller; Tanya Branning; Jack Branning; Abi Branning; Lucy Beale; Jean Slater; Charlie Slater; Shirley Carter; Roxy Mitchell; Ronnie Mitchell; Zainab Masood; Shabnam Masood; Ian Beale</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00cc5x2</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00cc5x2</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5217256547507511999.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>29/06/2008</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Max arrives back on the Square - will he cope with the changes in his family? Jean searches for love as Stacey's life takes a dramatic turn, and Bianca finds she might have a guardian angel.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Will Max cope with his family's changed circumstances as he arrives back in the Square? Jean searches for love as Stacey's life takes a dramatic turn. Bianca thinks she might have a guardian angel.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Max Branning; Stacey Branning; Bianca Jackson; Jean Slater; May Wright; Darren Miller; Tanya Branning; Jack Branning; Abi Branning; Lucy Beale; Charlie Slater; Shirley Carter; Roxy Mitchell; Ronnie Mitchell; Zainab Masood</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00cdpny</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00cdpny</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5219838681845868979.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>06/07/2008</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Max's attempt at revenge has unexpected consequences for Jack and Tanya. Stacey and Bradley make a shocking discovery about Sean, and Mickey makes a big decision about his life.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Max's attempt at revenge has unexpected consequences for Jack and Tanya. Stacey and Bradley make a shocking discovery about Sean. Mickey makes a big decision about his life.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Max Branning; Jack Branning; Tanya Branning; Stacey Branning; Bradley Branning; Sean Slater; Mickey Miller; Bianca Jackson; Jean Slater; May Wright; Darren Miller; Abi Branning; Lucy Beale; Charlie Slater; Shirley Carter</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00cjyyk</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00cjyyk</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5222476221262344289.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>13/07/2008</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Peggy forces Ronnie to face up to someone and something from the past. Meanwhile, Sean searches for Roxy and life gets complicated for Phil when he meets Max's sister.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Peggy reveals Roxy's hiding-place to Ronnie - but does she have a hidden agenda? Phil takes on a special errand for Max. Billy and Honey step up when their family needs them. 

	While Roxy is having the time of her life, Ronnie struggles to get through to her sister. Life gets complicated for Phil when he meets Max's sister. 

	Back in Walford, Phil gets more than he bargained for from Suzy. Tensions run high as Ronnie and Archie open old wounds. Peggy makes a big decision.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Peggy Mitchell; Ronnie Mitchell; Sean Slater; Roxy Mitchell; Phil Mitchell; Suzy Branning; Max Branning; Jack Branning; Tanya Branning; Stacey Branning; Bradley Branning; Mickey Miller; Bianca Jackson; Jean Slater; May Wright</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00cmw7y</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00cmw7y</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5225040316738057988.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>20/07/2008</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Bianca makes a surprising discovery about Whitney, Ronnie goes to devious lengths to get her sister away from Sean's clutches, and Jase has a dangerous solution to his and Dawn's money worries.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Bianca makes a surprising discovery about Whitney. Ronnie goes to devious lengths to get her sister away from Sean's clutches. Jase has a dangerous solution to his and Dawn's money worries.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Bianca Jackson; Whitney Dean; Ronnie Mitchell; Roxy Mitchell; Sean Slater; Jase Dyer; Dawn Swann; Peggy Mitchell; Phil Mitchell; Suzy Branning; Max Branning; Jack Branning; Tanya Branning; Stacey Branning; Bradley Branning</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00csgyz</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00csgyz</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5227646932390001944.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>27/07/2008</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Max turns to underhand tactics to get his own way, while Bradley makes a shocking discovery about Clare. Jase takes on a risky job, and Shabnam encourages her family to think big.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Max turns to underhand tactics to get his own way, while Bradley makes a shocking discovery about Clare. Jase takes on a risky job and Shabnam encourages her family to think big.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Jase Dyer; Terry Bates; Dawn Swann; Lucas Johnson; Max Branning; Tanya Branning; Lauren Branning; Abi Branning; Jack Branning; Ronnie Mitchell; Shabnam Masood; Masood Ahmed; Zainab Masood; Tamwar Masood</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00cwdpm</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00cwdpm</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5230269009924211852.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>03/08/2008</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Roxy and Sean's bombshell throws the Slater household into chaos; will they make it up the aisle? Shirley takes on Phil following Ben's appearance in the talent show, but has she gone too far?</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Roxy and Sean's bombshell throws the Slater household into chaos - will they make it up the aisle? Shirley takes on Phil following Ben's appearance in the talent show, but has she gone too far?</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Roxy Mitchell; Sean Slater; Shirley Carter; Phil Mitchell; Ben Mitchell; Jase Dyer; Terry Bates; Dawn Swann; Lucas Johnson; Max Branning; Tanya Branning; Lauren Branning; Abi Branning; Jack Branning; Ronnie Mitchell</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00czd5b</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00czd5b</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5232849855772379884.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>10/08/2008</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Tensions run high in the Mitchell household, with drastic consequences for all. Meanwhile, Dot tries to help Clare.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Tensions run high in the Mitchell household, whilst Dot tries to help Clare. The Masoods try to follow their dream but come into conflict with a belligerent Ian. Dot's adamant that she can't face Jim's birthday homecoming but will Bradley and Stacey respect her wishes?</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Bradley Branning; Stacey Branning; Dot Branning; Max Branning; Suzy Branning; Peggy Mitchell; Archie Mitchell; Ian Beale; Christian Clarke; Peter Beale; Masood Ahmed; Zainab Masood; Tamwar Masood; Shabnam Masood; Ricky Butcher</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00d6g65</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00d6g65</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5235455182938329306.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>17/08/2008</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Old friends and family rally round to welcome Jim home for his birthday. Wellard's health takes a turn for the worse, forcing the family to make a difficult decision.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Emotions run high as Jim returns to the Square for his birthday party, but will Dot be able to confront her fears? Max gets disappointing news and is driven to punish his father before discovering something intriguing about Jack's past, and Ronnie's attempts to get back at Archie lead her to question her life in Walford.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Ricky Butcher; Bianca Jackson; Tiffany Dean; Liam Butcher; Whitney Dean; Ronnie Mitchell; Roxy Mitchell; Sean Slater; Archie Mitchell; Peggy Mitchell; Denise Wicks; Libby Fox; Zainab Masood; Tamwar Masood</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00dkhhl</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00dkhhl</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5240620740101037385.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>31/08/2008</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>On the eve of his wedding, Jase agrees to one final job with Terry, with dramatic consequences. Dawn's hen night doesn't go as she expected and Vinnie is thrown by a surprise visitor.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>On the eve of his wedding, Jase agrees to one final job with Terry, with dramatic consequences. Dawn's hen night doesn't go as planned and Vinnie is thrown by a surprise visitor.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Jase Dyer; Terry Bates; Dawn Swann; Vinnie Monks; Whitney Dean; Ronnie Mitchell; Roxy Mitchell; Sean Slater; Archie Mitchell; Peggy Mitchell; Denise Wicks; Libby Fox; Zainab Masood; Tamwar Masood</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00dbhx6</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00dbhx6</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5243233798203925568.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>07/09/2008</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Dawn picks up the pieces following Jase's death. Billy fights to save his marriage while Stacey struggles to keep Callum at arm's length.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Dawn picks up the pieces following Jase's death. Billy fights to save his marriage while Stacey struggles to keep Callum at arm's length.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Dawn Swann; Billy Mitchell; Stacey Branning; Callum Monks; Whitney Dean; Ronnie Mitchell; Roxy Mitchell; Sean Slater; Archie Mitchell; Peggy Mitchell; Denise Wicks; Libby Fox; Zainab Masood; Tamwar Masood</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00djm23</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00djm23</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5245830105934359183.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>14/09/2008</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Bianca is excited when she receives good news but there are darker forces at work. Max has plans for Jack, while Ian finds that meddling in other people's business can be dangerous.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Bianca is excited to receive good news but there are darker forces at work. Max has plans for Jack, while Ian finds that meddling in other people's business can be dangerous. And should Stacey follow her heart?</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Bianca Jackson; Max Branning; Jack Branning; Ian Beale; Stacey Branning; Whitney Dean; Ronnie Mitchell; Roxy Mitchell; Sean Slater; Archie Mitchell; Peggy Mitchell; Denise Wicks; Libby Fox; Zainab Masood</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00dn8ff</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00dn8ff</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5248439298566680341.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>21/09/2008</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Max shocks Tanya with some hard truths about Jack's past and Stacey finds herself with a big decision to make. Whitney lands the lead role in the school play but the news isn't welcomed by all.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>War breaks out amongst the Brannings when Max shocks Tanya with some hard truths about Jack's past and Stacey finds herself with a big decision to make. Whitney lands the lead role in the school play but the news is not welcomed by all. Danielle has high hopes for her romance with Callum but all is not as it seems.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Max Branning; Tanya Branning; Jack Branning; Stacey Branning; Whitney Dean; Danielle Jones; Callum Monks; Roxy Mitchell; Sean Slater; Archie Mitchell; Peggy Mitchell; Denise Wicks; Libby Fox; Zainab Masood</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00dp23s</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00dp23s</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5251033029316736209.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>28/09/2008</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Suzy makes a discovery about Max, and Tony's jealousy takes a dark turn. Tensions run high between Pat and Archie, Danielle learns Stacey's secret, and Suzy meddles in Denise's lovelife.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Suzy interferes in Denise's love-life and makes a shocking discovery about Max, while Tony's jealousy takes a dark turn with disastrous consequences for all. Tensions run high between Pat and Archie and Danielle discovers Stacey's secret.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Suzy Branning; Denise Wicks; Max Branning; Tony King; Pat Evans; Archie Mitchell; Danielle Jones; Tanya Branning; Stacey Branning; Jack Branning; Whitney Dean; Callum Monks; Roxy Mitchell; Sean Slater</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00dshgz</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00dshgz</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5253646087419594905.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>05/10/2008</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Tony plays a dangerous game with Bianca and Whitney, while his affections take a sinister turn. Ronnie engages Christian's company at her school reunion in her bid to exorcise her demons.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Tony's affections take a sinister turn while he plays a dangerous game with Bianca and Whitney. Ronnie engages Christian's company at her school reunion in a bid to exorcise her demons. Bradley faces up to the truth about his relationship with Stacey.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Tony King; Bianca Jackson; Whitney Dean; Ronnie Mitchell; Christian Clarke; Stacey Branning; Max Branning; Archie Mitchell; Danielle Jones; Tanya Branning; Jack Branning; Callum Monks; Roxy Mitchell; Sean Slater</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00dxk39</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00dxk39</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5256228221757951173.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>12/10/2008</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Tensions run high between Jay and Dawn at Jase's funeral, and Garry leads Dawn to make a decision about her future. Danielle gets caught up in Ronnie and Archie's ongoing battle.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Tensions run high between Jay and Dawn at Jase's funeral and Garry leaves Dawn to make a decision about her future. Danielle gets caught up between Ronnie and Archie's ongoing battle and Tony has his work cut out to keep things between him and Whitney a secret.

	Things take a surprising turn for Billy and Jay, whilst Christian's new relationship forces him to face up to an unwanted truth.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Jay Brown; Dawn Swann; Garry Hobbs; Danielle Jones; Ronnie Mitchell; Archie Mitchell; Tony King; Whitney Dean; Billy Mitchell; Christian Clarke; Bianca Jackson; Stacey Branning; Max Branning; Tanya Branning; Pat Evans</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00f0sw1</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00f0sw1</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5258818087037440299.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>19/10/2008</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Tanya and Jack come back from France with big plans, but will keeping it secret from Max create cracks in their relationship? Ronnie faces up to the past, while Ian is shocked by Jane's secret.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Tanya and Jack come back from France with big plans, but will keeping them a secret from Max create cracks in their relationship? Ronnie faces up to the past and opens her heart to love again. Ian is shocked to discover Jane's secret.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Tanya Branning; Jack Branning; Max Branning; Ronnie Mitchell; Ian Beale; Jane Beale; Garry Hobbs; Danielle Jones; Archie Mitchell; Whitney Dean; Billy Mitchell; Bianca Jackson; Stacey Branning</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00f91s9</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00f91s9</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5264050645694159353.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>02/11/2008</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Things take a dramatic turn when Max discovers Jack and Tanya's plan to move to France, and a shock event could change the Brannings' lives forever.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>As Jack and Tanya pack for their big move to France, things take dramatic twists and turns when Max discovers their plans and a shock event could change the Brannings' lives forever.

	Denise's life is thrown into disarray when Libby makes a big decision about her future. A bust-up with Ronnie leads Bianca to make a confesssion to Pat about her relationship with Tony.

	Bradley is given hope when he gets his wires crossed with Stacey and Darren takes his driving test.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Tanya Branning; Jack Branning; Abi Branning; Lauren Branning; Max Branning; Bradley Branning; Dot Branning; Stacey Branning; Callum Monks; Danielle Jones; Libby Fox; Darren Miller; Denise Wicks; Lucas Johnson; Pat Evans</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00fgq3j</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00fgq3j</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5266645664934403562.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>09/11/2008</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Suspicion falls on Jack as the police investigation into Max's accident gets underway and Tanya's left reeling when Lauren makes a shocking revelation.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Suspicion falls on Jack as the police investigation into Max's accident gets underway, and Tanya is left reeling when Lauren makes a shocking revelation. 

	Sean has to take action when Archie's manipulations go too far, and Dot becomes concerned by Bradley's strange behaviour. 

	Meanwhile, Ben confides in Shirley about his fears for the future.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Jack Branning; Tanya Branning; Max Branning; Lauren Branning; Sean Slater; Archie Mitchell; Dot Branning; Bradley Branning; Ben Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Ronnie Mitchell; Bianca Jackson; Pat Evans; Tony King; Stacey Branning</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00flx4v</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00flx4v</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5269245838135402929.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>16/11/2008</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Shockwaves hit the Brannings when the identity of Max's would-be murderer is revealed, while a terrified Roxy goes into early labour, with Sean nowhere to be seen.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Shockwaves hit the Brannings when the identity of Max's would-be murderer is revealed, while a terrified Roxy goes into early labour, with Sean nowhere to be seen. Elsewhere, Masood takes drastic action to save his business, and Jane is thrown when her mum turns up on the Square with some shocking news.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Roxy Slater; Peggy Mitchell; Archie Mitchell; Jack Branning; Tanya Branning; Lauren Branning; Abi Branning; Bradley Branning; Stacey Branning; Masood Ahmed; Zainab Masood; Phil Mitchell; Ben Mitchell; Suzy Branning; Dot Branning</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00fnr3k</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00fnr3k</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5271844722846213628.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>23/11/2008</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Everyone's worried when Roxy's rushed to hospital in premature labour and it looks like Archie will get his way when Sean is nowhere to be seen. Christian reassesses his life.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Everyone is worried when Roxy is rushed to hospital in premature labour, and it looks like Archie will get his way when Sean is nowhere to be seen. Christian reassesses his life whilst Bradley discovers that Max can still affect him. Vinnie turns to Shirley for help and Whitney struggles with her feelings for Tony.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Roxy Slater; Archie Mitchell; Sean Slater; Christian Clarke; Bradley Branning; Max Branning; Vinnie Monks; Shirley Carter; Whitney Dean; Tony King; Jane Beale; Ronnie Mitchell; Heather Trott; Suzy Branning; Phil Mitchell</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00fszbh</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00fszbh</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5274434588125702436.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>30/11/2008</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Max battles to win back his life and his kids, but behind his back Tony is taking sinister steps to get closer to Lauren. Phil's relationship with Shirley takes a dramatic twist.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Max battles to win back his life and kids but, behind his back, Tony is taking sinister steps to get closer to Lauren. Phil's relationship with Shirley takes a dramatic twist, leaving Shirley in a quandary about her future. Lucas stuns Denise with his beliefs and Lucy is determined to prove her dad is wrong about her.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Max Branning; Tony King; Lauren Branning; Phil Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Lucas Johnson; Denise Wicks; Lucy Beale; Ricky Butcher; Jack Branning; Tanya Branning; Vinnie Monks; Chelsea Fox; Patrick Trueman; Whitney Dean</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00g31dl</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00g31dl</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5279641376978644926.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>14/12/2008</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Whitney's birthday is thrown into disarray when the truth comes out about her and Tony. Roxy is pressured into getting a paternity test and Lucas's faith forces Denise to make a sacrifice.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Whitney's 16th birthday is thrown into disarray when the truth comes out about her and Tony. Roxy is pressured by Jack into getting a paternity test, and Lucas' faith forces Denise to make a massive sacrifice.

	If you are affected by any of the issues in this episode of EastEnders, information regarding sources of help, support and advice can be found at:
	http://www.bbc.co.uk/eastenders/news/news_20081104.shtml.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Roxy Slater; Christian Clarke; Sean Slater; Bianca Jackson; Tiffany Dean; Tony King; Pat Evans; Ricky Butcher; Lucas Johnson; Denise Wicks; Libby Fox; Darren Miller; Lauren Branning; Max Branning; Jane Beale</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00g4dys</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00g4dys</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5282235107728699991.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>21/12/2008</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Bianca and Whitney struggle with life after Tony, while Roxy tries desperately to keep her secret safe from Sean. Meanwhile, Suzy makes a surprising announcement.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Bianca and Whitney struggle with life after Tony, while Roxy tries desperately to keep her secret safe from Sean. Meanwhile, Suzy makes a surprising announcement, and Pat, Billy and Ricky race to stop Janine's latest devious deception.

	If you are affected by any of the issues in this episode of EastEnders, information regarding sources of help, support and advice can be found at:
	http://www.bbc.co.uk/eastenders/news/news_20081104.shtml.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Ricky Butcher; Pat Evans; Janine Butcher; Roxy Slater; Sean Slater; Archie Mitchell; Peggy Mitchell; Suzy Branning; Phil Mitchell; Ben Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Heather Trott; Dot Branning; Billy Mitchell; Denise Wicks; Patrick Trueman; Charlie Slater; Ronnie Mitchell; Jack Branning; Bianca Jackson; Whitney Dean; Liam Butcher; Whitney Dean; Christian Clarke; Ahmet; Scally; Will Holden; Sarah; David; Rabbi; Reverend Stevens</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00gfk6q</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00gfk6q</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5284846877341398011.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>28/12/2008</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Everything is set up for a perfect Mitchell Christmas until Sean discovers Roxy's terrible secret. Ian the Scrooge finally discovers his Christmas spirit and Suzy gets the exit she deserves.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Everything is set up for a perfect Mitchell Christmas until Sean discovers Roxy's terrible secret. Ian the Scrooge finally discovers his Christmas spirit, Suzy gets the exit she deserves, and Dot is resigned to spending Chrismas alone until a nasty figure from the past comes knocking.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Roxy Slater; Dot Branning; Nick Cotton; Dotty Cotton; Shirley Carter; Suzy Branning; Phil Mitchell; Sean Slater; Ronnie Mitchell; Jack Branning; Archie Mitchell; Peggy Mitchell; Billy Mitchell; Ben Mitchell; Jay Brown; Stacey Branning; Danielle Jones; Charlie Slater; Mo Harris; Jean Slater; Bradley Branning; Jim Branning; Garry Hobbs; Minty Peterson; Christian Clarke; Ian Beale; Jane Beale; Linda Clarke; Peter Beale; Lucy Beale; Bobby Beale; Heather Trott; Dawn Swann; Darren Miller; Zainab Masood; Masood Ahmed; Tamwar Masood; Pat Evans; Bianca Jackson; Ricky Butcher; Janine Butcher; Whitney Dean; Liam Butcher; Tiffany Dean; Patrick Trueman; Denise Wicks; Chelsea Fox; Libby Fox; Tanya Branning; Brenda Boyle; Aunt Sal; Paul</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00gjcfn</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00gjcfn</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5287439319601264181.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>04/01/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Amy is still missing, and as it emerges that Jean holds the key to her safe return, Sean disappears from the Square - but not without one last goodbye.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Amy is still missing, and as it emerges that Jean holds the key to her safe return, Sean disappears from the Square - but not without one last goodbye.

	Ricky does his best to bring new year cheer to Bianca and her brood, and Shirley does the same for Heather, but Stacey and Tanya face heartbreaking decisions.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Lauren Branning; Max Branning; Tanya Branning; Roxy Slater; Sean Slater; Ronnie Mitchell; Jack Branning; Stacey Branning; Jean Slater; Archie Mitchell; Peggy Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Heather Trott; Phil Mitchell; Ben Mitchell; Mo Harris; Charlie Slater; Callum Monks; Whitney Dean; Janine Butcher; Bianca Jackson; Ricky Butcher; Pat Evans; Liam Butcher; Tiffany Dean; Dot Branning; Nick Cotton; Dotty Cotton; Bradley Branning; Abi Branning; Denise Wicks; Chelsea Fox; Libby Fox; Zainab Masood; Tamwar Masood; Christian Clarke; Danielle Jones; Patrick Trueman; Darren Miller; PC Lance; Kendra Hill-Smythe; Crown Court Judge; Clerk of the Court; Neighbour; Carouser; Man in Flat</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00gllpt</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00gllpt</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5290025319410186490.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>11/01/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Max goes from hope to devastation in his struggle to keep his family together. Dot tries to come to terms with Nick's proposition, and Whitney's search for her birth mother ends in heartbreak.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Max goes from hope to devastation in his struggle to keep his family together, while Dot tries to come to terms with Nick's nasty proposition, and Whitney's journey to find her birth mother ends in heartbreak. 

	Meanwhile, Danielle sails close to the wind with Ronnie.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Danielle Jones; Ronnie Mitchell; Lauren Branning; Max Branning; Jack Branning; Ian Beale; Jane Beale; Dot Branning; Nick Cotton; Dotty Cotton; Bradley Branning; Jay Brown; Billy Mitchell; Janine Butcher; Peggy Mitchell; Archie Mitchell; Denise Wicks; Lucas Johnson; Zainab Masood; Libby Fox; Tamwar Masood; Heather Trott; Shirley Carter; Stacey Branning; Charlie Slater; Mo Harris; Jean Slater; Callum Monks; Paul; Lucy Beale; Linda Clarke; Tanya Branning; Kendra Hill-Smythe; Abi Branning; Pat Evans; Patrick Trueman; Whitney Dean; Bianca Jackson; Tiffany Dean; Debra Dean; Waitress; DS Grimwood; Crown Court Judge; Desk Sergeant; Guard</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00gvg6j</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00gvg6j</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5292624204120996763.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>18/01/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Lucas and Denise finally commit to each other but is there a dark secret in Lucas' past? Meanwhile, Jean continues on a downward spiral ending with a heartbreaking decision.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Lucas and Denise finally commit to each other, but is there a dark secret in Lucas' past? Meanwhile, Jean continues on a downward spiral which ends in a hearbreaking decision. 

	Elsewhere, Danielle reveals her secret to Ronnie, Jay befriends a working girl, and Peggy's anti-filth campaign lands her in trouble with the law.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Stacey Branning; Jean Slater; Mo Harris; Charlie Slater; Danielle Jones; Ronnie Mitchell; Denise Wicks; Lucas Johnson; Chelsea Fox; Libby Fox; Jordan Johnson; Zainab Masood; Billy Mitchell; Jay Brown; Janine Butcher; Peggy Mitchell; Archie Mitchell; Roxy Slater; Patrick Trueman; Heather Trott; Minty Peterson; Jack Branning; Callum Monks; Dot Branning; Dotty Cotton; Ian Beale; PC Kenny Morris; Paul; Marissa; Elaine; Andy; Ticket Inspector</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00h45sr</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00h45sr</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5295223088831807011.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>25/01/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Tanya returns to the Square a changed woman. Janine's plans to escape Walford are foiled by Peggy, so she decides to wreak havoc in R&amp;R. Jay's relationship with Marissa escalates.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Tanya returns to the Square, but she is not the woman she was when she left. 

	Janine's plans to escape Walford are foiled by Peggy, so she decides to wreak havoc in R&amp;R. 

	Meanwhile, Jay's relationship with Marissa escalates, and Dot awaits Jim's return.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Dotty Cotton; Nick Cotton; Dot Branning; Billy Mitchell; Jay Brown; Marissa; Janine Butcher; Ronnie Mitchell; Jack Branning; Max Branning; Tanya Branning; Lauren Branning; Abi Branning; Bradley Branning; Jane Beale; Ian Beale; Christian Clarke; Peter Beale; Zainab Masood; Chelsea Fox; Peggy Mitchell; Pat Evans; Stacey Branning; Danielle Jones; Charlie Slater; Linda Clarke; Kieran; Social Worker</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00hd33v</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00hd33v</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5297820685052472127.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>01/02/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Janine wreaks wicked havoc on Ronnie and Jack. Meanwhile, Jay is pushed to the limit by his relationship with Marissa, and Bradley and Max's relationship takes an unexpected twist.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Janine wreaks wicked havoc on Ronnie and Jack. Meanwhile, Jay is pushed to the limit by his relationship with Marissa, and Bradley and Max's relationship takes an unexpected twist.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Janine Butcher; Jack Branning; Ronnie Mitchell; Billy Mitchell; Jay Brown; Marissa; Patrick Trueman; Linda Clarke; Denise Wicks; Lucas Johnson; Chelsea Fox; Libby Fox; Jordan Johnson; Jane Beale; Christian Clarke; Ian Beale; Zainab Masood; Masood Ahmed; Phil Mitchell; Ben Mitchell; Bradley Branning; Max Branning; Tanya Branning; Stacey Branning; Dot Branning; Theo Kelly; Don; Deputy Editor</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00hgmgx</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00hgmgx</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5300410550331962313.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>08/02/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Ronnie reaches out to Danielle, before breaking her heart. Meanwhile, Bianca celebrates Tiffany's birthday with a shocking confession, and Linda wreaks havoc on Ian and Christian.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Ronnie finally reaches out to Danielle, before breaking her heart. 

	Meanwhile, Bianca celebrates Tiffany's birthday with a shocking confession, Linda wreaks havoc on Ian and Christian, and Archie is set on ending Peggy's foray into politics.

	If you are affected by any of the issues in this episode of EastEnders, information regarding sources of help, support and advice can be found at:

	http://www.bbc.co.uk/eastenders/news/news_20081104.shtml.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Bianca Jackson; Shirley Carter; Ricky Butcher; Whitney Dean; Tiffany Dean; Danielle Jones; Stacey Branning; Ronnie Mitchell; Dot Branning; Ian Beale; Linda Clarke; Roger Clarke; Heather Trott; Garry Hobbs; Minty Peterson; Bradley Branning; Syd Chambers; Darren Miller; Libby Fox; Janine Butcher; Jack Branning; Max Branning; Peggy Mitchell; Archie Mitchell; Roxy Slater; Callum Monks; Peter Beale; Billy Mitchell; Masood Ahmed; Zainab Masood; Liam Butcher; Bobby Beale; Dr Maynard; DS Louise Hill</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00hpdrs</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00hpdrs</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5300433743159556513.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>08/02/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Ronnie reaches out to Danielle before breaking her heart. Meanwhile, Bianca celebrates Tiffany's birthday with a shocking confession, and Linda wreaks havoc on Ian and Christian.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Ronnie finally reaches out to Danielle before breaking her heart. 

	Meanwhile, Bianca celebrates Tiffany's birthday with a shocking confession, Linda wreaks havoc on Ian and Christian, and Archie is set on ending Peggy's foray into politics.

	If you are affected by any of the issues in this episode of EastEnders, information regarding sources of help, support and advice can be found at:

	http://www.bbc.co.uk/eastenders/news/news_20081104.shtml.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Bianca Jackson; Shirley Carter; Ricky Butcher; Whitney Dean; Tiffany Dean; Danielle Jones; Stacey Branning; Ronnie Mitchell; Dot Branning; Ian Beale; Linda Clarke; Roger Clarke; Heather Trott; Garry Hobbs; Minty Peterson; Bradley Branning; Syd Chambers; Darren Miller; Libby Fox; Janine Butcher; Jack Branning; Max Branning; Peggy Mitchell; Archie Mitchell; Roxy Slater; Callum Monks; Peter Beale; Billy Mitchell; Masood Ahmed; Zainab Masood; Liam Butcher; Bobby Beale; Dr Maynard; DS Louise Hill</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00hmj3j</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00hmj3j</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5303026185415228226.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>15/02/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Bianca and Ricky struggle with the possibility that Ricky is Tiffany's father, while Hev and Shirl take a trip to George Michael's house, and Garry's life is turned upside-down.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Bianca and Ricky struggle with the possibility that Ricky is Tiffany's father, while Hev and Shirl take a trip to George Michael's house, and Garry's life is turned upside-down.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Dawn Swann; Minty Peterson; Garry Hobbs; Shirley Carter; Heather Trott; Bianca Jackson; Ricky Butcher; Whitney Dean; Tiffany Dean; Liam Butcher; Darren Miller; Christian Clarke; Callum Monks; Phil Mitchell; Todd; Eddie; Waiter; Tim; Les; PC Henderson</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00j06pc</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00j06pc</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5305617339184877785.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>22/02/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Dawn realises her true feelings for Garry, but is it too late? Ricky and Bianca receive life-changing news, and Tanya waits to hear if she is going back behind bars.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Dawn realises her true feelings for Garry as the residents of Walford attend his memorial service, but is it too late?

	Ricky and Bianca receive life-changing news, and Tanya waits to hear if she is going back behind bars. The Beales and Masoods try to work together in harmony.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Bianca Jackson; Ricky Butcher; Tiffany Dean; Liam Butcher; Whitney Dean; Tanya Branning; Jane Beale; Abi Branning; Max Branning; Dawn Swann; Garry Hobbs; Shirley Carter; Heather Trott; Callum Monks; Minty Peterson</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00hxyb7</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00hxyb7</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5308226531817199474.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>01/03/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Five years of tension bubble over in the Masood house, while Lucas and Patrick make a pact to keep their secrets safe. And Ian's 40th birthday party starts well but ends in shame.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Five years of tension bubble over in the Masood house, while Lucas and Patrick make a grim pact to keep their secrets safe. Meanwhile, Ian's 40th birthday party in the Vic starts well but ends shamefully.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Janine Butcher; Peggy Mitchell; Pat Evans; Ian Beale; Jane Beale; Tanya Branning; Christian Clarke; Patrick Trueman; Lucas Johnson; Denise Wicks; Chelsea Fox; Theo Kelly; Libby Fox; Tamwar Masood; Zainab Masood</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00j3vrn</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00j3vrn</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5310822839547632763.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>08/03/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>As Stacey spirals out of control, Danielle's attempts to cheer her up lead to disaster. Peggy's political dreams lie in tatters after a scheming Janine wreaks her revenge.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>As Stacey continues to spiral out of control, Danielle's attempts to cheer her up lead to disaster. 

	Peggy's political dreams lie in tatters after a scheming Janine wreaks her revenge. 

	Jack makes Roxy an offer she finds hard to refuse, and Callum reaches a momentous decision about his life.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Roxy Slater; Jack Branning; Ronnie Mitchell; Stacey Branning; Callum Monks; Jean Slater; Garry Hobbs; Peggy Mitchell; Archie Mitchell; Pat Evans; Patrick Trueman; Janine Butcher; Billy Mitchell; Darren Miller; Ian Beale; Jane Beale; Tanya Branning; Christian Clarke; Zainab Masood; Masood Ahmed; Tamwar Masood; Mo Harris; Danielle Jones; Charlie Slater; Brenda Boyle; Minty Peterson; Dot Branning; Bradley Branning; Syd Chambers; Paul; Aunt Sal; Olive; Manda Best</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00j8dq4</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00j8dq4</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5313398531435045858.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>15/03/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Danielle thinks of new ways to get closer to her mother, while Ronnie and Roxy get mixed up in Peggy's electioneering. Billy opens the door to Jay but closes another from his past.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Danielle thinks of new ways to get closer to her mother, while Ronnie and Roxy get mixed up in Peggy's electioneering. 

	Billy opens the door to Jay but closes another from his past, and Minty finds that an old friend might be a new flame.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Jay Brown; Billy Mitchell; Ronnie Mitchell; Roxy Slater; Archie Mitchell; Peggy Mitchell; Phil Mitchell; Jack Branning; Ian Beale; Jane Beale; Tanya Branning; Masood Ahmed; Zainab Masood; Shirley Carter; Heather Trott; Minty Peterson; Manda Best; Patrick Trueman; Janine Butcher; Jean Slater; Stacey Branning; Danielle Jones; Dawn Swann; Lucy Beale; Paul; PC Kenny Morris; Custody Sergeant; PC Annie Young</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00j9lz5</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00j9lz5</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5316007724067368375.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>22/03/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Archie presents Peggy with a dark ultimatum about the wedding. Chelsea brings Theo home for dinner, much to Patrick's displeasure, and Max has a surprise dinner date of his own.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Archie presents Peggy with a dark ultimatum about the wedding. Chelsea brings Theo home for dinner, much to Patrick's displeasure, and Max has a surprise dinner date of his own.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Archie Mitchell; Ronnie Mitchell; Danielle Jones; Roxy Slater; Max Branning; Tanya Branning; Peggy Mitchell; Billy Mitchell; Jay Brown; Lucas Johnson; Patrick Trueman; Chelsea Fox; Denise Wicks; Theo Kelly; Charlie Slater; Pat Evans; Abi Branning; Jack Branning; Heather Trott; Minty Peterson; Shirley Carter; Ian Beale; Jane Beale; Masood Ahmed; Zainab Masood; Mo Harris; Dot Branning; Janine Butcher; Polly; Reverend Stevens; Mohinder Singh</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00jkcrg</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00jkcrg</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5318609185758554501.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>29/03/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Archie begins to buckle under the pressure of Danielle's constant presence. Janine comes round to the idea that family is important, and Bradley makes headway in his relationship with Syd.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Archie begins to buckle under the pressure of Danielle's constant presence. 

	Janine comes round to the idea that family is important, and Bradley makes headway in his relationship with Syd.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Archie Mitchell; Danielle Jones; Roxy Slater; Ronnie Mitchell; Jack Branning; Peggy Mitchell; Pat Evans; Bianca Jackson; Ricky Butcher; Janine Butcher; Tiffany Dean; Liam Butcher; Ian Beale; Jane Beale; Zainab Masood; Jean Slater; Bradley Branning; Syd Chambers; Max Branning; Tanya Branning; Abi Branning; Billy Mitchell; Jay Brown; Patrick Trueman; Denise Wicks; Chelsea Fox; Theo Kelly; Minty Peterson; Manda Best; Charlie Slater; Mo Harris; Phil Mitchell; Ben Mitchell; Darren Miller; Tommy Clifford; Polly; Sandra; Rupert; Portia</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00jvb1b</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00jvb1b</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5321170704253895214.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>05/04/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Archie goes to extreme lengths to silence Danielle, but the Mitchell wedding is rocked by her explosive revelations. A devastating event changes everything.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Archie goes to extreme lengths to silence Danielle, but the Mitchell wedding is rocked by her explosive revelations. 

	A devastating event changes everything and Ronnie's grief leads her into a terrible deception.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Ronnie Mitchell; Andy Jones; Danielle Jones; Archie Mitchell; Roxy Slater; Phil Mitchell; Billy Mitchell; Janine Butcher; Stacey Branning; Peggy Mitchell; Pat Evans; Aunt Sal; Charlie Slater; Ian Beale; Jane Beale</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00jqg3p</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00jqg3p</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5323778608396028180.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>12/04/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Peggy returns to the Square, intent on settling things with Archie, while Lauren's future hangs in the balance as she comes to trial. And Patrick faces the demons of his past.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Peggy returns to the Square, intent on settling things with Archie, while Lauren's future hangs in the balance as she comes to trial. And Patrick comes face-to-face with the demons of his past.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Peggy Mitchell; Phil Mitchell; Archie Mitchell; Roxy Slater; Ronnie Mitchell; Lauren Branning; Tanya Branning; Max Branning; Abi Branning; Jane Beale; Peter Beale; Patrick Trueman; Tommy Clifford; Chelsea Fox; Theo Kelly; Libby Fox; Darren Miller; Denise Wicks; Lucas Johnson; Whitney Dean; Todd; Ricky Butcher; Tiffany Dean; Stacey Branning; Mo Harris; Jean Slater; Charlie Slater; Brenda Boyle; Billy Mitchell; Janine Butcher; Pat Evans; Bradley Branning; Jack Branning; Ben Mitchell; Clive Robinson; Social Worker; Mrs Weston; Judge; Clerk of the Court; Kendra Hill-Smythe; Jury Foreman</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00jzjn5</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00jzjn5</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5326387801028349263.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>19/04/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>The Square struggle to come to terms with tragedy, while Dot discovers that Dotty has been in touch with Nick. Shirley keeps Phil's secret and Patrick refuses to face his past.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>The Square struggle to come to terms with tragedy, while Dot discovers that Dotty has been in touch with Nick. Meanwhile, Shirley keeps Phil's dirty secret and Patrick refuses to face his past.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Jack Branning; Roxy Slater; Ronnie Mitchell; Stacey Branning; Andy Jones; Charlie Slater; Jean Slater; Shirley Carter; Phil Mitchell; Ben Mitchell; Heather Trott; Dot Branning; Dotty Cotton; Nick Cotton; Max Branning</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00k369s</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00k369s</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5328999570641048431.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>26/04/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Syed Masood is reunited with Zainab, but how will his father take the news? Roxy and Jack share an illicit kiss, and Dot is perturbed by strange goings-on in the Branning house.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>The prodigal son returns as Syed Masood is reunited with Zainab, but how will his father take the news? 

	Roxy and Jack share an illicit kiss, and Dot is perturbed by strange goings-on in the Branning household. Meanwhile, Patrick finally confronts Tommy Clifford.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Masood Ahmed; Syed Masood; Zainab Masood; Roxy Slater; Ronnie Mitchell; Jack Branning; Max Branning; Tanya Branning; Phil Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Heather Trott; Patrick Trueman; Tommy Clifford; Denise Wicks; Chelsea Fox</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00k8f69</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00k8f69</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5329022763468644559.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>26/04/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Syed Masood is reunited with Zainab, but how will his father take the news? Roxy and Jack share an illicit kiss, and Dot is perturbed by strange goings-on in the Branning house.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>The prodigal son returns as Syed Masood is reunited with Zainab, but how will his father take the news? 

	Roxy and Jack share an illicit kiss, and Dot is perturbed by strange goings-on in the Branning household. Meanwhile, Patrick finally confronts Tommy Clifford.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Masood Ahmed; Syed Masood; Zainab Masood; Roxy Slater; Ronnie Mitchell; Jack Branning; Max Branning; Tanya Branning; Phil Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Heather Trott; Patrick Trueman; Tommy Clifford; Denise Wicks; Chelsea Fox; Theo Kelly; Libby Fox; Dot Branning; Nick Cotton; Dotty Cotton; Ian Beale; Jane Beale; Stacey Branning; Christian Clarke; Tamwar Masood; Ben Mitchell; Val; Roger</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00k6lxj</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00k6lxj</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5331593301391104626.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>03/05/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Heather takes action to protect her friend, with shocking results. The Masood family are thrown into chaos while Billy and Jay worry for each other as the trial looms.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Heather takes tough love action to protect her friend, with shocking results. The Masood family are thrown into chaos as the prodigal son returns. 

	Billy and Jay worry for each other as the trial over Jase's murder looms heavy, and Whitney's steps into friendship with Todd are not wholly successful.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Heather Trott; Dr Al Jenkins; Billy Mitchell; Jay Brown; Dot Branning; Nick Cotton; Zainab Masood; Masood Ahmed; Syed Masood; Christian Clarke; Tamwar Masood; Phil Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Ronnie Mitchell; Roxy Slater</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00kfclb</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00kfclb</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5334183166670595181.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>10/05/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Birthday greetings turn to blackmail for Billy, and Ronnie throws Amy a christening to remember. Zainab's romantic plans backfire, while Jack comes to a romantic epiphany.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Birthday greetings turn to blackmail for Billy, and Ronnie throws Amy a christening to remember, but for all the wrong reasons. 

	Zainab's romantic plans backfire disastrously, and Jack comes to a romantic epiphany. But will it be too late?</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Ronnie Mitchell; Jack Branning; Roxy Slater; Billy Mitchell; Nick Cotton; Jay Brown; Phil Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Peggy Mitchell; Zainab Masood; Masood Ahmed; Tamwar Masood; Syed Masood; Janine Butcher; Tanya Branning; Max Branning; Dr Al Jenkins; Jane Beale; Ian Beale; Christian Clarke; Heather Trott; Dawn Swann; Garry Hobbs; Minty Peterson; Ricky Butcher; Darren Miller; Denise Wicks; Chelsea Fox; Stacey Branning; Jean Slater; Charlie Slater; Dot Branning; Ben Mitchell; Reverend Stevens; Amira Shah; Check-In Desk Woman</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00kks0f</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00kks0f</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5336761435538386209.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>17/05/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Phil's drinking throws the Mitchells into crisis, Tanya's love life gets a diagnosis and Jack and Ronnie go back to basics. Jean is forced to confront the truth about her daughter.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Phil's drinking throws the Mitchell women into crisis, while Tanya's love life gets a diagnosis and Jack and Ronnie go back to basics. 

	And as Stacey's behaviour spirals out of control, Jean is forced to confront the devastating truth about her daughter.

	If you are affected by any of the issues in this episode of EastEnders, please visit the address below for information regarding sources of help, support, and advice:

	http://www.bbc.co.uk/eastenders/news/news_20081104.shtml.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Stacey Branning; Jean Slater; Bradley Branning; Max Branning; Tanya Branning; Charlie Slater; Mo Harris; Ronnie Mitchell; Jack Branning; Roxy Slater; Dot Branning; Nick Cotton; Billy Mitchell; Ian Beale; Jane Beale</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00kpycc</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00kpycc</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5339374493641274357.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>24/05/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Nick forces Billy into a horrible mistake, before Phil defends the Mitchell name with horrifying results. Bradley learns Syd's secret; will this mean the end of their relationship?</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Nick forces Billy into a horrible mistake, before Phil defends the Mitchell name with horrifying results. Bradley learns Syd's secret; will this mean the end of their relationship?</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Nick Cotton; Dotty Cotton; Dot Branning; Billy Mitchell; Dawn Swann; Jay Brown; Phil Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Peggy Mitchell; Chelsea Fox; Theo Kelly; Libby Fox; Jordan Johnson; Patrick Trueman; Stacey Branning</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00ktqxb</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00ktqxb</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5341975955332463984.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>31/05/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Billy has to face his demons, but can he save Jay and bring Jase's killer to justice? Nick and Dotty cement their plans for Dot's death, and Jack discovers how fragile Ronnie is.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Billy has to face up to his demons, but can he save Jay and bring Jase's killer to justice? 

	Nick and Dotty cement their plans for Dot's death, Jack discovers how fragile Ronnie really is, and Ian forces Mo to make the ultimate sacrifice.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Dot Branning; Nick Cotton; Dotty Cotton; Billy Mitchell; Jay Brown; Minty Peterson; Garry Hobbs; Dawn Swann; Phil Mitchell; Ben Mitchell; Ronnie Mitchell; Jack Branning; Roxy Slater; Bradley Branning; Syd Chambers</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00l1627</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00l1627</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5344574840043246379.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>07/06/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Nick and Dotty's murderous plan comes to an explosive end. Bianca tries to be a proper mother to Whitney, and Christian realises that being Ian Beale isn't as easy as it looks.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Nick and Dotty's murderous plan comes to an explosive end. Bianca tries to be a proper mother to Whitney, and Christian realises that being Ian Beale isn't as easy as it looks.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Whitney Dean; Debra Dean; Bianca Jackson; Dot Branning; Dotty Cotton; Nick Cotton; Bradley Branning; Syd Chambers; Max Branning; Tanya Branning; Patrick Trueman; Garry Hobbs; Dawn Swann; Phil Mitchell; Christan Clarke</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00l76yt</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00l76yt</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5347167282303113665.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>14/06/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>The unexpected return of Whitney's mother threatens to tear Bianca and Whitney apart, while Ronnie harbours a secret that could destroy her relationship with Jack.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>The unexpected return of Whitney's mother threatens to tear Bianca and Whitney apart. 

	Ronnie harbours a secret that could destroy her relationship with Jack, while Syed has a surprising announcement for his family. 

	Meanwhile, will Chelsea be able to resist her old demons?</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Whitney Dean; Debra Dean; Bianca Jackson; Ricky Butcher; Ronnie Mitchell; Roxy Slater; Jack Branning; Tanya Branning; Max Branning; Denise Wicks; Chelsea Fox; Lucas Johnson; Theo Kelly; Ellis Prince; Zainab Masood</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00lbtdb</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00lbtdb</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5349771320974680424.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>21/06/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Christian has a shock, and a bedraggled Stacey returns to the Square. Meanwhile, Denise and Lucas cannot keep Chelsea under control, and Whitney recovers from Debra's latest visit.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Christian gets a bit of a shock, and a bedraggled Stacey returns to the Square. 

	Meanwhile, Denise and Lucas cannot keep Chelsea under control, and Whitney picks up the pieces from Debra's latest visit.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Syed Masood; Christan Clarke; Zainab Masood; Amira Shah; Lucas Johnson; Denise Wicks; Chelsea Fox; Libby Fox; Darren Miller; Whitney Dean; Bianca Jackson; Stacey Branning; Jean Slater; Bradley Branning; Charlie Slater</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00ldhc5</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00ldhc5</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5352354743803225263.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>28/06/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Ronnie's secret threatens to tear her relationship with Jack apart. Christian has hopes for his new relationship, but things don't go as expected.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Ronnie's secret threatens to tear her relationship with Jack apart. Christian has hopes for his new relationship, but things don't go as expected.

	Meanwhile, Lucas is losing control of his plans. Denise's dreams are splintering, and Trina is there to exploit it all.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Lucas Johnson; Trina Johnson; Denise Wicks; Patrick Trueman; Christan Clarke; Syed Masood; Amira Shah; Zainab Masood; Masood Ahmed; Ian Beale; Jane Beale; Roxy Slater; Jack Branning; Ronnie Mitchell; Minty Peterson</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00llk75</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00llk75</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5354914973808375695.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>05/07/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Denise struggles to forgive Lucas, unaware that Trina has more nasty surprises in store. Minty makes a shocking discovery in the Arches, while Heather faces a life-changing decision.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Denise struggles to forgive Lucas, unaware that Trina has more nasty surprises in store. Minty makes a shocking discovery in the Arches, while Heather faces a life-changing decision.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Minty Peterson; Manda Best; Phil Mitchell; Roxy Slater; Jack Branning; Denise Wicks; Lucas Johnson; Trina Johnson; Jordan Johnson; Janine Butcher; Amira Shah; Syed Masood; Zainab Masood; Masood Ahmed; Tamwar Masood</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00lp1bf</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00lp1bf</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5354936878145780735.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>05/07/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Denise struggles to forgive Lucas, unaware that Trina has more nasty surprises in store. Minty makes a shocking discovery in the Arches, while Heather faces a life-changing decision.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Denise struggles to forgive Lucas, unaware that Trina has more surprises in store. Minty makes a shocking discovery in the Arches, while Heather faces a life-changing decision.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Minty Peterson; Manda Best; Phil Mitchell; Roxy Slater; Jack Branning; Denise Wicks; Lucas Johnson; Trina Johnson; Jordan Johnson; Janine Butcher; Amira Shah; Syed Masood; Zainab Masood; Masood Ahmed; Tamwar Masood; Christan Clarke; Ian Beale; Jane Beale; Bobby Beale; Heather Trott; Dr Al Jenkins; Shirley Carter; Dawn Swann; Garry Hobbs; Tanya Branning; Syd Chambers; Bradley Branning; Billy Mitchell; Libby Fox; Darren Miller; Pat Evans; Liam Butcher; Derek Evans; Judge</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00lpkn3</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00lpkn3</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5357558955675792747.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>12/07/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Heather's secret is out, but who's the daddy? Dawn's web of lies falls apart when Minty gives her a brutal ultimatum, and Jordan has a shock announcement.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Heather's secret is out, but who's the daddy? Dawn's web of lies falls apart when Minty gives her a brutal ultimatum, Jordan has a shock announcement, and the new owner of number 27 shocks Peggy to her core.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Peggy Mitchell; Roxy Slater; Archie Mitchell; Heather Trott; Shirley Carter; Manda Best; Minty Peterson; Garry Hobbs; Pat Evans; Denise Wicks; Lucas Johnson; Trina Johnson; Jordan Johnson; Ian Beale; Jane Beale</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00lvzff</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00lvzff</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5360139801528157279.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>19/07/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Archie's return upsets things for Peggy and pushes Phil right to the edge, while Christian discovers Syed is serious about Amira.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Archie's return upsets things for Peggy and pushes Phil right to the edge, while Christian discovers Syed is serious about Amira. Meanwhile, Janine and Ian compete to win the Teeny Weeny Talent Contest, Ricky comes up trumps with Bianca's present, and Max and Tanya get a bit naughty on Dot's kitchen table.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Whitney Dean; Debra Dean; Ricky Butcher; Bianca Jackson; Janine Butcher; Tiffany Dean; Max Branning; Tanya Branning; Stacey Branning; Jean Slater; Mo Harris; Ian Beale; Jane Beale; Bobby Beale; Christian Clarke; Syed Masood; Amira Shah; Zainab Masood; Masood Ahmed; Tamwar Masood; Billy Mitchell; Dot Branning; Dotty Cotton; Liam Butcher; Archie Mitchell; Peggy Mitchell; Phil Mitchell; Ben Mitchell; Roxy Slater; Ronnie Mitchell; Charlie Slater; Man; Lauren Branning; Abi Branning; Colin; Ed; Support Group Man</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00lyr01</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00lyr01</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5362768321513312336.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>26/07/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Stacey hits rock bottom but with the support of Jean, sees a light at the end of the tunnel. A mysterious stranger from Whitney's past returns. Continues on BBC One.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Stacey hits rock bottom but with the support of Jean, finally sees a light at the end of the tunnel. A mysterious stranger from Whitney's past returns, but is he who he says he is? Max and Tanya tentatively decide to try again, but Stacey has other ideas.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Stacey Branning; Jean Slater; Whitney Dean; Bianca Jackson; Ryan Malloy; Debra Dean; Max Branning; Tanya Branning; Lauren Branning; Abi Branning; Charlie Slater; Mo Harris; Dr Al Jenkins; Ronnie Mitchell; Garry Hobbs; Nurse Kennedy; Dr Simmonds; Dr Stewart</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00lw657</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00lw657</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5362776052450249538.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>26/07/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Stacey hits rock bottom but with the support of Jean, sees a light at the end of the tunnel. A mysterious stranger from Whitney's past returns. Max and Tanya decide to try again.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Stacey hits rock bottom but with the support of Jean, finally sees a light at the end of the tunnel. A mysterious stranger from Whitney's past returns, but is he who he says he is? Max and Tanya tentatively decide to try again, but Stacey has other ideas.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Stacey Branning; Jean Slater; Whitney Dean; Bianca Jackson; Ryan Malloy; Debra Dean; Max Branning; Tanya Branning; Lauren Branning; Abi Branning; Charlie Slater; Mo Harris; Dr Al Jenkins; Ronnie Mitchell; Garry Hobbs; Nurse Kennedy; Dr Simmonds; Dr Stewart</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00lyxlt</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00lyxlt</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5365320820573129752.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>02/08/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Christian's despair plumbs horrible depths, Libby comes face to face with the darkest demon of her past, and Janine and Ronnie go head to head in the seduction stakes.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Christian's despair plumbs horrible depths before Syed provides a chink of light. Libby comes face to face with the darkest demon of her past: her father. And Janine and Ronnie go head to head in the seduction stakes, with explosive results.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Denise Wicks; Libby Fox; Liz Turner; Chelsea Fox; Lucas Johnson; Darren Miller; Archie Mitchell; Janine Butcher; Ronnie Mitchell; Ryan Malloy; Jack Branning; Roxy Slater; Peggy Mitchell; Christian Clarke; Syed Masood; Amira Shah; Zainab Masood; Masood Ahmed; Tamwar Masood; Ian Beale; Jane Beale; Bianca Jackson; Whitney Dean; Liam Butcher; Patrick Trueman; Syd Chambers; Bradley Branning; Billy Mitchell; Owen Turner; Imam Ali; Luke</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00m3z98</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00m3z98</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5367932590185829051.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>09/08/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Dawn makes a tough decision but will she get her first choice? Denise comes face-to-face with Owen, but has he really changed? Tanya opens her door and heart to Max.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Dawn makes a tough decision but will she get her first choice? Denise comes face-to-face with Owen to find out if he has really changed.

	Tanya opens her door and heart to Max, and Ronnie meets a mysterious stranger from her past.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Owen Turner; Liz Turner; Libby Fox; Denise Wicks; Lucas Johnson; Chelsea Fox; Jordan Johnson; Trina Johnson; Ronnie Mitchell; Janine Butcher; Archie Mitchell; Roxy Slater; Peggy Mitchell; Phil Mitchell; Dawn Swann</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00m6z84</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00m6z84</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5370535340367206998.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>16/08/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Ronnie is determined to get her man, whatever the consequences, while Ricky and Bianca go head-to-head on the dating circuit. A surprise visitor throws Dot into turmoil.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Ronnie is determined to get her man, whatever the consequences, while Ricky and Bianca go head-to-head on the dating circuit. 

	A surprise visitor throws Dot into turmoil, and Mo is devastated when Charlie says goodbye.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Archie Mitchell; Joel Reynolds; Ronnie Mitchell; Jack Branning; Roxy Slater; Ricky Butcher; Bianca Jackson; Dr Al Jenkins; Charlie Slater; Brenda Boyle; Mo Harris; Jean Slater; Stacey Branning; Dot Branning; Liz Turner; Denise Wicks; Libby Fox; Patrick Trueman; Jane Beale; Ian Beale; Darren Miller; Dawn Swann; Garry Hobbs; Whitney Dean; Ryan Malloy; Janine Butcher; Peggy Mitchell; Bradley Branning; Billy Mitchell; Minty Peterson; Manda Best; Heather Trott; Lauren Branning; Liam Butcher; Tiffany Dean; Dotty Cotton; Stephanie Reynolds; Bob</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00mbtzz</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00mbtzz</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5373144532999528628.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>23/08/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Dot reels from the news that Jim is coming home, Ronnie makes a drastic decision about her relationship with Joel, and Libby and Tamwar receive their A-Level results.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Dot reels from the news that Jim is coming home, while Ronnie makes a drastic decision about her relationship with Joel. 

	It is crunch time for Libby and Tamwar as they get their A-Level results, and Minty learns a disturbing secret about Dawn.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Minty Peterson; Phil Mitchell; Garry Hobbs; Dawn Swann; Dot Branning; Jim Branning; Patrick Trueman; Liz Turner; Masood Ahmed; Zainab Masood; Christian Clarke; Syed Masood; Amira Shah; Tamwar Masood; Ian Beale</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00mfkvj</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00mfkvj</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5375742129220150945.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>30/08/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Will Garry and Dawn sail into the sunset together, or will Dawn's misdeeds catch up with her? Zainab has a shocking revelation for Masood. Meanwhile, Bradley fights to keep Gumbo.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Will Garry and Dawn sail into the sunset together, or will Dawn's misdeeds catch up with her? Zainab has a shocking revelation for Masood. Meanwhile, Bradley fights to keep Gumbo.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Zainab Masood; Masood Ahmed; Minty Peterson; Manda Best; Garry Hobbs; Dawn Swann; Darren Miller; Bradley Branning; Syd Chambers; Noah Chambers; Jane Beale; Syed Masood; Tamwar Masood; Amira Shah; Heather Trott</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00ml66g</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00ml66g</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5378320398087942136.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>06/09/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Lucas tries to deal with the havoc created by Trina, with shocking consequences. The Masoods' marriage is tested, and Ricky returns to the square with a blast from the past.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Lucas tries to deal with the havoc created by Trina, with shocking consequences. The Masoods' marriage is stretched to breaking point, and Ricky returns to the square with a blast from the past.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Bianca Jackson; Sam Mitchell; Ricky Butcher; Phil Mitchell; Lucas Johnson; Denise Wicks; Trina Johnson; Jordan Johnson; Chelsea Fox; Libby Fox; Patrick Trueman; Charlie Slater; Mo Harris; Orlenda; Jean Slater; Stacey Branning; Whitney Dean; Liam Butcher; Tiffany Dean; Zainab Masood; Masood Ahmed; Syed Masood; Amira Shah; Tamwar Masood; Dot Branning; Jim Branning; Darren Miller; Jane Beale; William</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00mqhq6</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00mqhq6</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5380941187131962683.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>13/09/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Sam Mitchell's return to Walford sends shockwaves across the Square, and has heartbreaking consequences for Bianca. Meanwhile, Lucas makes a troubling discovery about Trina.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Sam Mitchell's return to Walford sends shockwaves across the Square, and has heartbreaking consequences for Bianca. 

	Lucas makes a troubling discovery about Trina, and Archie manages to gain the upper hand over Peggy. 

	Meanwhile, Janine and Ryan circle round an unsuspecting Chelsea, and Minty finally meets Manda's son, Adam.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Sam Mitchell; Phil Mitchell; Ricky Butcher; Minty Peterson; Peggy Mitchell; Roxy Slater; Ronnie Mitchell; Joel Reynolds; Billy Mitchell; Jay Brown; Bianca Jackson; Pat Evans; Whitney Dean; Ryan Malloy; Janine Butcher; Chelsea Fox; Lucas Johnson; Denise Wicks; Jordan Johnson; Manda Best; Adam Best; Archie Mitchell; Ben Mitchell; Masood Ahmed; Zainab Masood; Amira Shah; Syed Masood; Tamwar Masood; Liam Butcher; Tiffany Dean; Morgan Jackson-King; Hannah Reynolds; Libby Fox; Patrick Trueman; Charlie Slater; Ritchie Scott; DS Grimwood; PC Young</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00mwb0l</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00mwb0l</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5383536206372207589.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>20/09/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Trina's body is found, and the police investigation puts pressure on Denise and Lucas. Bradley and Stacey come to an understanding, and Christian and Syed are pushed further apart.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Trina's body is found, and the police investigation puts Denise and Lucas under pressure. Bradley and Stacey come to a new understanding, while Christian and Syed are pushed further and further apart. Meanwhile, Ricky turns against Bianca and Whitney, and Lauren is the victim of a nasty rumour.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Peggy Mitchell; Archie Mitchell; Phil Mitchell; Ronnie Mitchell; Sam Mitchell; Ricky Butcher; Bianca Jackson; Liam Butcher; Tiffany Dean; Morgan Jackson-King; Whitney Dean; Denise Wicks; Lucas Johnson; DC Deane Cunningham; Chelsea Fox; Libby Fox; Jordan Johnson; Ian Beale; Jane Beale; Max Branning; Tanya Branning; Lauren Branning; Peter Beale; Abi Branning; Lucy Beale; Jay Brown; Bradley Branning; Stacey Branning; Syd Chambers; Noah Chambers; Jean Slater; Christian Clarke; Syed Masood; Amira Shah; James Mackie; Charlie Slater; Patrick Trueman; Roxy Slater; Ben Mitchell; Jack Branning; Dr Al Jenkins; Joel Reynolds; Ryan Malloy; Janine Butcher; Ritchie Scott</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00n13q3</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00n13q3</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5386135091082989193.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>27/09/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>The Mitchell women stand up for themselves, but in doing so awaken the giant that is Archie. Bradley takes the next step with Syd, but how will Stacey cope with the changes?</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>The Mitchell women stand up for themselves, but in doing so awaken the giant that is Archie. Bradley takes the next step with Syd, but how will Stacey cope with the changes? And Bianca finds the courage to tell Ricky how she feels - but will it be too late?</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Ian Beale; Jane Beale; Ricky Butcher; Bianca Jackson; Sam Mitchell; Peggy Mitchell; Stacey Branning; Bradley Branning; Syd Chambers; Jean Slater; Tanya Branning; Max Branning; Peter Beale; Lauren Branning; Christian Clarke; James Mackie; Denise Wicks; Darren Miller; Whitney Dean; Liam Butcher; Tiffany Dean; Morgan Jackson-King; Ryan Malloy; Janine Butcher; Pat Evans; Roxy Slater; Ronnie Mitchell; Phil Mitchell; Billy Mitchell; Archie Mitchell; Lucas Johnson; Patrick Trueman; Adam Best; Libby Fox; Chelsea Fox; Syed Masood; Amira Shah; Abi Branning; Lucy Beale; Noah Chambers; Sandra Fielding; Mr Lister; Photographer</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00n5lvp</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00n5lvp</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5388697898068513166.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>04/10/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Syed and Christian's attempts to move on prove futile, Roxy worries that Ronnie is about to sabotage another relationship and Denise receives a visit from the police.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Syed and Christian's attempts to move on prove futile, Roxy worries that Ronnie is about to sabotage another relationship and Denise receives a visit from the police.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Syed Masood; Zainab Masood; Masood Ahmed; Ian Beale; Jane Beale; Christian Clarke; Amira Shah; Tamwar Masood; Lucas Johnson; Chelsea Fox; Jordan Johnson; Denise Wicks; Libby Fox; Darren Miller; Patrick Trueman; Stacey Branning; Dr Al Jenkins; Ryan Malloy; Roxy Slater; Ronnie Mitchell; Sam Mitchell; Joel Reynolds; Peggy Mitchell; Adam Best; Manda Best; Minty Peterson; Pat Evans; Liz Turner; Jim Branning; Lucy Beale; Heather Trott; Ricky Butcher; Liam Butcher; James Mackie; Imam Ali; Mr Lister; Himself; Funeral Director; Hannah Reynolds; Bobby Beale</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00n6zt9</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00n6zt9</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5388748149185878226.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>04/10/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Lucas lays Trina to rest, Stacey takes a dramatic turn for the worse, and Christian struggles with his place in Syed's affections.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Lucas lays Trina to rest, Stacey takes a dramatic turn for the worse, and Christian struggles with his place in Syed's affections.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Syed Masood; Zainab Masood; Masood Ahmed; Ian Beale; Jane Beale; Christian Clarke; Amira Shah; Tamwar Masood; Lucas Johnson; Chelsea Fox; Jordan Johnson; Denise Wicks; Libby Fox; Darren Miller; Patrick Trueman; Stacey Branning; Dr Al Jenkins; Ryan Malloy; Roxy Slater; Ronnie Mitchell; Sam Mitchell; Joel Reynolds; Peggy Mitchell; Adam Best; Manda Best; Minty Peterson; Pat Evans; Liz Turner; Jim Branning; Lucy Beale; Heather Trott; Ricky Butcher; Liam Butcher; James Mackie; Imam Ali; Mr Lister; Himself; Funeral Director; Hannah Reynolds; Bobby Beale</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00n9lt8</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00n9lt8</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5391310956171401520.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>11/10/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Syed has the opportunity to come clean, but his decision could be disastrous for the Masoods. Stacey's condition worsens and Max struggles to keep his head above water.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Syed has the opportunity to come clean, but his decision could be disastrous for the Masoods. Meanwhile, Stacey's condition worsens until there is no-one left to help her, Max struggles to keep his head above water, and Ronnie's relationship with Joel reaches crisis point.

	If you are affected by any of the issues in this episode of EastEnders, you can find information regarding sources of help, support, and advice at the following address:
	http://www.bbc.co.uk/eastenders/news/news_20081104.shtml.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Stacey Branning; Jean Slater; Dr Al Jenkins; Bradley Branning; Syd Chambers; Noah Chambers; Charlie Slater; Mo Harris; Max Branning; Tanya Branning; Jack Branning; Rachel Branning; Ronnie Mitchell; Joel Reynolds; Peggy Mitchell; Roxy Slater; Sam Mitchell; Archie Mitchell; Ricky Butcher; Bianca Jackson; Ryan Malloy; Liam Butcher; Lauren Branning; Abi Branning; Dot Branning; Jim Branning; Zainab Masood; Masood Ahmed; Syed Masood; Tamwar Masood; Amira Shah; Jane Beale; Christian Clarke; Phil Mitchell; Liz Turner; Patrick Trueman; Sonographer; Stag; Little Girl</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00nfkw1</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00nfkw1</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5393899532960700718.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>18/10/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Owen returns to the Square, but what does he want? Sam gets a job with Jack, but is she after more? And can Shirley resort to desperate measures for cash?</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Owen returns to the Square, but what does he want? Sam gets a job with Jack, but is she after more? And can Shirley resort to desperate measures for cash? 

	Archie plots with Janine, and Ronnie sets her sights on Ryan, but he has his eye on someone else.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Sam Mitchell; Jack Branning; Syed Masood; Christian Clarke; Jane Beale; Zainab Masood; Masood Ahmed; Tamwar Masood; Amira Shah; Archie Mitchell; Janine Butcher; Ryan Malloy; Ronnie Mitchell; Phil Mitchell; Peggy Mitchell; Ricky Butcher; Bianca Jackson; Patrick Trueman; Liz Turner; Owen Turner; Darren Miller; Jim Branning; Libby Fox; Pat Evans; Shirley Carter; Heather Trott; Minty Peterson; Mo Harris; Liam Butcher; Charlie Slater; Jean Slater; Tiffany Dean; Liam Butcher; Abi Branning</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00nks3n</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00nks3n</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5396544803318313330.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>25/10/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Heather gives birth, and all is revealed. Libby accepts Darren's offer, but Denise wades in. Tamwar celebrates his birthday, and Syed suspects his blackmailer is close to home.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Heather gives birth, and all is revealed when the father finally arrives. Libby accepts Darren's offer, but Denise soon wades in. Tamwar celebrates his birthday, and Syed suspects his blackmailer is close to home.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Heather Trott; Billy Mitchell; Darren Miller; Minty Peterson; Phil Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Adam Best; Manda Best; Libby Fox; Patrick Trueman; Denise Wicks; Lucas Johnson; Chelsea Fox; Tamwar Masood; Syed Masood; Amira Shah; Christian Clarke; Peter Beale; Lucy Beale; Ronnie Mitchell; Roxy Slater; Owen Turner; Jay Brown; Peggy Mitchell; Dr Al Jenkins; Jack Branning; Zainab Masood; Masood Ahmed; Pat Evans; Jean Slater; Sam Mitchell; Janine Butcher; Archie Mitchell; Liam Butcher; Midwife</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00nv926</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00nv926</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5399126937660868308.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>01/11/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Heather and Baby George's return to the Square puts the pressure on the father - but will he face up to his responsibilities? Jack and Archie join forces against the Mitchells.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Heather and Baby George's return to the Square puts the pressure on the father - but will he face up to his responsibilities?

	Jack and Archie join forces against the Mitchells and Syed and Christian decide to take on their blackmailer. Owen is shocked when Lucas reveals his true colours.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Lucas Johnson; Owen Turner; Denise Wicks; Libby Fox; Darren Miller; Adam Best; Chelsea Fox; Archie Mitchell; Jack Branning; Sam Mitchell; Ricky Butcher; Janine Butcher; Ryan Malloy; Ronnie Mitchell; Christian Clarke; Syed Masood; Lucy Beale; Tamwar Masood; Amira Shah; Zainab Masood; Heather Trott; Shirley Carter; Billy Mitchell; Ian Beale; Jane Beale; Minty Peterson; Manda Best; Pat Evans; Patrick Trueman; Dr Al Jenkins; Liz Turner; Jordan Johnson; Bobby Beale; Dave</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00nv92m</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00nv92m</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5399153995950634590.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>01/11/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Heather and Baby George's return to the Square puts the pressure on the father - can he face up to his responsibilities? Jack and Archie join forces against the Mitchells.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Heather and Baby George's return to the Square puts the pressure on the father - can he face up to his responsibilities?

	Jack and Archie join forces against the Mitchells, and Syed and Christian decide to take on their blackmailer. Owen is shocked when Lucas reveals his true colours.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Lucas Johnson; Owen Turner; Denise Wicks; Libby Fox; Darren Miller; Adam Best; Chelsea Fox; Archie Mitchell; Jack Branning; Sam Mitchell; Ricky Butcher; Janine Butcher; Ryan Malloy; Ronnie Mitchell; Christian Clarke; Syed Masood; Lucy Beale; Tamwar Masood; Amira Shah; Zainab Masood; Heather Trott; Shirley Carter; Billy Mitchell; Ian Beale; Jane Beale; Minty Peterson; Manda Best; Pat Evans; Patrick Trueman; Dr Al Jenkins; Liz Turner; Jordan Johnson; Bobby Beale; Dave</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00ny81x</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00ny81x</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5404314399156784194.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>15/11/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Ronnie and Owen share an unexpected connection, Peggy has a secret but Archie's is more serious, Ricky makes a mess of the T-shirt business and Sam ends her relationship with Jack.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Ronnie and Owen share an unexpected connection that sends shockwaves through the Square. Peggy has a secret, but Archie's is much more serious. Meanwhile, Ricky makes a mess of Whitney's T-shirt business, Lucy and Jay draw closer despite Jay's guilt, and Sam ends her relationship with Jack - but someone sees their final kiss.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Archie Mitchell; Sam Mitchell; Jack Branning; Peggy Mitchell; Roxie Mitchell; Ronnie Mitchell; Owen Turner; Denise Wicks; Lucas Johnson; Libby Fox; Darren Miller; Patrick Trueman; Whitney Dean; Ricky Butcher; Bianca Jackson; Janine Butcher; Ian Beale; Tanya Branning; Max Branning; Jane Beale; Lucy Beale; Jay Brown; Billy Mitchell; Syed Masood; Christian Clarke; Pat Evans; Masood Ahmed; Liz Turner; Abi Branning; Jordan Johnson; PC Lance; Adam Best; Ray; Lian; Pastor</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00p29js</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00p29js</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5406946784612504113.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>22/11/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Archie does everything he can to ruin the Mitchells, Max sinks lower than ever before, and Ricky and Bianca share a special connection at the Children in Need dance competition.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Archie does everything he can to ruin the Mitchells, and he might just succeed. Max sinks lower than ever before as he battles his financial woes. And Ricky and Bianca share a special connection at the Children in Need dance competition.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Sam Mitchell; Archie Mitchell; Ricky Butcher; Bianca Jackson; Peggy Mitchell; Denise Wicks; Lucas Johnson; Patrick Trueman; Pat Evans; Liz Turner; Owen Turner; Libby Fox; Dr Al Jenkins; Roxy Slater; Jack Branning; Phil Mitchell; Billy Mitchell; Janine Butcher; Minty Pearson; Charlie Slater; Heather Trott; Max Branning; Tanya Branning; Ryan Malloy; Mr Stuart</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00p66v4</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00p66v4</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5409528918950861690.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>29/11/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>As Lucas prepares to marry Denise, Owen shows up on the square. Phil's loans catch up with him and Sam's disappearance threatens to cost the Mitchells everything they have.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>As Lucas prepares to marry Denise, Owen shows up on the square, determined to put a stop to the wedding at all costs. Phil's loans catch up with him, Sam's disappearance threatens to cost the Mitchells everything they have, and Roxy and Doctor Al share a very special connection.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Max Branning; Phil Mitchell; Ian Beale; Peggy Mitchell; Pat Evans; Lucas Johnson; Denise Wicks; Owen Turner; Libby Fox; Chelsea Fox; Liz Turner; Charlie Slater; Patrick Trueman; Heather Trott; Shirley Carter; Darren Miller; Roxy Mitchell; Dr Al Jenkins; Lucy Beale; Christian Clarke; Syed Masood; Amira Shah; Zainab Masood; Masood Ahmed; Minty Pearson; Manda Best; Adam Best; Ricky Butcher; Bianca Jackson; Jack Branning; Archie Mitchell; Billy Mitchell; Tanya Branning; Lauren Branning; Abi Branning; Jordan Johnson; Ben Mitchell; Kim Fox; Dexter; Winston; Gaynor; Charity; Council Worker; Pastor; Isaacs; Colin Sydenham; PC Shona Blake</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00p98hg</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00p98hg</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5412134246112617653.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>06/12/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Ronnie returns with exciting news, Phil is forced to swallow his pride, Masood's attempts to provide for his family end in disaster, and Whitney is rocked by some upsetting news.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Ronnie returns to the Square with some exciting news, Phil is forced to swallow his pride in order to protect the Mitchell name, and Masood's attempts to provide for his family end in disaster. Meanwhile, with Tony's trial looming, Whitney is rocked by some upsetting news.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Whitney Dean; Mark; Bianca Jackson; Ricky Butcher; Ryan Malloy; Christian Clarke; Syed Masood; Masood Ahmed; Zainab Masood; Amira Shah; Ian Beale; Archie Mitchell; Janine Butcher; Max Branning; Tanya Branning; Rachel Branning; Phil Mitchell; Ronnie Mitchell; Roxy Mitchell; Jean Slater; Mo Harris; Peter Beale; Lauren Branning; Pat Evans; Patrick Trueman; Liz Turner; Charlie Slater; Dr Al Jenkins; Tiffany Dean; Bobby Beale; Ben Mitchell; Isaacs; PC Henderson; DS Louise Hills</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00pf5d6</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00pf5d6</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5414726688372484623.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>13/12/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>As the week of Tony's trial arrives, will Whitney be strong enough to testify? Meanwhile, Stacey is surprised to see Bradley, and Max's secrets finally catch up with him.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>As the week of Tony's trial arrives, will Whitney be strong enough to testify? Meanwhile, Stacey is surprised to see Bradley, and Max's secrets finally catch up with him.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Max Branning; Tanya Branning; Abi Branning; Lauren Branning; Whitney Dean; Tony King; Bianca Jackson; Ricky Butcher; Tiffany Dean; Liam Butcher; Morgan Jackson-King; Pat Evans; Janine Butcher; Ian Beale; Ryan Malloy; Archie Mitchell; Jean Slater; Stacey Slater; Bradley Branning; Syd Chambers; Noah Chambers; Phil Mitchell; Rachel Branning; Becca Swanson; Tyler; Vivien; Mrs Taylor; Ms Gilroy; Judge; DS Hill; Fiona; Nurse Wilkins</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00pjm5k</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00pjm5k</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5417334592514618865.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>20/12/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Archie surprises the Mitchells, while the Masoods battle their financial troubles. Whitney deals with the news of Tony's sentence, and Max is forced to face up to his crime.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Archie surprises the Mitchells, while the Masoods battle their financial troubles. Meanwhile, Whitney deals with the news of Tony's sentence, Max is forced to face up to his crime, and a monster is created when Mo is signed up to direct the kids' Nativity.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Peggy Mitchell; Archie Mitchell; Janine Butcher; Phil Mitchell; Ronnie Mitchell; Roxy Mitchell; Ben Mitchell; Ryan Malloy; Whitney Dean; Bianca Jackson; Tony King; Ricky Butcher; Todd Taylor; Christian Clarke; Syed Masood; Zainab Masood; Masood Ahmed; Amira Shah; Ian Beale; Jane Beale; Billy Mitchell; Charlie Slater; Mo Harris; Aunt Sal; Max Branning; Shirley Carter; Heather Trott; Bobby Beale; Lucy Beale; Peter Beale; Dotty Cotton; Abi Branning; Jay Brown; Qadim Shah; Judge; Mrs Taylor; Vivien; DS Louise Hills; PC Andy Henderson; Barbara</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00pjplf</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00pjplf</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5419885803088443114.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>27/12/2009</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Christmas in Walford sees Archie finally conquer the Mitchells and manoeuvre his way into the Vic, but the day itself ends with someone in handcuffs for his brutal murder.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Christmas in Walford sees Archie finally conquer the Mitchells and manoeuvre his way into the Vic, but the day itself ends with someone in handcuffs for his brutal murder. 

	Amidst the mayhem, Ricky and Bianca have their most romantic Christmas ever, Stacey and Bradley come to a life-changing decision, and Christian begins to realise that he and Syed can never be together.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Ronnie Mitchell; Roxy Mitchell; Archie Mitchell; Jack Branning; Peggy Mitchell; Phil Mitchell; Bradley Branning; Stacey Slater; Janine Butcher; Ryan Malloy; Ian Beale; Jane Beale; Billy Mitchell; Ricky Butcher; Bianca Jackson; Mo Harris; Charlie Slater; Jean Slater; Patrick Trueman; Heather Trott; Shirley Carter; Minty Peterson; Manda Best; Adam Best; Masood Ahmed; Zainab Masood; Amira Shah; Tamwar Masood; Whitney Dean; Max Branning; Tanya Branning; Dot Branning; Jim Branning; Dr Al Jenkins; Darren Miller; Libby Fox; Pat Evans; Christian Clarke; Liam Butcher; Tiffany Dean; Morgan Jackson-King; Peter Beale; Lucy Beale; Bobby Beale; Ben Mitchell; Abi Branning; Lauren Branning; Dotty Cotton; PC Adams; PC Sim</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00pr5zb</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00pr5zb</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5422498861191302677.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>03/01/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>It is the week of Syed and Amira's wedding, but Christian cannot keep his and Syed's secret any longer, and tells all to Zainab. Meanwhile, the police search for Archie's killer.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>It is the week of Syed and Amira's wedding, and both the lead-up and the event are among the most spectacular the Square has seen. But Christian cannot keep his and Syed's secret any longer, and tells all to Zainab. 

	Meanwhile, the police search for Archie's killer, and someone notices something very odd indeed in Darren and Heather's relationship.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Darren Miller; Libby Fox; Heather Trott; Christian Clarke; Syed Masood; Zainab Masood; Amira Shah; Qadim Shah; Masood Ahmed; Tamwar Masood; Afia; Minty Peterson; Manda Best; Adam Best; Denise Johnson; Chelsea Fox; Lucas Johnson; Ian Beale; Jane Beale; Peter Beale; Lucy Beale; Phil Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Ben Mitchell; Ricky Butcher; Ryan Malloy; Stacey Slater; Bradley Branning; Jean Slater; Charlie Slater; Mo Harris; Billy Mitchell; Jim Branning; Dotty Cotton; Patrick Trueman; Max Branning; Ronnie Mitchell; Roxy Mitchell; Peggy Mitchell; Jack Branning; Archie Mitchell; Dr Al Jenkins; DCI Marsden; Bushra Abbasi; Zulekha Abbasi; Inzamam Ahmed; Imam Ali; DC Hughes; PC Sim; PC Adams; Ali Ahmed</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00qbspp</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00qbspp</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5427722400416703259.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>17/01/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Archie's will is read, and its contents will send shockwaves around the Square for years to come. Meanwhile, Stacey and Bradley's big secret comes out.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Archie's will is read, and its contents will send shockwaves around the Square for years to come. 

	Meanwhile, Stacey and Bradley's big secret comes out, Zainab hands over dirt on Ian to Jane, and Janine finds a sneaky way to make money.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Ronnie Mitchell; Glenda Mitchell; Roxy Mitchell; Peggy Mitchell; Janine Butcher; Billy Mitchell; Phil Mitchell; Ian Beale; Jane Beale; Zainab Masood; Tamwar Masood; Peter Beale; Lauren Branning; Stacey Slater; Bradley Branning; Jean Slater; Max Branning; Mo Harris; Charlie Slater; Ricky Butcher; Jean Slater; Max Branning; Mo Harris; Charlie Slater; Ricky Butcher; Bianca Jackson; Whitney Dean; Todd Taylor; Ryan Malloy; Heather Trott; Shirley Carter; Denise Johnson; Christian Clarke; Jack Branning; Dr Al Jenkins; DCI Marsden; Emma West</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00qh1kc</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00qh1kc</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5430295515323739606.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>24/01/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Janine wreaks havoc on Ian and Jane for ignoring her blackmail demands. Ronnie pays Glenda a visit in a desperate search for answers, and Bradley makes a sacrifice for Stacey.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>A vengeful Janine wreaks havoc on Ian and Jane for ignoring her blackmail demands, Ronnie pays Glenda a visit in a desperate search for answers, and Bradley makes a sacrifice for Stacey.

	Meanwhile, Denise discovers she has competition for Lucas's attention and Peggy is increasingly sidelined.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Pat Evans; Bianca Jackson; Janine Butcher; Liam Butcher; Tiffany Dean; Peggy Mitchell; Roxy Mitchell; Ronnie Mitchell; Glenda Mitchell; Jack Branning; Jane Beale; Ian Beale; Denise Johnson; Chelsea Fox; Lucas Johnson; Stacey Slater; Bradley Branning; Jean Slater; Mo Harris; Becca Swanson; Christian Clarke; Tracey; DCI Marsden; Ryan Malloy; Billy Mitchell; Ricky Butcher; Darren Miller; Lucy Beale; Peter Beale; Bobby Beale; Loretta; Danny Mitchell; Reg; Nick Greenway; Julia</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00qnqql</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00qnqql</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5432920169838327808.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>31/01/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Ronnie and Roxy reel at the surprise arrival of a new Mitchell at Archie's wake. Janine comes clean to Marsden, but it is a little too late for a seriously ill Pat.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Ronnie and Roxy reel at the surprise arrival of a new Mitchell at Archie's wake. Janine comes clean to Marsden, but it is a little too late for a seriously ill Pat. Max has big plans, while Archie has romantic ideas of his own.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Stacey Slater; Becca Swanson; Bradley Branning; Ronnie Mitchell; Roxy Mitchell; Danny Mitchell; Glenda Mitchell; Peggy Mitchell; Phil Mitchell; Pat Evans; Ricky Butcher; Janine Butcher; Max Branning; Abi Branning; Lauren Branning; Ian Beale; Jane Beale; Christian Clarke; Syed Masood; Amira Masood; Masood Ahmed; Jack Branning; Mo Harris; Charlie Slater; Jean Slater; Billy Mitchell; Ryan Malloy; Chelsea Fox; Shirley Carter; Ben Mitchell; Dr Al Jenkins; Bianca Jackson; Liam Butcher; Tiffany Dean; Morgan Jackson-King; DCI Marsden; DC Wayne Hughes; Reverend Stevens; Reg; Leyton; Paramedic; Dr Clayton</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00qr4wc</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00qr4wc</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5435485553804231154.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>07/02/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Amira's attempt to seduce Syed leads them both into dangerous territory, while Danny causes tension in the Vic. Meanwhile, Jack harbours chilling suspicions about Ronnie.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Amira's attempt to seduce Syed leads them both into dangerous territory, while the new Mitchell brother causes tension in the Vic. Meanwhile, Jack harbours chilling suspicions about Ronnie, but nothing can prepare him for what he discovers next. Has he finally found Archie's murderer?</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Jack Branning; Tiffany Dean; Bradley Branning; Stacey Slater; Bianca Jackson; Ricky Butcher; Max Branning; Becca Swanson; Billie Jackson; Whitney Dean; Janine Butcher; Todd Taylor; Amira Masood; Syed Masood; Christian Clarke; Zainab Masood; Masood Ahmed; Peggy Mitchell; Ronnie Mitchell; Roxy Mitchell; Danny Mitchell; Dot Branning; Dotty Cotton; Heather Trott; Dr Al Jenkins; Mo Harris; Chelsea Fox; Ian Beale; Pat Evans; Billy Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Tracey; Liam Butcher; Morgan Jackson-King; Leyton; DCI Marsden; Mr Lister</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00qzct9</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00qzct9</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5438083150024854276.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>14/02/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Marsden is determined to stop at nothing to discover who murdered Archie Mitchell. Ronnie tries in vain to make a fresh start, while mounting pressure gets to Bradley.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Marsden is determined to stop at nothing to discover who murdered Archie Mitchell. Ronnie tries in vain to make a fresh start, while mounting pressure gets to Bradley. Meanwhile, events at Bianca's hen night make Ricky question if marrying Bianca is the right thing to do.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Ronnie Mitchell; Roxy Mitchell; Peggy Mitchell; Phil Mitchell; Janine Butcher; Jack Branning; Max Branning; Bradley Branning; Stacey Slater; Becca Swanson; Dot Branning; Jim Branning; Dotty Cotton; Sonia Fowler; Patrick Trueman; Bianca Jackson; Ricky Butcher; Zainab Masood; Denise Johnson; Libby Fox; Chelsea Fox; Heather Trott; Shirley Carter; Whitney Dean; Todd Taylor; Billie Jackson; Ian Beale; Jane Beale; Lucy Beale; Leon Small; Zsa Zsa Carter; Fat Boy; Manda Best; Minty Peterson; Adam Best; Darren Miller; Pat Evans; Billy Mitchell; Charlie Slater; Jean Slater; Ryan Malloy; Liam Butcher; Tiffany Dean; Morgan Jackson-King; DCI Marsden; DC Hughes; DC Field</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00qzn12</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00qzn12</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5438098611911316590.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>14/02/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Marsden is determined to stop at nothing to discover who murdered Archie Mitchell. Ronnie tries in vain to make a fresh start, while mounting pressure gets to Bradley.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Marsden is determined to stop at nothing to discover who murdered Archie Mitchell. Ronnie tries in vain to make a fresh start, while mounting pressure gets to Bradley. Meanwhile, events at Bianca's hen night make Ricky question if marrying Bianca is the right thing to do.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Ronnie Mitchell; Roxy Mitchell; Peggy Mitchell; Phil Mitchell; Janine Butcher; Jack Branning; Max Branning; Bradley Branning; Stacey Slater; Becca Swanson; Dot Branning; Jim Branning; Dotty Cotton; Sonia Fowler; Patrick Trueman; Bianca Jackson; Ricky Butcher; Zainab Masood; Denise Johnson; Libby Fox; Chelsea Fox; Heather Trott; Shirley Carter; Whitney Dean; Todd Taylor; Billie Jackson; Ian Beale; Jane Beale; Lucy Beale; Leon Small; Zsa Zsa Carter; Fat Boy; Manda Best; Minty Peterson; Adam Best; Darren Miller; Pat Evans; Billy Mitchell; Charlie Slater; Jean Slater; Ryan Malloy; Liam Butcher; Tiffany Dean; Morgan Jackson-King; DCI Marsden; DC Hughes; DC Field</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00r4x4f</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00r4x4f</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5440689765680991449.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>21/02/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Bianca and Ricky's wedding day approaches, but Carol is set on ruining the celebrations. Janine's set on revenge and Archie's killer is revealed.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Bianca and Ricky's wedding day approaches, but Carol is set on ruining the celebrations. Jack is desperate to protect Bradley from the police, and Stacey and Bradley have a shock announcement to make. Janine's set on revenge and Archie's killer is revealed.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Abi Branning; Adam Best; Amira Masood; Becca Swanson; Ben Mitchell; Bianca Jackson; Billie Jackson; Billy Mitchell; Bobby Beale; Bradley Branning; Carol Jackson; Charlie Slater; Chelsea Fox; Christian Clarke; Darren Miller; DC Hughes; DCI Marsden; Denise Johnson; Dot Branning; Dotty Cotton; Fat Boy; Heather Trott; Ian Beale; Jack Branning; Jane Beale; Janine Butcher; Jay Brown; Jean Slater; Jim Branning; Jordan Johnson; Lauren Branning; Leon Small; Liam Butcher; Lucas Johnson; Lucy Beale; Masood Ahmed; Max Branning; Minty Peterson; Morgan Jackson-King; Pat Evans; Peggy Mitchell; Peter Beale; Phil Mitchell; Registrar; Ricky Butcher; Robbie Jackson; Ronnie Mitchell; Roxy Mitchell; Ryan Malloy; Sandy; Shirley Carter; Sonia Fowler; Stacey Slater; Syed Masood; Tamwar Masood; Tiffany Dean; Vicar; Whitney Dean; Zainab Masood; Zsa Zsa Carter</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00r7mcv</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00r7mcv</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5443278342466100962.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>28/02/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>The Square comes to terms with recent events, while Masood helps Zainab give birth to their son, and Lucas puts a stop to anyone digging away at Trina's tree.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>The Square comes to terms with recent events, while Masood helps Zainab give birth to their son, and Lucas puts a stop to anyone digging away at Trina's tree.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Zainab Masood; Tamwar Masood; Masood Ahmed; Syed Masood; Amira Masood; Christian Clarke; Lucas Johnson; Denise Johnson; Patrick Trueman; Jordan Johnson; Chelsea Fox; Stacey Branning; Bradley Branning; Max Branning; Carol Jackson; Jean Slater; Becca Swanson; Mo Harris; Charlie Slater; Peggy Mitchell; Roxy Mitchell; Ronnie Mitchell; Jack Branning; Phil Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Heather Trott; Zsa Zsa Carter; Leon Small; Lucy Beale; Ian Beale; Jane Beale; Peter Beale; Whitney Dean; Billie Jackson; Dot Branning; Dotty Cotton; Jim Branning; Janine Butcher; Pat Evans; Billy Mitchell; Minty Peterson; Liz Turner; DCI Marsden; Mr Allcock; Sandy; Kylie; David Hensler</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00r9qgk</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00r9qgk</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5443293804352559100.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>28/02/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>The Square comes to terms with recent events, while Masood helps Zainab give birth to their son, and Lucas puts a stop to anyone digging away at Trina's tree.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>The Square comes to terms with recent events, while Masood helps Zainab give birth to their son, and Lucas puts a stop to anyone digging away at Trina's tree.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Zainab Masood; Tamwar Masood; Masood Ahmed; Syed Masood; Amira Masood; Christian Clarke; Lucas Johnson; Denise Johnson; Patrick Trueman; Jordan Johnson; Chelsea Fox; Stacey Branning; Bradley Branning; Max Branning; Carol Jackson; Jean Slater; Becca Swanson; Mo Harris; Charlie Slater; Peggy Mitchell; Roxy Mitchell; Ronnie Mitchell; Jack Branning; Phil Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Heather Trott; Zsa Zsa Carter; Leon Small; Lucy Beale; Ian Beale; Jane Beale; Peter Beale; Whitney Dean; Billie Jackson; Dot Branning; Dotty Cotton; Jim Branning; Janine Butcher; Pat Evans; Billy Mitchell; Minty Peterson; Liz Turner; DCI Marsden; Mr Allcock; Sandy; Kylie; David Hensler</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00rlx0r</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00rlx0r</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5448461938499838027.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>14/03/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Ian hears devastating news from Lucy and Jane. Peggy is called to the police station, but who is waiting in the cells? Whitney takes the rap for vandalism on the Square.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Ian hears devastating news from Lucy and Jane, unaware that worse is to come. Peggy is called to the police station, but who is waiting in the cells? Whitney takes the rap for vandalism on the Square, and Becca makes an ill-advised attempt to seduce a grieving Max.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Ian Beale; Lucy Beale; Leon Small; Jane Beale; Peter Beale; Dot Branning; Heather Trott; Lucas Johnson; Libby Fox; Denise Johnson; Chelsea Fox; Patrick Trueman; Adam Best; Darren Miller; Tamwar Masood; Carol Jackson; Billie Jackson; Whitney Dean; Bianca Butcher; Ricky Butcher; Max Branning; Abi Branning; Becca Swanson; Peggy Mitchell; Danny Mitchell; Roxy Mitchell; Pat Evans; Charlie Slater; Jean Slater; Billy Mitchell; Liam Butcher; Morgan Jackson-King; Kylie; Connor; Dave; Sergeant Lewis; Theresa</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00rr592</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00rr592</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5451071131132164849.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>21/03/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>The war between Ronnie and the Mitchells intensifies. Lucas sweats as Denise makes plans to overhaul the gardens, while Phil Mitchell shows his romantic side.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>The war between Ronnie and the Mitchells intensifies, but has she crossed the line for good? Lucas sweats as Denise makes plans to overhaul the gardens, while Phil Mitchell shows his romantic side.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Ronnie Mitchell; Little Girl; Phil Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Roxy Mitchell; Peggy Mitchell; Danny Mitchell; Heather Trott; Ian Beale; Jane Beale; Lucy Beale; Peter Beale; Billie Jackson; Carol Jackson; Ricky Butcher; Lucas Johnson; Libby Fox; Denise Johnson; Jean Slater; Charlie Slater; Mo Harris; Zainab Masood; Minty Peterson; Billy Mitchell; Max Branning; Jack Branning; Fat Boy; Leon Small; Ben Mitchell; Abi Branning; Tim Brown; Bev; Auctioneer</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00rt9kk</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00rt9kk</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5453682900740639513.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>28/03/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Max's search for Stacey takes him to the very edge of his sanity - and then he finds her. Meanwhile, Lucy comes clean to Ian and puts him in an impossible situation.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Max's search for Stacey takes him to the very edge of his sanity - and then he finds her. Lucy comes clean to Ian and puts him in an impossible situation. Meanwhile, Ben's party goes off with a bang, Chelsea hunts for a man, and Billie Jackson's gang turns the screws on Phil.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Max Branning; Stacey Branning; Becca Swanson; Lucy Beale; Jane Beale; Ian Beale; Peggy Mitchell; Phil Mitchell; Louise Mitchell; Roxy Mitchell; Ronnie Mitchell; Danny Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Heather Trott; Billie Jackson; Whitney Dean; Kylie; Connor; Mitch; Billy Mitchell; Carol Jackson; Chelsea Fox; Jack Branning; Jean Slater; Mo Harris; Charlie Slater; Lucas Johnson; Denise Johnson; Libby Fox; Zainab Masood; Ricky Butcher; Fat Boy; Peter Beale; Bobby Beale; Ben Mitchell; Jordan Johnson; Abi Branning; Reporter; DC Hargreaves; Dr Cameron</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00s37lz</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00s37lz</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5458863919789809122.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>11/04/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Billie Jackson makes a decision that will change his life, but furious Carol is determined to stop him. Meanwhile, Zainab begins to lose control of the Syed situation.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Billie Jackson makes a decision that will change his life, but furious Carol is determined to stop him. Meanwhile, Zainab begins to lose control of the Syed situation, Danny plays Ronnie and Roxy off against each other, and Ben's worst fears become sickening reality.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Christian Clarke; Syed Masood; Zainab Masood; Billie Jackson; Carol Jackson; Max Branning; Whitney Dean; Amira Masood; Masood Ahmed; Tamwar Masood; Pat Evans; Peggy Mitchell; Roxy Mitchell; Danny Mitchell; Glenda Mitchell; Ronnie Mitchell; Phil Mitchell; Billy Mitchell; Minty Peterson; Zsa Zsa Carter; Leon Small; Denise Johnson; Chelsea Fox; Ricky Butcher; Bianca Butcher; Dot Branning; Janine Butcher; Ryan Malloy; Stacey Branning; Shirley Carter; Heather Trott; Abi Branning; Ben Mitchell; Louise Mitchell; Liam Butcher; Mr Steele; Councillor Singh Walia; Recruiting Sergeant; PC Henderson; Terry</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00s6257</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00s6257</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5461430592250097390.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>18/04/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Syed and Christian's secret threatens to come out when Amira enlists Christian's help to seduce her husband and someone witnesses a clandestine tryst.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Syed and Christian's secret threatens to come out when Amira enlists Christian's help to seduce her husband and someone witnesses a clandestine tryst. Meanwhile, Jack emerges from his coma to find that his life may never be the same again, Pat and Peggy go head to head with a charming journo and each other, and Fat Boy gets a one-way ticket to the ladies.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Masood Ahmed; Syed Masood; Christian Clarke; Amira Masood; Zainab Masood; Tanwar Masood; Mitchell, Phil; Shirley Carter; Ben Mitchell; Louise Mitchell; Ronnie Mitchell; Max Branning; Mr Steele; Zsa Zsa Carter; Darren Millar; Fat Boy; Leon Small; Peggy Mitchell; Pat Evans; Roxy Mitchell; Danny Mitchell; Jack Branning; Chelsea Fox; Lucy Beale; Libby Fox; Adam Best; Whitney Dean; Bianca Butcher; Dot Branning; Jim Branning; Billie Jackson; Carol Jackson; Mo Harris; Ricky Butcher; Liam Butcher; Abi Branning; Jordan Johnson; Tasha; Harvey Freeman; Elaine; Julie</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00s62g1</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00s62g1</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5461438323187034145.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>18/04/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Syed and Christian's secret threatens to come out when Amira enlists Christian's help to seduce her husband and someone witnesses a clandestine tryst.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Syed and Christian's secret threatens to come out when Amira enlists Christian's help to seduce her husband and someone witnesses a clandestine tryst. Meanwhile, Jack emerges from his coma to find that his life may never be the same again, Pat and Peggy go head to head with a charming journo and each other, and Fat Boy gets a one-way ticket to the ladies.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Masood Ahmed; Syed Masood; Christian Clarke; Amira Masood; Zainab Masood; Tanwar Masood; Mitchell, Phil; Shirley Carter; Ben Mitchell; Louise Mitchell; Ronnie Mitchell; Max Branning; Mr Steele; Zsa Zsa Carter; Darren Millar; Fat Boy; Leon Small; Peggy Mitchell; Pat Evans; Roxy Mitchell; Danny Mitchell; Jack Branning; Chelsea Fox; Lucy Beale; Libby Fox; Adam Best; Whitney Dean; Bianca Butcher; Dot Branning; Jim Branning; Billie Jackson; Carol Jackson; Mo Harris; Ricky Butcher; Liam Butcher; Abi Branning; Jordan Johnson; Tasha; Harvey Freeman; Elaine; Julie</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00s90gw</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00s90gw</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5464062977701622467.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>25/04/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Syed and Christian hope that Masood did not see them together, but are they hoping in vain? Meanwhile, Shirley and Phil go head to head with the father of Ben's bully.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Syed and Christian hope that Masood did not see them together, but are they hoping in vain?

	Meanwhile, Shirley and Phil go head to head with the father of Ben's bully, Chelsea and Amira get whopping surprises, and Ronnie declares herself to Jack for what could be the last time.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Amira Masood; Syed Masood; Christian Clarke; Masood Ahmed; Zainab Masood; Tanwar Masood; Chelsea Fox; Denise Johnson; Lucas Johnson; Libby Fox; Adam Best; Darren Miller; Bianca Butcher; Jane Beale; Roxy Mitchell; Ronnie Mitchell; Jack Branning; Max Branning; Mr Steele; Peggy Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Heather Trott; Zsa Zsa Carter; Ben Mitchell; Louise Mitchell; Leon Small; Fat Boy; Peter Beale; Whitney Dean; Billie Jackson; Dot Branning; Jim Branning; Charlie Slater; Pat Evans; Jordan Johnson; Qadim Shah; Bushra Abbasi; Imam Ali; Harvey Freeman; Nurse Denton; Tasha's Dad</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00scc0b</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00scc0b</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5466659285432056680.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>02/05/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>The truth about Syed and Christian emerges, with devastating consequences. Whitney is determined that Billie Jackson will not join the army and Ben reveals a darker side to Louise.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>The truth about Syed and Christian emerges, with devastating consequences. Whitney is determined that Billie Jackson will not join the army, Ben reveals a darker side to a terrified Louise, and Peggy and Pat have hot dates - with the same man!</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Masood Ahmed; Zainab Masood; Jane Beale; Christian Clarke; Roxy Mitchell; Ronnie Mitchell; Peggy Mitchell; Pat Evans; Harvey Freeman; Dot Branning; Liz Turner; Lucy Beale; Ian Beale; Shirley Carter; Ben Mitchell; Louise Mitchell; Phil Mitchell; Whitney Dean; Zsa Zsa Carter; Becca Swanson; Fat Boy; Leon Small; Qadim Shah; Amira Masood; Syed Masood; Danny Mitchell; Chelsea Fox; Tamwar Masood; Jack Branning; Billie Jackson; Carol Jackson; Charlie Slater; Mo Harris; Bianca Butcher; Ricky Butcher; Denise Johnson; Lucas Johnson; Libby Fox; Adam Best; Darren Miller; Bushra Abbasi; Mr Lister</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00sfwct</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00sfwct</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5469219515441401057.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>09/05/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Ronnie is desperate to put a smile on Jack's face again, but how far will she go to make it happen? Pressured Billy crosses a line and pays the price.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Ronnie is desperate to put a smile on Jack's face again, but how far will she go to make it happen? Pressured Billy crosses a line and pays the price, Syed makes a promise he can't keep, and Lucy's secret is finally out.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Jack Branning; Ronnie Mitchell; Billy Mitchell; Ian Beale; Jane Beale; Lucy Beale; Peter Beale; Zsa Zsa Carter; Leon Small; Fat Boy; Syed Masood; Masood Ahmed; Zainab Masood; Tamwar Masood; Christian Clarke; Shirley Carter; Heather Trott; Jay Brown; Phil Mitchell; Roxy Mitchell; Danny Mitchell; Carol Jackson; Max Branning; Darren Miller; Minty Peterson; Dot Branning; Peggy Mitchell; Pat Evans; Harvey Freeman; Dr Bickerton; Jonno; PC Lance</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00sj13n</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00sj13n</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5471850612406932231.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>16/05/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Zainab's cruel streak rears its head and Syed hits rock bottom. Ronnie refuses to turn into her father but at what cost to Jack? Ian decides to give Jane what she wants.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Zainab's cruel streak rears its head and Syed hits rock bottom. 

	Ronnie refuses to turn into her father but at what cost to Jack? 

	Ian decides to give Jane what she wants but when he receives bad news from the bank he has to look to the plan B he thought he'd never need.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Zainab Masood; Masood Ahmed; Syed Masood; Tamwar Masood; Christian Clarke; Roxy Mitchell; Ronnie Mitchell; Max Branning; Jack Branning; Danny Mitchell; Billy Mitchell; Heather Trott; Dot Branning; Ian Beale; Jane Beale; Lucy Beale; Peter Beale; Minty Peterson; Chelsea Fox; Phil Mitchell; Ben Mitchell; Louise Mitchell; Jordan Johnson; Darren Miller; Janine Butcher; Charlie Slater; Lucas Johnson; Denise Johnson; Shirley Carter; Jay Brown; Abi Branning; Alex; Imam Ali; Bushra Abbasi; Nadim Abbasi; Mr Lister</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00shrmg</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00shrmg</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5471858343343866390.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>16/05/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Zainab's cruel streak rears its head and Syed hits rock bottom. Ronnie refuses to turn into her father but at what cost to Jack? Ian decides to give Jane what she wants.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Zainab's cruel streak rears its head and Syed hits rock bottom. Ronnie refuses to turn into her father but at what cost to Jack? Ian decides to give Jane what she wants but when he receives bad news from the bank he has to look to the plan B he thought he'd never need...</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Zainab Masood; Masood Ahmed; Syed Masood; Tamwar Masood; Christian Clarke; Roxy Mitchell; Ronnie Mitchell; Max Branning; Jack Branning; Danny Mitchell; Billy Mitchell; Heather Trott; Dot Branning; Ian Beale; Jane Beale; Lucy Beale; Peter Beale; Minty Peterson; Chelsea Fox; Phil Mitchell; Ben Mitchell; Louise Mitchell; Jordan Johnson; Darren Miller; Janine Butcher; Charlie Slater; Lucas Johnson; Denise Johnson; Shirley Carter; Jay Brown; Abi Branning; Alex; Imam Ali; Bushra Abbasi; Nadim Abbasi; Mr Lister</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00slm9q</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00slm9q</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5474441766172415791.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>23/05/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Phil crosses a violent line with Ben. Danny tries to fleece Roxy of all her money, but finds the Mitchell sisters are not an easy target. And Syed returns home.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Phil crosses a violent line with Ben. Danny tries to fleece Roxy of all her money, but finds the Mitchell sisters are not an easy target. And Syed returns home, but the cracks in his family lead him to take drastic action.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Ben Mitchell; Jordan Johnson; Phil Mitchell; Louise Mitchell; Lucas Johnson; Denise Johnson; Chelsea Fox; Stacey Branning; Max Branning; Becca Swanson; Jean Slater; Ryan Malloy; Janine Butcher; Syed Masood; Tamwar Masood; Masood Ahmed; Zainab Masood; Danny Mitchell; Ronnie Mitchell; Roxy Mitchell; Glenda Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Heather Trott; Minty Peterson; Ricky Butcher; Bianca Butcher; Charlie Slater; Mo Harris; Carver; Allen Conlon</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00snyf3</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00snyf3</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5477052247294927142.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>30/05/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Ben's encounter with Jordan ends disastrously, while Whitney's relationship with Billie Jackson takes a very unexpected twist. Meanwhile, Stacey finds maternity leave unbearable.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Ben's encounter with Jordan ends disastrously, while Whitney's relationship with Billie Jackson takes a very unexpected twist. Meanwhile, Stacey finds maternity leave unbearable, and Ryan and Janine battle to win their twisted bet.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Phil Mitchell; Ben Mitchell; Ian Beale; Jordan Johnson; Lucas Johnson; Libby Fox; Chelsea Fox; Denise Johnson; Patrick Trueman; Billie Jackson; Whitney Dean; Bianca Butcher; Leon Small; Fat Boy; Zsa Zsa Carter; Lucy Beale; Adam Best; Minty Peterson; Shirley Carter; Louise Mitchell; Janine Butcher; Ryan Malloy; Stacey Branning; Peter Beale; Danny Mitchell; Becca Swanson; Max Branning; Abi Branning; Mo Harris; Jean Slater; Heather Trott; Darren Miller; Carol Jackson; Liam Butcher; PC Shona Blake; Nurse Denton</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00sr5s7</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00sr5s7</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5479613765790262884.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>06/06/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Lucy's Machievellian plans take chilling and dangerous turns on a road trip, while Pat and Peggy realise that their friendship is all-important.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Lucy's Machievellian plans take chilling and dangerous turns on a road trip, while Pat and Peggy realise that their friendship is all-important when they battle heartbreaking challenges together, and Bianca has to deliver tough news to Liam.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Lucy Beale; Peter Beale; Zsa Zsa Carter; Leon Small; Fat Boy; Whitney Dean; Billie Jackson; Mercy Olbumi; Pat Evans; Peggy Mitchell; Harvey Freeman; Bianca Butcher; Ricky Butcher; Carol Jackson; Dot Branning; Liam Butcher; Darren Miller; Liz Turner; Patrick Trueman; Ian Beale; Libby Fox; Desk Sergeant; Katy; Hayley; Simon James; Andrew; Donald; Vince</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00swk1k</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00swk1k</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5484832151054906012.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>20/06/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Denise is distraught when her marriage hits a turning point. Meanwhile Ryan gets closer to the Slaters, and Roxy and Ronnie make a shocking discovery about Danny.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Denise is distraught when her marriage hits a turning point, and struggles to push her fears about Lucas to one side. Meanwhile Ryan gets closer to the Slaters, and Roxy and Ronnie make a shocking discovery about Danny.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Peggy Mitchell; Pat Evans; Ronnie Mitchell; Roxy Mitchell; Glenda Mitchell; Danny Mitchell; Denise Johnson; Lucas Johnson; Patrick Trueman; Dot Branning; Liz Turner; Jim Branning; Janine Butcher; Ryan Malloy; Stacey Branning; Charlie Slater; Jean Slater; Mo Harris; Becca Swanson; Max Branning; Darren Miller; Jodie Gold; Libby Fox; Adam Best; Chelsea Fox; Phil Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Jordan Johnson; Abi Branning; Jade</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>none</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/none</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5487392381060028758.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>27/06/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Lucy plays a dangerous game with Adam. When a frantic Stacey goes into labour, the only person she doesn't want to see is the one person who ends up being there for her.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription></episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters></episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00t1qkf</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00t1qkf</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5489989977280645307.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>04/07/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Lucas and Denise's world spirals out of control. Peggy and Glenda continue to snipe at each other, Ryan's shocked at Janine's state, and Stacey names her baby.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Lucas and Denise's world spirals out of control. Peggy and Glenda continue to snipe at each other, Ryan's shocked at Janine's state, and Stacey names her baby.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Denise Johnson; Liz Turner; Lucas Johnson; Glenda Mitchell; Peggy Mitchell; Roxy Mitchell; Ronnie Mitchell; Leon Small; Zsa Zsa Carter; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Mercy Olubunmi; Ryan Malloy; Janine Butcher; Stacey Branning; Mo Harris; Pat Evans; Patrick Trueman; Chelsea Fox; Libby Fox; Adam Best; Jordan Johnson; Minty Peterson; Dot Branning; Shirley Carter; Jean Slater; Becca Swanson; Charlie Slater; Gloria Fisher; Rob Wilkins; DI Kelly; Prostitute</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00t3trv</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00t3trv</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5492642978579388802.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>11/07/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Libby and Chelsea are broken by a shattering revelation, while Ian sees a different side to Phil. Darren loses Minty's friendship, and Christian has a brand new business venture.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Libby and Chelsea are broken girls when the police make a shattering revelation. Elsewhere, Ian sees a different side to Phil as he tries to do his best for Ben, Darren's foolishness loses him Minty's friendship and a roof over his head, and Christian has a brand new business venture.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Shirley Carter; Phil Mitchell; Ben Mitchell; Lucas Johnson; Libby Fox; Chelsea Fox; Patrick Trueman; Denise Johnson; Liz Turner; Jack Branning; Ronnie Mitchell; Glenda Mitchell; Peggy Mitchell; Roxy Mitchell; Christian Clarke; Syed Masood; Zainab Masood; Darren Miller; Jodie Gold; Max Branning; Abi Branning; Minty Peterson; Ian Beale; Jane Beale; Heather Trott; Zsa Zsa Carter; Mercy Olubunmi; Ryan Malloy; Janine Butcher; Dot Branning; Mo Harris; Adam Best; Louise Mitchell; Jordan Johnson; Ritchie Scott; DI Kelly; Allen Conlon</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00t6t6g</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00t6t6g</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5495222535941565020.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>18/07/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>While Lucas identifies a body, Chelsea and Libby struggle to deal with recent events. Syed comes to a life-changing decision. The Mitchells are shocked by Ben's prison sentence.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>While Lucas has to identify a body at the morgue, Chelsea and Libby struggle to come to terms with recent events. Syed comes to a life-changing decision. The Mitchells are shocked by Ben's prison sentence.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Syed Masood; Christian Clarke; Masood Ahmed; Zainab Masood; Tamwar Masood; Peggy Mitchell; Phil Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Ben Mitchell; Ian Beale; Jane Beale; Lucy Beale; Peter Beale; Stacey Branning; Jean Slater; Becca Swanson; Ronnie Mitchell; Jack Branning; Roxy Mitchell; Libby Fox; Adam Best; Patrick Trueman; Chelsea Fox; Lucas Johnson; Jordan Johnson; Heather Trott; Billy Mitchell; Jay Brown; Zsa Zsa Carter; Darren Miller; Abi Branning; MaX Branning; Carol Jackson; Louise Mitchell; Bushra Abbasi; Ina Foot; Ritchie Scott; DI Kelly; Allen Conlon; Judge</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00t932d</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00t932d</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5497831728569688871.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>25/07/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Peggy and Glenda are shocked at Ronnie's shattering revelation, Patrick tries to come to terms with Denise's death, and Christian tries to get under the skin of Syed's religion.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Peggy and Glenda are shocked at Ronnie's shattering revelation, Patrick struggles to come to terms with Denise's death, and Christian tries to get under the skin of Syed's religion. Meanwhile, Phil finds Ben coping with prison - but is everything what it seems?

	If you are affected by any of the issues in this episode of EastEnders, please visit the below website for information regarding sources of help, support, and advice:
	http://www.bbc.co.uk/eastenders/news/news_20081104.shtml.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Lucas Johnson; Chelsea Fox; Libby Fox; Patrick Trueman; Kim Fox; Liz Turner; Daphne Fox; Peggy Mitchell; Roxy Mitchell; Ronnie Mitchell; Glenda Mitchell; Jack Branning; Max Branning; Darren Miller; Jodie Gold; Abi Branning; Tamwar Masood; Syed Masood; Christian Clarke; Zainab Masood; Masood Ahmed; Pat Evans; Shirley Carter; Jane Beale; Heather Trott; Billy Mitchell; Minty Peterson; Phil Mitchell; Ben Mitchell; Louise Mitchell; Jim Branning; Dot Branning; Jordan Johnson; Lucy Beale; Peter Beale; Adam Best; Olive Woodhouse; Dagenham Derek Smith; Mr Barker; Cal Childs</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00tbskn</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00tbskn</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5500429324790314097.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>01/08/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Lucas begins to unravel as his family's grief takes an unexpected turn. Phil gets an unwelcome visit from the social, while Darren treads the never-smooth path of true love.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Lucas begins to unravel as his family's grief takes an unexpected turn. Phil gets an unwelcome visit from the social, while Darren treads the never-smooth path of true love. The Square comes together for some fun in the sun, but Peggy is devastated when Roxy makes a shocking decision about the fate of the Vic.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Peggy Mitchell; Pat Evans; Phil Mitchell; Ben Mitchell; Lucas Johnson; Libby Fox; Chelsea Fox; Jordan Johnson; Patrick Trueman; Zainab Masood; Tamwar Masood; Darren Miller; Jodie Gold; Zsa Zsa Carter; Dot Branning; Liz Turner; Max Branning; Jack Branning; Stacey Branning; Heather Trott; Roxy Mitchell; Charlie Slater; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Mercy Olubunmi; Grace Olubunmi; Bianca Butcher; Ricky Butcher; Glenda Mitchell; Louise Mitchell; Abi Branning; Liam Butcher; Rob Stevenson; Custody Officer; Cal Childs; Reverend Wallace; Derek Evans</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00tfbzk</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00tfbzk</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5503024344030559423.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>08/08/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Phil's worst nightmare becomes a reality, sending him spiralling into his darkest tailspin yet. Meanwhile Max battles with woman trouble, and Carol has a shot at romance.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Phil's worst nightmare becomes a reality as he spirals into his darkest tailspin yet. Meanwhile Max battles with woman trouble, Carol has a shot at romance, and Walford bids farewell to a much-loved pair.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Phil Mitchell; Rainie Cross; Carol Jackson; Bianca Butcher; Ricky Butcher; Max Branning; Abi Branning; Darren Miller; Peggy Mitchell; Lisa Fowler; Louise Mitchell; Pat Evans; Patrick Trueman; Libby Fox; Chelsea Fox; Kim Fox; Liz Turner; Jordan Johnson; Shirley Carter; Minty Peterson; Jane Beale; Dot Branning; Liam Butcher; Tiffany Butcher; Morgan Jackson-King; Whitney Dean; Zsa Zsa Carter; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Leon Small; Billy Mitchell; Zainab Masood; Syed Masood; Vanessa Gold; Mo Harris; Roxy Mitchell; Derek Evans; Vicar; Gaynor Lucas; Sgt Lewis Daley; Police Officer; Custody Officer</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00th87t</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00th87t</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5505620651760993161.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>15/08/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Phil's descent into crack oblivion takes a darker turn when he hatches a chilling plan. Meanwhile, Carol makes a humiliatingly public accusation.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Phil's descent into crack oblivion takes a darker turn when he hatches a chilling plan. Meanwhile, Carol makes a humiliatingly public accusation - and does a shock engagement spell happiness at last for the Square's most-tortured couple?</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Phil Mitchell; Rainie Cross; Peggy Mitchell; Roxy Mitchell; Ronnie Mitchell; Jack Branning; Carol Jackson; Bianca Butcher; Ricky Butcher; Billie Jackson; Whitney Dean; Ryan Malloy; Janine Butcher; Pat Evans; Dot Branning; Shirley Carter; Max Branning; Minty Peterson; Abi Branning; Liam Butcher; Tiffany Butcher; Morgan Jackson-King; Zainab Masood; Tamwar Masood; Heather Trott; Glenda Mitchell; Kim Fox; Stacey Branning; Ken Tate; Waiter; Colin Logan; CAB Advisor</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00tl9bk</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00tl9bk</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5508218247981616465.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>22/08/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Ronnie and Roxy launch the new R&amp;R, but Glenda has a secret which blows the night apart. Shirley is torn between helping Phil and keeping the bailiffs from the door.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Ronnie and Roxy launch the new R&amp;R, but Glenda has a secret which blows the night apart. Shirley is torn between helping Phil and keeping the bailiffs from the door. Carol is persuaded to get dating; after early nerves, has she got her va va voom back? And Darren goes to extreme lengths to win Jodie over, but has it all been for nothing?</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Sam Mitchell; Peggy Mitchell; Phil Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Ronnie Mitchell; Roxy Mitchell; Jack Branning; Carol Jackson; Bianca Butcher; Ricky Butcher; Pat Evans; Max Branning; Darren Miller; Vanessa Gold; Jodie Gold; Abi Branning; Heather Trott; Minty Peterson; Billy Mitchell; Glenda Mitchell; Sal Martin; Zsa Zsa Carter; Mercy Olubunmi; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Leon Small; Christian Clarke; Syed Masood; Whitney Dean; Liam Butcher; Morgan Jackson-King; Rainie Cross; Harry Gold; Sgt Lewis Daley; Bailiff</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00tmtv6</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00tmtv6</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5510818421182616259.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>29/08/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Minty pinballs from woman to woman; where will he end up? The Beales get a shock, Christian and Roxy rediscover their youth, and Tamwar holds firm in the face of his mother's fire.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Minty pinballs from woman to woman - where will he end up? Meanwhile, the Beales get a nasty shock, Christian and Roxy rediscover their boozy youth, and Tamwar holds firm in the face of his mother's fire.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Jane Beale; Denise Johnson; Ian Beale; Lucy Beale; Peter Beale; Stacey Branning; Max Branning; Vanessa Gold; Abi Branning; Becca Swanson; Dot Branning; Jean Slater; Mo Harris; Heather Trott; Minty Peterson; Shirley Carter; Syed Masood; Tamwar Masood; Zainab Masood; Masood Ahmed; Zsa Zsa Carter; Darren Miller; Jordan Johnson; Christian Clarke; Roxy Mitchell; Grace Olubunmi; Mercy Olubunmi; Leon Small; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Ricky Butcher; Bianca Butcher; Sam Mitchell; Peggy Mitchell; Kim Fox; Bobby Beale; Mr Allcock; Sales Assistant; Officer Tamsin Reilly</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00tr2kk</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00tr2kk</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5513413440422861390.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>05/09/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Ricky panics when Sam tells him he is the father of her baby, but how will he break the news to Bianca? Jean remains powerless as Becca continues to manipulate Stacey against her.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Ricky panics when Sam tells him he is the father of her baby, but how will he break the news to Bianca? Jean remains powerless as Becca continues to manipulate Stacey against her, and Peggy is horrified when she finally tracks down Phil.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Peggy Mitchell; Phil Mitchell; Billy Mitchell; Sam Mitchell; Ricky Butcher; Bianca Butcher; Carol Jackson; Jack Branning; Ronnie Mitchell; Roxy Mitchell; Pat Evans; Janine Malloy; Ryan Malloy; Stacey Branning; Jean Slater; Becca Swanson; Whitney Dean; Minty Peterson; Heather Trott; Shirley Carter; Denise Johnson; Kim Fox; Jane Beale; Ian Beale; Dot Branning; Jay Brown; Jordan Johnson; Liam Butcher; Tiffany Butcher; Morgan Jackson-King; Bobby Beale; Sgt Lewis Daley; Officer Tamsin Reilly; Matt Hearn; Tim Kenward; Brogan Callan</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00tv7dy</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00tv7dy</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5516014902114050495.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>12/09/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Peggy resumes ownership of the Vic, while Phil continues to descend into his private hell. Janine and Ryan's wedding day is unexpectedly halted, and Stacey spirals out of control.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Peggy resumes ownership of the Vic, while Phil continues to descend into his own private hell. Janine and Ryan's wedding day is unexpectedly halted, and Stacey spirals out of control, with truly shocking consequences.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Peggy Mitchell; Phil Mitchell; Billy Mitchell; Sam Mitchell; Ronnie Mitchell; Roxy Mitchell; Stacey Branning; Ryan Malloy; Janine Malloy; Pat Evans; Whitney Dean; Bianca Butcher; Ricky Butcher; Carol Jackson; Minty Peterson; Glenda Mitchell; Dot Branning; Ian Beale; Jane Beale; Peter Beale; Mo Harris; Charlie Slater; Jean Slater; Patrick Trueman; Jay Brown; Denise Johnson; Kim Fox; Shirley Carter; Heather Trott; Max Branning; Vanessa Gold; Jodie Gold; Darren Miller; Jack Branning; Zainab Masood; Masood Ahmed; Syed Masood; Tamwar Masood; Christian Clarke; Liam Butcher; Tiffany Butcher; Morgan Jackson-King; Richard Monroe; Male Stripper; Celebrant; Nurse Denton; DS Andrew Newton</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00txwmn</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00txwmn</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5518616363805241247.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>19/09/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Morals are discarded with shocking consequences as the result of the paternity test is revealed. The Mitchells struggle to cope and a familiar face returns to Albert Square.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Morals are discarded with shocking consequences as the result of the paternity test is finally revealed. The Mitchells struggle to cope in the aftermath of the Vic fire, and a familiar face returns to Albert Square.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Kat Moon; Mo Harris; Charlie Slater; Stacey Branning; Sam Mitchell; Jack Branning; Ronnie Mitchell; Roxy Mitchell; Minty Peterson; Heather Trott; Phil Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Kim Fox; Patrick Trueman; Denise Johnson; Darren Miller; Jodie Gold; Ricky Butcher; Bianca Butcher; Pat Evans; Dot Branning; Billy Mitchell; Jim Branning; Jean Slater; Liam Butcher; Carol Jackson; Glenda Mitchell; Jay Brown; Reverend Stevens; Policeman; Maria de Costa</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00v3kdy</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00v3kdy</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5521212671535675656.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>26/09/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>The Slater family find themselves in jeopardy as Kat and Alfie return to Albert Square. Meanwhile, Minty makes a life-changing decision, and Darren's dreams come true while Max's fall apart.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>The Slater family find themselves in jeopardy as Kat and Alfie return to Albert Square. Meanwhile, Minty makes a life-changing decision, and Darren's dreams come true while Max's fall apart.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Alfie Moon; Kat Moon; Charlie Slater; Mo Harris; Stacey Branning; Jean Slater; Heather Trott; Minty Peterson; Dot Branning; Sam Mitchell; Phil Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Max Branning; Darren Miller; Jodie Gold; Vanessa Gold; Harry Gold; Bianca Butcher; Carol Jackson; Glenda Mitchell; Roxy Mitchell; Leon Small; Zsa Zsa Carter; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Billy Mitchell; Patrick Trueman; Jane Beale; Ronnie Mitchell; Jay Brown; Lee Finnerty; Jono Finnerty; Reverend Stevens</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00v8ln0</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00v8ln0</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5523757439662722521.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>03/10/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Janine's world is ripped apart by a shocking revelation. Max struggles to cope when Lauren returns home, and Zsa Zsa and Leon prepare to bid a fond farewell to Walford.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Janine's world is ripped apart by a shocking revelation, but will she choose revenge over Ryan? Max struggles to cope when Lauren returns home, and Zsa Zsa and Leon prepare to bid a fond farewell to Walford. Alfie and Kat set up home together, but could a new arrival threaten their happiness?</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Kat Moon; Alfie Moon; Michael Moon; Phil Mitchell; Bianca Butcher; Max Branning; Tanya Branning; Lauren Branning; Abi Branning; Greg Jessop; Vanessa Gold; Jodie Gold; Darren Miller; Harry Gold; Janine Malloy; Ryan Malloy; Stacey Branning; Jean Slater; Pat Evans; Charlie Slater; Shirley Carter; Zsa Zsa Carter; Leon Small; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Mercy Olubunmi; Grace Olubunmi; Heather Trott; Masood Ahmed; Christian Clarke; Patrick Trueman; Ricky Butcher; Whitney Dean; Jim Branning; Maria de Costa; Edward Brooks</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00v8n69</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00v8n69</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5523772901540793112.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>03/10/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Janine's world is ripped apart by a shocking revelation. Max struggles to cope when Lauren returns home, and Zsa Zsa and Leon prepare to bid a fond farewell to Walford.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Janine's world is ripped apart by a shocking revelation, but will she choose revenge over Ryan? Max struggles to cope when Lauren returns home, and Zsa Zsa and Leon prepare to bid a fond farewell to Walford. Alfie and Kat set up home together, but could a new arrival threaten their happiness?</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Kat Moon; Alfie Moon; Michael Moon; Phil Mitchell; Bianca Butcher; Max Branning; Tanya Branning; Lauren Branning; Abi Branning; Greg Jessop; Vanessa Gold; Jodie Gold; Darren Miller; Harry Gold; Janine Malloy; Ryan Malloy; Stacey Branning; Jean Slater; Pat Evans; Charlie Slater; Shirley Carter; Zsa Zsa Carter; Leon Small; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Mercy Olubunmi; Grace Olubunmi; Heather Trott; Masood Ahmed; Christian Clarke; Patrick Trueman; Ricky Butcher; Whitney Dean; Jim Branning; Maria de Costa; Edward Brooks</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00vf727</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00vf727</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5526405286996514129.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>10/10/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Alfie's world is blown apart after Michael works out Kat's secret - but will he be able to forgive his wife? A letter from Billy's past has terrible consequences for Jay.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Alfie's world is blown apart after Michael works out Kat's secret - but will he be able to forgive his wife? A letter from Billy's past has terrible consequences for Jay, and Carol starts to prepare for Billie's birthday homecoming, but is persuaded to take a detour into romance.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Alfie Moon; Kat Moon; Michael Moon; Billy Mitchell; Jean Slater; Stacey Branning; Whitney Dean; Glenda Mitchell; Carol Jackson; Bianca Butcher; Zainab Masood; Kim Fox; Grace Olubunmi; Dot Branning; Mercy Olubunmi; Mo Harris; Jack Branning; Phil Mitchell; Darren Miller; Lauren Branning; Greg Jessop; Sgt Lewis Daley; Thommo Newby; Claudia Maskry</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00vfgr9</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00vfgr9</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5526436210765238209.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>10/10/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Alfie's world is blown apart after Michael works out Kat's secret - but will he be able to forgive his wife? A letter from Billy's past has terrible consequences for Jay.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Alfie's world is blown apart after Michael works out Kat's secret - but will he be able to forgive his wife? A letter from Billy's past has terrible consequences for Jay, and Carol starts to prepare for Billie's birthday homecoming, but is persuaded to take a detour into romance.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Alfie Moon; Kat Moon; Michael Moon; Billy Mitchell; Jay Brown; Phil Mitchell; Billie Jackson; Carol Jackson; Bianca Butcher; Ricky Butcher; Liam Butcher; Kim Fox; Whitney Dean; Peter Beale; Lauren Branning; Max Branning; Jack Branning; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Dot Branning; Grace Olubunmi; Mercy Olubunmi; Charlie Slater; Jean Slater; Stacey Branning; Pat Evans; Greg Jessop; Connor Stanley; Sonographer; DS Mulligan</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00vj37c</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00vj37c</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5528984844354493562.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>17/10/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Carol struggles to deal with the death of her son. A furious Bianca confronts Kim when she hears she kissed Ricky, and Billy is shocked by the arrival of a face from his past.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Carol struggles with the death of her son and lashes out at all sides. A furious Bianca confronts Kim when she hears she kissed Ricky, and Billy is shocked by the arrival of a face from his past.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Billy Mitchell; Julie Perkins; Carol Jackson; Billie Jackson; Bianca Butcher; Ricky Butcher; Whitney Dean; Max Branning; Jack Branning; Phil Mitchell; Jay Brown; Kim Fox; Peter Beale; Jane Beale; Patrick Trueman; Denise Johnson; Kat Moon; Lauren Branning; Abi Branning; Tanya Branning; Vanessa Gold; Greg Jessop; Alan Jackson; Pat Evans; Liam Butcher; Tiffany Butcher; Morgan Jackson-King; Darren Miller; Jim Branning; Alfie Moon; Connor Stanley; Reverend Stevens; Sgt Major Banfield; Doctor; PC Lance; Paramedic</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00vmzwm</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00vmzwm</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5531550228324592939.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>24/10/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>An ill-advised drink at R and R descends into chaos when Billy lashes out in all directions. A night in the cells has unexpected consequences for Janine and Stacey.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>An ill-advised drink at R and R descends into chaos when Billy lashes out in all directions. A night in the cells has unexpected consequences for Janine and Stacey, while Ryan reaches a momentous decision about Lily. Bianca's attempt to support a grieving Carol leads to a devastating outburst. Alfie's financial worries are lifted by a surprise benefactor.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Carol Jackson; Bianca Butcher; Liam Butcher; Ricky Butcher; Whitney Dean; Max Branning; Jack Branning; Dot Branning; Lauren Branning; Pat Evans; Ryan Malloy; Janine Malloy; Stacey Branning; Kat Moon; Alfie Moon; Roxy Mitchell; Phil Mitchell; Billy Mitchell; Julie Perkins; Jay Brown; Christian Clark; Syed Masood; Kim Fox; Jean Slater; Jim Branning; Charlie Slater; Patrick Trueman; Morgan Jackson-King; Sgt Stone</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00vv10f</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00vv10f</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5534228999422914578.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>31/10/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Billie's funeral has shocking consequences as an isolated Carol struggles to cope with her grief, and Janine appals Ryan as her unhinged behaviour spirals out of control.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Billie's funeral has shocking consequences as an isolated Carol struggles to cope with her grief, Janine appals Ryan as her unhinged behaviour spirals out of control, and Max accidentally reveals a dangerous truth to Lauren. Meanwhile, Kat and Alfie's grand plans for the Vic's opening suffer a setback.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Janine Malloy; Ryan Malloy; Stacey Branning; Kat Moon; Alfie Moon; Carol Jackson; Glenda Mitchell; Pat Evans; Bianca Butcher; Ricky Butcher; Max Branning; Lauren Branning; Jack Branning; Vanessa Gold; Darren Miller; Jodie Gold; Jay Brown; Billy Mitchell; Julie Perkins; Charlie Slater; Jean Slater; Masood Ahmed; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Mercy Olubunmi; Tanya Branning; Greg Jessop; Dot Branning; Jim Branning; Alan Jackson; Blossom Jackson; Harry Gold; Abi Branning; Liam Butcher; Morgan Jackson-King; Whitney Dean; Peter Beale; Tracey; Connor Stanley; Mitch Gannon; Mr Lister; Vicky Saunders</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00w6cxm</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00w6cxm</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5539381671692122744.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>14/11/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>It's Ronnie and Jack's wedding, but a nasty surprise awaits the happy couple. Alfie and Kat get their own special moment closer to home and Jane is left guilty by Ian's kindness.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>It's Ronnie and Jack's wedding, but a nasty surprise awaits the happy couple on their big day. Alfie and Kat get their own special moment closer to home and Jane is left guilty by Ian's kindness. Roxy is distraught when she loses everything, and a shock lies in store for Lauren.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Vanessa Gold; Jodie Gold; Harry Gold; Max Branning; Darren Miller; Kat Moon; Alfie Moon; Roxy Mitchell; Ronnie Mitchell; Jack Branning; Ian Beale; Jane Beale; Connor Stanley; Sal Martin; Bianca Butcher; Stacey Branning; Mo Harris; Charlie Slater; Jean Slater; Glenda Mitchell; Carol Jackson; Billy Mitchell; Jay Brown; Kim Fox; Heather Trott; Phil Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Masood Ahmed; Tamwar Masood; Julie Perkins; Dot Branning; Lauren Branning; Jim Branning; Hotel Manager; Superintendent Registrar; Stripper</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00wckff</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00wckff</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5542003749222140011.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>21/11/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Max struggles to contain an increasingly unstable Lauren, while Stacey wrestles with her conscience. Carol seeks answers in ill-advised places when she receives Billie's ashes.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Max struggles to contain an increasingly unstable Lauren, while Stacey wrestles with her conscience about Bradley. Carol seeks answers in ill-advised places when she receives Billie's ashes, and Shirley's generous spirit causes friction with Phil. Meanwhile, Darren and Jodie help Tamwar out on his first date with Afia.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Max Branning; Jean Slater; Ryan Malloy; Stacey Branning; Lauren Branning; Vanessa Gold; Shirley Carter; Phil Mitchell; Billy Mitchell; Julie Perkins; Roxy Mitchell; Tamwar Masood; Afia Khan; Zainab Masood; Masood Ahmed; Jodie Gold; Darren Miller; Bianca Butcher; Carol Jackson; Connor Stanley; Connor Stanley; Janine Butcher; Heather Trott; Whitney Dean; Peter Beale; Tiffany Butcher; Abi Branning</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00wkf11</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00wkf11</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5544574287152993687.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>28/11/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>A desperate Janine goes to unnerving lengths to stop Ryan from seeing Stacey, and the Masood household is rocked to the core by a chilling visitor from the past.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>A desperate Janine goes to unnerving lengths to stop Ryan from seeing Stacey, the Masood household is rocked to the core by a chilling visitor from the past, and Ian and Jane's marriage threatens to fall apart - but who will Jane turn to for comfort? Meanwhile, Shirley's concerns turn to unbridled joy when Phil reveals his latest investment and Glenda's manhunt culminates in a startling admission.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Masood Ahmed; Jane Beale; Ian Beale; Zainab Masood; Janine Malloy; Ryan Malloy; Pat Evans; Phil Mitchell; Glenda Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Alfie Moon; Kat Moon; Bianca Butcher; Carol Jackson; Connor Stanley; Patrick Trueman; Billy Mitchell; Christian Clarke; Peter Beale; Tamwar Masood; Afia Khan; Yusef Khan; Ricky Butcher; Denise Johnson; Mo Harris; Whitney Dean; Jay Brown; Vanessa Gold; Lauren Branning; Max Branning; Roxy Mitchell; Heather Trott; Mr Atherton; Bushra Abbasi; Maria De Costa; Lad</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00wh0vn</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00wh0vn</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5544620672795594434.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>28/11/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>A desperate Janine goes to unnerving lengths to stop Ryan from seeing Stacey, and the Masood household is rocked to the core by a chilling visitor from the past.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>A desperate Janine goes to unnerving lengths to stop Ryan from seeing Stacey, the Masood household is rocked to the core by a chilling visitor from the past, and Ian and Jane's marriage threatens to fall apart - but who will Jane turn to for comfort? Meanwhile, Shirley's concerns turn to unbridled joy when Phil reveals his latest investment, and Glenda's manhunt culminates in a startling admission.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Masood Ahmed; Jane Beale; Ian Beale; Zainab Masood; Janine Malloy; Ryan Malloy; Pat Evans; Phil Mitchell; Glenda Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Alfie Moon; Kat Moon; Bianca Butcher; Carol Jackson; Connor Stanley; Patrick Trueman; Billy Mitchell; Christian Clarke; Peter Beale; Tamwar Masood; Afia Khan; Yusef Khan; Ricky Butcher; Denise Johnson; Mo Harris; Whitney Dean; Jay Brown; Vanessa Gold; Lauren Branning; Max Branning; Roxy Mitchell; Heather Trott; Mr Atherton; Bushra Abbasi; Maria de Costa; Lad</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00wnrvk</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00wnrvk</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5547193787702629969.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>05/12/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>A desperate Ryan tries to track down Stacey and Lily, but will Kat help or hinder him in his quest? Emotions run high when Jane makes a shocking confession to Ian.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>A desperate Ryan tries to track down Stacey and Lily, but will Kat help or hinder him in his quest? Emotions run high when Jane makes a shocking confession to Ian, and Syed wrestles with a secret that could destroy his parents' marriage. Dot embarks on a new venture with the help of Heather and Fat Boy, while Julie's first day in the Vic ends in chaos. Glenda turns to her familiar tricks when she finds herself in financial difficulties.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Billy Mitchell; Julie Perkins; Ryan Malloy; Stacey Branning; Masood Ahmed; Zainab Masood; Jane Beale; Ian Beale; Glenda Mitchell; Kat Moon; Janine Malloy; Syed Masood; Christian Clarke; Tamwar Masood; Afia Khan; Dot Branning; Heather Trott; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Phil Mitchell; Carol Jackson; Charlie Slater; Jean Slater; Mo Harris; Patrick Trueman; Jim Branning; Peter Beale; Lauren Branning; Grace Olubunmi; Mercy Olubunmi; Edward Bishop; Cab Driver</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00ww7h1</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00ww7h1</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5549784941472309008.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>12/12/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>A conflicted Pat wrestles with a secret that could destroy Janine's marriage, while Ryan struggles to contain a volatile Whitney when she realises the truth about Stacey.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>As Janine prepares for her perfect Christmas, a conflicted Pat wrestles with a secret that could destroy her marriage. Ryan struggles to contain a volatile Whitney when she realises the truth about Stacey, and Jane is thrown by Peter's startling revelation. Billy and Julie's road trip leads to a run-in with the police, and a drunken Ian causes chaos at Peter's birthday party.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Janine Malloy; Ryan Malloy; Stacey Branning; Kat Moon; Jean Slater; Pat Evans; Glenda Mitchell; Phil Mitchell; Billy Mitchell; Julie Perkins; Ian Beale; Jane Beale; Peter Beale; Whitney Dean; Christian Clarke; Syed Masood; Lauren Branning; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Dot Branning; Alfie Moon; Shirley Carter; Jay Brown; Mo Harris; Bobby Beale; Connor Stanley; Maria de Costa; Roger Green; Policeman</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00x3373</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00x3373</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5552368364300855101.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>19/12/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Glenda is the victim of a terrifying act of violence after her outburst at the Mitchells' party. Meanwhile, Ben makes an explosive return home to the Square.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Glenda is the victim of a terrifying act of violence after her outburst at the Mitchells' party. Meanwhile, Ben makes an explosive return home to the Square, and Ryan's life hangs in the balance as Janine carries out her chilling revenge. Carol is horrified when Connor sets his sights on Whitney.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Janine Malloy; Ryan Malloy; Stacey Branning; Ronnie Branning; Jack Branning; Max Branning; Glenda Mitchell; Ian Beale; Jane Beale; Peter Beale; Phil Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Ben Mitchell; Jay Mitchell; Whitney Dean; Carol Jackson; Bianca Butcher; Ricky Butcher; Kat Moon; Jean Slater; Denise Johnson; Kim Fox; Dot Branning; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Billy Mitchell; Julie Perkins; Roxy Mitchell; Lauren Branning; Abi Branning; Heather Trott; Alfie Moon; Pat Evans; Connor Stanley; Morgan Jackson-King</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00x2yjk</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00x2yjk</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5555325449284154780.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>27/12/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Janine carries out her final, devastating act of revenge against Stacey, but will Max and Ryan be able to save her? Meanwhile, Jean is left horrified by a shocking discovery.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Janine carries out her final, devastating act of revenge against Stacey, but will Max and Ryan be able to save her? Jean is left horrified by a shocking discovery while Ronnie and Roxy vow to see justice done. Ian accidentally reveals a dangerous truth to Peter, and Glenda is caught out when Phil stumbles across her secret. Denise is left heartbroken by Jordan's decision, and Bianca resorts to desperate measures to give her children a special Christmas. Dot's nose is put out of joint as Kim and Fat Boy join forces to save the carol concert.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Ryan Malloy; Janine Malloy; Stacey Branning; Max Branning; Jean Slater; Ronnie Branning; Roxy Mitchell; Kat Moon; Alfie Moon; Lauren Branning; Tanya Branning; Abi Branning; Greg Jessop; Vanessa Gold; Dot Branning; Pat Evans; Bianca Butcher; Ricky Butcher; Charlie Slater; Mo Harris; Phil Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Heather Trott; Billy Mitchell; Julie Perkins; Jay Mitchell; Ben Mitchell; Kim Fox; Denise Johnson; Jordan Johnson; Gloria MacDonald; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Darren Miller; Jodie Gold; Mercy Olubunmi; Patrick Trueman; Ian Beale; Jane Beale; Peter Beale; Glenda Mitchell; Carol Jackson; Whitney Dean; Connor Stanley; Zainab Masood; Edward Bishop; Liam Butcher; Tiffany Butcher; Morgan Jackson-King; Bobby Beale; PC Heathcote; PC Lance; Stallholder; Doctor; Nurse Kennedy</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00x2z5l</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00x2z5l</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5555360238519252381.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>27/12/2010</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Janine carries out her final, devastating act of revenge against Stacey, but will Max and Ryan be able to save her? Meanwhile, Jean is left horrified by a shocking discovery. Also in HD.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Janine carries out her final, devastating act of revenge against Stacey, but will Max and Ryan be able to save her? Jean is left horrified by a shocking discovery while Ronnie and Roxy vow to see justice done. Ian accidentally reveals a dangerous truth to Peter, and Glenda is caught out when Phil stumbles across her secret. Denise is left heartbroken by Jordan's decision, and Bianca resorts to deseperate measures to give her children a special Christmas. Dot's nose is put out of joint as Kim and Fat Boy join forces to save the carol concert.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Ryan Malloy; Janine Malloy; Stacey Branning; Max Branning; Jean Slater; Ronnie Branning; Roxy Mitchell; Kat Moon; Alfie Moon; Lauren Branning; Tanya Branning; Abi Branning; Greg Jessop; Vanessa Gold; Dot Branning; Pat Evans; Bianca Butcher; Ricky Butcher; Charlie Slater; Mo Harris; Phil Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Heather Trott; Billy Mitchell; Julie Perkins; Jay Mitchell; Ben Mitchell; Kim Fox; Denise Johnson; Jordan Johnson; Gloria MacDonald; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Darren Miller; Jodie Gold; Mercy Olubunmi; Patrick Trueman; Ian Beale; Jane Beale; Peter Beale; Glenda Mitchell; Carol Jackson; Whitney Dean; Connor Stanley; Zainab Masood; Edward Bishop; Liam Butcher; Tiffany Butcher; Morgan Jackson-King; Bobby Beale; PC Heathcote; PC Lance; Stallholder; Doctor; Nurse Kennedy</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00xc954</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00xc954</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5557581595604745631.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>02/01/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Kat and Alfie are confronted with heartrending tragedy when Ronnie's grief leads to a momentary act of desperation with devastating consequences. Also in HD.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Kat and Alfie are confronted with heartrending tragedy when Ronnie's grief leads to a momentary act of desperation with devastating consequences. Meanwhile Carol continues to succumb to temptation, much to Tiffany's horror, and a broken Jean makes a painful decision. Dot hosts a party to show her guests the true spirit of Christmas, while Pat turns her back on Janine for good.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Ronnie Branning; Jack Branning; Kat Moon; Alfie Moon; Charlie Slater; Mo Harris; Roxy Mitchell; Christian Clarke; Ian Beale; Jane Beale; Tanya Branning; Greg Jessop; Max Branning; Lauren Branning; Whitney Dean; Carol Jackson; Connor Stanley; Bianca Butcher; Ricky Butcher; Masood Ahmed; Zainab Masood; Denise Johnson; Kim Fox; Patrick Trueman; Darren Miller; Jodie Gold; Shirley Carter; Heather Trott; Billy Mitchell; Julie Perkins; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Mercy Olubunmi; Glenda Mitchell; Dot Branning; Edward Bishop; Jean Slater; Phil Mitchell; Pat Evans; Janine Malloy; Ryan Malloy; Liam Butcher; Tiffany Butcher; Morgan Jackson-King; Nurse; Piper; Midwife Diane; Midwife Brigitte</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00xjw2f</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00xjw2f</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5560179191825337466.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>09/01/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>As Kat and Alfie struggle to come to terms with the loss of Tommy, a terrible shock awaits them at the hospital. A tormented Ronnie's actions leave her trapped in a web of deceit. Also in HD.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>As Kat and Alfie struggle to come to terms with the loss of Tommy, a terrible shock awaits them at the hospital. A tormented Ronnie's actions leave her trapped in a web of deceit as Jack vows to uncover the reason for her anguish. Phil and Ian form an uneasy alliance against Glenda to protect Ben, while Charlie wrestles with a terrible secret. Tanya has good news to share with Max and the girls, and Christian tells Syed that he thinks two should become three. Tiffany decides to let Liam know the truth about Carol.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Glenda Mitchell; Phil Mitchell; Ian Beale; Ben Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Jay Mitchell; Jane Beale; Kat Moon; Charlie Slater; Alfie Moon; Jack Branning; Ronnie Branning; Roxy Mitchell; Max Branning; Tanya Branning; Greg Jessop; Lauren Branning; Abi Branning; Dot Branning; Christian Clarke; Syed Masood; Bianca Butcher; Ricky Butcher; Liam Butcher; Tiffany Butcher; Morgan Jackson-King; Billy Mitchell; Julie Perkins; Mo Harris; Patrick Trueman; Vanessa Gold; Sergeant Morris; Midwife David; Nurse Jenny; Taneshia; DI Sallinger</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00xyc9n</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00xyc9n</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5562797403888981787.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>16/01/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>It is baby Tommy's funeral and, as Kat and Alfie bid farewell to their son, a devastated Ronnie interrupts the wake with a shocking announcement. Also in HD.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>It is baby Tommy's funeral and, as Kat and Alfie bid farewell to their son, a devastated Ronnie interrupts the wake with a shocking announcement. A stunned Carol tries to silence Tiffany when she realises what her grand-daughter witnessed. Meanwhile, Roxy is displeased to discover who Jack has sold his share of the club to and, despite her best intentions, will Glenda succumb to Phil's advances once again?</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Phil Mitchell; Glenda Mitchell; Kat Moon; Alfie Moon; Charlie Slater; Mo Harris; Jean Slater; Ronnie Branning; Jack Branning; Roxy Mitchell; Greg Jessop; Tanya Branning; Zainab Masood; Masood Ahmed; Tamwar Masood; Carol Jackson; Connor Stanley; Shirley Carter; Ian Beale; Dot Branning; Edward Bishop; Bianca Butcher; Kim Fox; Liam Butcher; Tiffany Butcher; Morgan Jackson-King; Darren Miller; Jodie Gold; Poppy Meadow; Jane Beale; Whitney Dean; Ricky Butcher; Heather Trott; Max Branning; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Mercy Olubunmi; Tracey; Bushra Abbasi; Zulekha Abbasi; Vicar</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00y42nb</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00y42nb</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5565388557658661325.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>23/01/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Bianca's disappearance sends Ricky and the kids into a tailspin - but will the return of a familiar face hold the key to her whereabouts? Tamwar makes a public declaration. Also in HD.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Carol's shocking confession sets in motion a chain of events that lead to tragedy for her family. Bianca's disappearance sends Ricky and the kids into a tailspin - but will the return of a familiar face hold the key to her whereabouts? Tamwar makes a public declaration at the opening of the Argee Bhajee, much to Zainab and Masood's horror. 

	Kat stumbles across an upsetting discovery about Alfie, while Christian is overjoyed when Syed agrees to his latest proposition. Kim ropes Patrick into her latest money-making scam, and Mo decides to move house - although her new home is not too far away.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Carol Jackson; Bianca Butcher; Sonia Fowler; Max Branning; Whitney Dean; Connor Stanley; Jack Branning; Ricky Butcher; Tiffany Butcher; Liam Butcher; Morgan Jackson-King; Christian Clarke; Syed Masood; Masood Ahmed; Zainab Masood; Tamwar Masood; Afia Khan; Alfie Moon; Kat Moon; Mo Harris; Julie Perkins; Kim Fox; Patrick Trueman; Denise Johnson; Roxy Mitchell; Glenda Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Phil Mitchell; Ian Beale; Bobby Beale; Tanya Branning; Greg Jessop; Darren Miller; Mrs Dibley; Nurse Kennedy; DS Marsh</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00yd04m</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00yd04m</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5567986153879284861.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>30/01/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>On finding himself in a unique position of power, Ian goes to unspeakable lengths to punish Phil for a lifetime of torture. Christian and Syed have an explosive falling-out. Also in HD.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>On finding himself in a unique position of power, Ian goes to unspeakable lengths to punish Phil for a lifetime of torture. Christian and Syed have an explosive falling-out when Roxy makes an enormous gesture for her best friend. Meanwhile, Whitney and Carol's relationship deteriorates rapidly in the aftermath of Bianca's imprisonment and Ryan is stunned when Janine returns to the Square. Max finds himself out in the cold as Tanya and Greg move into their new home.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Shirley Carter; Phil Mitchell; Ben Mitchell; Ian Beale; Jane Beale; Glenda Mitchell; Roxy Mitchell; Ronnie Branning; Christian Clarke; Syed Masood; Whitney Dean; Janine Malloy; Ryan Malloy; Darren Miller; Jodie Gold; Jack Branning; Max Branning; Tanya Branning; Heather Trott; Patrick Trueman; Billy Mitchell; Carol Jackson; Ricky Butcher; Zainab Masood; Masood Ahmed; Tamwar Masood; Vanessa Gold; Lauren Branning; Abi Branning; Mo Harris; Greg Jessop; Alfie Moon; Jay Brown; Liam Butcher; Morgan Jackson-King; Bobby Beale; Ms Underwood; Connor Stanley; Paramedic 1; Paramedic 2; Boy</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00yltl5</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00yltl5</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5570581173123726063.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>06/02/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Phil is forced to take drastic action when Glenda threatens to expose him at his engagement party - but whose side will Ian pick? Roxy is left reeling by a shocking revelation.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Phil is forced to take drastic action when Glenda threatens to expose him at his engagement party - but whose side will Ian pick? Darren faces extreme pressure when his plan to sabotage the car lot relaunch backfires and Kat and Alfie draw closer, only to be interrupted by an unwelcome visitor. Vanessa is furious to hear Jodie's life-changing news and Roxy is left reeling by a shocking revelation.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Roxy Mitchell; Phil Mitchell; Glenda Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Jay Brown; Ben Mitchell; Ian Beale; Michael Moon; Kat Moon; Alfie Moon; Jack Branning; Max Branning; Vanessa Gold; Jodie Gold; Darren Miller; Abi Branning; Lauren Branning; Tamwar Masood; Janine Malloy; Whitney Dean; Ryan Malloy; Ricky Butcher; Patrick Trueman; Kim Fox; Denise Johnson; Jane Beale; Billy Mitchell; Julie Perkins; Ronnie Branning; Mo Harris; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Mercy Olubunmi; David Priors; Market Inspector; Dr Griffiths; Triage Nurse</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00yrjlb</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00yrjlb</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5573158153497130603.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>13/02/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Whitney makes a dangerous decision and Janine has a narrow escape. A broken Kat turns on Alfie, and Zainab and Masood are forced to swallow their pride and meet with Yusef. Also in HD.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Whitney makes a dangerous decision and Janine has a narrow escape when a night at the R&amp;R spirals out of control. A broken Kat turns on Alfie when her grief threatens to overwhelm her - but will they be able to forgive one another before it's too late? Dot is horrified when she catches Heather stealing from her while Ronnie goes to desperate lengths in an attempt to find out more about Michael. Zainab and Masood are forced to swallow their pride and meet with Yusef - with an unexpected outcome.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Roxy Mitchell; Jack Branning; Ronnie Branning; Glenda Mitchell; Kat Moon; Alfie Moon; Michael Moon; Max Branning; Darren Miller; Jodie Gold; Dot Branning; Heather Trott; Kim Fox; Denise Johnson; Jane Beale; Tanya Branning; Julie Perkins; Mo Harris; Tamwar Masood; Afia Khan; Masood Ahmed; Zainab Masood; Yusef Khan; Janine Malloy; Whitney Dean; Ryan Malloy; Patrick Trueman; Vanessa Gold; Billy Mitchell; Ricky Butcher; David Priors; Gary Dewsbury</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00ytqm3</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00ytqm3</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5573181346324726072.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>13/02/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Whitney makes a dangerous decision and Janine has a narrow escape. A broken Kat turns on Alfie, and Zainab and Masood are forced to swallow their pride and meet with Yusef.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Whitney makes a dangerous decision and Janine has a narrow escape when a night at the R&amp;R spirals out of control. A broken Kat turns on Alfie when her grief threatens to overwhelm her - but will they be able to forgive one another before it's too late? Dot is horrified when she catches Heather stealing from her while Ronnie goes to desperate lengths in an attempt to find out more about Michael. Zainab and Masood are forced to swallow their pride and meet with Yusef - with an unexpected outcome.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Roxy Mitchell; Jack Branning; Ronnie Branning; Glenda Mitchell; Kat Moon; Alfie Moon; Michael Moon; Max Branning; Darren Miller; Jodie Gold; Dot Branning; Heather Trott; Kim Fox; Denise Johnson; Jane Beale; Tanya Branning; Julie Perkins; Mo Harris; Tamwar Masood; Afia Khan; Masood Ahmed; Zainab Masood; Yusef Khan; Janine Malloy; Whitney Dean; Ryan Malloy; Patrick Trueman; Vanessa Gold; Billy Mitchell; Ricky Butcher; David Priors; Gary Dewsbury</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00z1gpn</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00z1gpn</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5575755749717756038.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>20/02/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Michael's shocking revelation leaves Jack reeling, Heather Trott faces the toughest day of her life, and Shirley returns from Portugal with some exciting news. Also in HD.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>When Jack attacks Michael for making a pass at Ronnie, Michael retaliates with a shocking revelation that leaves Jack reeling. Heather Trott faces the toughest day of her life as a desperate visit to her mother and an altercation with Carol all lead to a terrible tragedy. Shirley returns from Portugal with some exciting news and Alfie is on hand to comfort Kat when she receives some sad news about Tommy.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Heather Trott; Shirley Carter; Darren Miller; Jodie Gold; Kat Moon; Alfie Moon; Mo Harris; Dot Branning; Edward Bishop; Whitney Dean; Janine Malloy; Roxy Mitchell; Christian Clarke; Syed Masood; Glenda Mitchell; Ronnie Branning; Jack Branning; Michael Moon; Max Branning; Billy Mitchell; Julie Perkins; Jay Mitchell; Ricky Butcher; Carol Jackson; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Tamwar Masood; Ryan Malloy; Patrick Trueman; Jane Beale; Doris Hounslow; Homeless Guy; Jenny Ashwood; Paramedic; Delivery Guy; Counsellor</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00z63w1</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00z63w1</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5578354634428568091.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>27/02/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Spiralling out of control, Whitney has to turn to a new friend for help after burning all her bridges in Walford. Zainab and Masood are rocked by Albert Square's new resident. Also in HD.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Spiralling out of control, Whitney has to turn to a new friend for help after burning all her bridges in Walford. Zainab and Masood are rocked by Albert Square's new resident, and Alfie is on a mission to get through to Kat.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Whitney Dean; Rob Grayson; Lauren Branning; Tanya Branning; Max Branning; Masood Ahmed; Zainab Masood; Tamwar Masood; Afia Khan; Yusef Khan; Denise Johnson; Ricky Butcher; Carol Jackson; Julie Perkins; Heather Trott; Patrick Trueman; Shirley Carter; Kim Fox; Janine Malloy; Dot Branning; Alfie Moon; Kat Moon; Mo Harris; Mercy Olubunmi; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Roxy Mitchell; Glenda Mitchell; Jodie Gold; Darren Miller; Billy Mitchell; Ian Beale; Liam Butcher; Tiffany Butcher; Morgan Jackson-King; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Roxy Mitchell; Glenda Mitchell; Jodie Gold; Darren Miller; Billy Mitchell; Ian Beale; Liam Butcher; Tiffany Butcher; Morgan Jackson-King; Seb Parker; David Priors; Nick Meth</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00zf8z5</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00zf8z5</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5580958673100135189.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>06/03/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Yusef's presence in the Square proves too much for Zainab and Masood to bear, Shirley is thrilled when Phil returns and Ronnie's lies continue to spiral. Jay wins a new admirer. Also in HD.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Yusef's presence in the Square proves too much for Zainab and Masood to bear but Tamwar and Afia remain determined to reunite their warring families. Shirley is thrilled when Phil returns but it's not long before a scorned Glenda makes a revelation which threatens to tear the Mitchells apart. Ronnie's lies continue to spiral whilst Kat and Alfie find themselves growing closer thanks to an unexpected visitor. An oblivious Jay wins a new admirer.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Ben Mitchell; Phil Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Glenda Mitchell; Ian Beale; Jane Beale; Ronnie Branning; Roxy Mitchell; Yusef Khan; Zainab Masood; Masood Ahmed; Tamwar Masood; Afia Khan; Denise Johnson; Kim Fox; Patrick Trueman; Kat Moon; Alfie Moon; Mo Harris; Carol Jackson; Ricky Butcher; Janine Malloy; Dot Branning; Syed Masood; Heather Trott; Jack Branning; Jay Mitchell; Abi Branning; Martina Quinn; Shenice Quinn; Reporter</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00zm6fc</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00zm6fc</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5583549826869814370.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>13/03/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Revelations ricochet across the Square, forcing Phil, Shirley, Ian and Jane to rake over their relationships in heartbreaking detail - will anyone survive Glenda's vicious legacy? Also in HD.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Revelations ricochet across the Square, forcing Phil, Shirley, Ian and Jane to rake over their relationships in heartbreaking detail - will either couple survive Glenda's poisonous legacy? 

	Kat and Alfie do their best to support a vulnerable Shenice, while Abi's crush on Jay leaves her humiliated. Dot is touched by Edward's kindness.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Shirley Carter; Phil Mitchell; Ben Mitchell; Jay Mitchell; Billy Mitchell; Julie Perkins; Heather Trott; Jane Beale; Ian Beale; Kat Moon; Alfie Moon; Abi Branning; Max Branning; Tanya Branning; Mo Harris; Martina Quinn; Shenice Quinn; Tiffany Butcher; Liam Butcher; Morgan Jackson-King; Glenda Mitchell; Ronnie Branning; Jack Branning; Roxy Mitchell; Kim Fox; Denise Fox; Dot Branning; Edward Bishop; Registrar</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00zp5vg</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00zp5vg</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5583573019697407629.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>13/03/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Revelations ricochet across the Square, forcing Phil, Shirley, Ian and Jane to rake over their relationships in heartbreaking detail - will anyone survive Glenda's vicious legacy?</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Revelations ricochet across the Square, forcing Phil, Shirley, Ian and Jane to rake over their relationships in heartbreaking detail - will either couple survive Glenda's poisonous legacy? 

	Kat and Alfie do their best to support a vulnerable Shenice, while Abi's crush on Jay leaves her humiliated. Dot is touched by Edward's kindness.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Shirley Carter; Phil Mitchell; Ben Mitchell; Jay Mitchell; Billy Mitchell; Julie Perkins; Heather Trott; Jane Beale; Ian Beale; Kat Moon; Alfie Moon; Abi Branning; Max Branning; Tanya Branning; Mo Harris; Martina Quinn; Shenice Quinn; Tiffany Butcher; Liam Butcher; Morgan Jackson-King; Glenda Mitchell; Ronnie Branning; Jack Branning; Roxy Mitchell; Kim Fox; Denise Fox; Dot Branning; Edward Bishop; Registrar</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b00zwcw2</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00zwcw2</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5586146134600246572.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>20/03/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Janine and Lauren finally track down Whitney, but are horrified when they discover what has happened to her - can they convince her to leave Rob? Carol lays the past to rest. Also in HD.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Janine and Lauren finally track down Whitney, but are horrified when they discover what has happened to her - will they be able to convince her to leave Rob? 

	Carol finally lays the past to rest after a visit to Connor, and Abi is thrilled after a romantic renedezvous with Jay. Fat Boy reveals a heartbreaking secret to Mercy, and Jodie has a close call when she leaves George with Heather.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Whitney Dean; Rob Grayson; Lauren Branning; Janine Malloy; Ricky Butcher; Carol Jackson; Connor Stanley; Max Branning; Abi Branning; Jay Mitchell; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Mercy Olubunmi; Vanessa Gold; Darren Miller; Jodie Gold; Heather Trott; Dot Branning; Mo Harris; Liam Butcher; Tiffany Dean; Morgan Jackson-King; Mr Lister; Chris; Chloe</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b0102rmt</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b0102rmt</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5588757904212947266.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>27/03/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Jodie's babysitting for George goes horribly wrong, Max warns off Abi, Roxy goes all-out to impress at the Boxing Gym opening and Edward's good intentions towards Dot backfire.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Darren is forced into a life-changing decision when Jodie's attempt at babysitting George goes horribly wrong. 

	Max plays dirty in an attempt to warn Abi off Jay while Tanya finds an unlikely ally in Syed when she makes a stand at the salon. 

	Roxy goes all-out to impress at the opening of the Boxing Gym unaware that Michael has gone missing. 

	Edward is devastated when his good intentions towards Dot backfire and a desperate Ronnie turns to Phil in her hour of need.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Kat Moon; Alfie Moon; Michael Moon; Jack Branning; Roxy Mitchell; Christian Clarke; Ronnie Branning; Phil Mitchell; Tanya Branning; Jane Beale; Kim Fox; Ian Beale; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Dot Branning; Edward Bishop; Carol Jackson; Billy Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Jay Mitchell; Abi Branning; Max Branning; Vanessa Gold; Darren Miller; Heather Trott; Patrick Walker; Syed Masood; Jodie Gold; Lauren Branning; greg Jessop; Ricky Butcher; Dr Yusef Khan; Morgan Jackson-King; Janine Malloy; Liam Butcher; Mercy Olubunmi; Jools; Dr Will; Paramedic</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b010945x</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b010945x</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5591311691767122873.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>03/04/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>An old face returns to help Kat; Dot has a terrifying accident, forcing Carol to take charge; and Roxy is determined to help Ronnie, but can she employ a reluctant Jack's help? Also in HD.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>An old face returns to help Kat; Dot has a terrifying accident, forcing Carol to take charge; and Roxy is determined to help Ronnie, but can she employ a reluctant Jack's help?</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Jack Branning; Ronnie Branning; Roxy Mitchell; Sal Martin; Michael Moon; Tanya Branning; Syed Masood; Christian Clarke; Masood Ahmed; Zainab Masood; Tamwar Masood; Afia Khan; Dr Yusef Khan; Alfie Moon; Kat Moon; Jean Slater; Dot Branning; Carol Jackson; Max Branning; Vanessa Gold; Jodie Gold; Lauren Branning; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Mercy Olubunmi; Heather Trott; Shirley Carter; Phil Mitchell; Billy Mitchell; Ricky Butcher; Mo Harris; Jane Beale; Greg Jessop; Ashley Chubb; Zulekha Abbasi; Edward Bishop</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b010hb78</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b010hb78</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5593907999501752147.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>10/04/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>A newly emboldened Jack vows to fight for his marriage - but will his declarations of love be enough to entice Ronnie back to the Square?</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>A newly emboldened Jack vows to fight for his marriage - but will his declarations of love be enough to entice Ronnie back to the Square? When tragedy strikes Tamwar and Afia's engagement party, guilt and deception lead Zainab to a place she never thought she'd visit again. Meanwhile, Heather's search for online love has unexpected results and Lydia proves herself to be more than a match for Janine. Lauren is horrified when an unexpected encounter leads to the truth about Whitney's whereabouts.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Whitney Dean; Lauren Branning; Masood Ahmed; Zainab Masood; Tamwar Masood; Afia Masood; Dr Yusef Khan; Syed Masood; Christian Clarke; Ian Beale; Jane Beale; Tanya Branning; Greg Jessop; Max Branning; Abi Branning; Jay Mitchell; Ricky Butcher; Pat Evans; Carol Jackson; Janine Malloy; Lydia Simmonds; Heather Trott; Shirley Carter; Ben Mitchell; Kim Fox; Denise Fox; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Mercy Olubunmi; Ashley Chubb; Darren Miller; Jodie Gold; Zulekha Abbasi; Jean Slater; Dot Branning; Ronnie Branning; Jack Branning; Roxy Mitchell; Michael Moon; Kat Moon; Alfie Moon; Liam Butcher; Tiffany Butcher; Morgan Jackson-King; Sal Martin; Seb Parker; Andy; PC Lance; Tammy; DC Newton</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b010p0rc</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b010p0rc</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5596522346094827581.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>17/04/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Tragedy strikes on the day of Greg and Tanya's wedding. Ronnie leaves a trail of devastation in her wake. Max is incensed when he discovers the truth about Abi and Jay.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Tragedy strikes on the day of Greg and Tanya's wedding - will the pair exchange vows before events take over? 

	A distraught Ronnie makes a life-changing decision leaving a trail of devastation in her wake. 

	A vulnerable Whitney seeks solace in unexpected arms upon her return to the Square. 

	Zainab battles with her pride as she begs friends and neighbours for financial support much to Masood's horror and Max is incensed when he discovers the truth about Abi and Jay.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Kat Moon; Ronnie Branning; Jack Branning; Alfie Moon; Tanya Jessop; Max Branning; Greg Jessop; Abi Branning; Lauren Branning; Vanessa Gold; Roxy Mitchell; Michael Moon; Ian Beale; Jane Beale; Jean Slater; Dot Branning; Whitney Dean; Carol Jackson; Ricky Butcher; Pat Evans; Janine Malloy; Liam Butcher; Tiffany Butcher; Morgan Jackson-King; Darren Miller; Jodie Gold; hil Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Heather Trott; Ben Mitchell; Jay Mitchell; Billy Mitchell; Zainab Masood; Masood Ahmed; Tamwar Masood; Mo Harris; Kim Fox; Denise Fox; Cora Cross; Rainie Cross; Lydia Simmonds; Pete; Stripper; Bridal Shop Owner; Reverend Jonathan Bryars; Receptionist; Doctor; Midwife Diane</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b010vw6m</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b010vw6m</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5599095461001863347.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>24/04/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Kat and Alfie are left reeling by shocking news, while an increasingly unstable Ronnie attempts to explain her actions. Tensions reach boiling point between Michael and Jack.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Kat and Alfie are left reeling by shocking news, while an increasingly unstable Ronnie attempts to explain her actions.

	Tensions reach boiling point between Michael and Jack as they struggle to deal with the fallout of recent events.

	Whitney finds herself further alienated from her family after becoming front page news, whilst Rainie's presence on the Square leaves Max and Phil questioning her motives.

	A desperate Masood turns to Phil in his hour of need, and Jay learns the identity of Heather's online admirer.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Jack Branning; Alfie Moon; Whitney Dean; Dot Branning; Carol Jackson; Ricky Butcher; Liam Butcher; Tiffany Butcher; Morgan Jackson-King; Janine Malloy; Lydia Simmonds; Pat Evans; Heather Trott; Shirley Carter; Phil Mitchell; Ben Mitchell; Jay Mitchell; Michael Moon; Kat Moon; Charlie Slater; Masood Ahmed; Zainab Masood; Dr Yusef Khan; Patrick Trueman; Max Branning; Abi Branning; Rainie Cross; Roxy Mitchell; Billy Mitchell; Ashley Chubb; Mercy Olubunmi; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Ian Beale; Mo Harris; Jean Slater; Ronnie Branning; Tanya Jessop; Greg Jessop; Lauren Branning; Mr Lister; Nathan Clayton; Seb Parker; Steve Merryman; Forensic Medical Examiner; Social Worker; Dr Niall Heaton; PC Cyril Hickey</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b01102zh</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b01102zh</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5601700788159427420.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>01/05/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Masood follows Zainab to a secret rendezvous and is stunned to see who she is meeting, while Tamwar and Afia prepare to come clean about their secret marriage.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Masood follows Zainab to a secret rendezvous and is stunned to see who she is meeting, while Tamwar and Afia prepare to come clean about their secret marriage. 

	Ryan is horrified to discover the truth about Whitney, while Fat Boy resorts to desperate measures to save Mercy. 

	Heather is delighted when her online boyfriend finally wants to meet face-to-face, and Alfie moots the idea of a christening for Tommy, much to Kat's displeasure.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Grace Olubunmi; Dot Branning; Tiffany Butcher; Masood Ahmed; Zainab Masood; Dr Yusef Khan; Tamwar Masood; Afia Masood; Syed Masood; Christian Clarke; Alfie Moon; Kat Moon; Jack Branning; Roxy Mitchell; Max Branning; Vanessa Gold; Abi Branning; Ben Mitchell; Jay Mitchell; Nathan; Lydia Simmonds; Mo Harris; Jean Slater; Jane Beale; Ian Beale; Ryan Malloy; Denise Fox; Kim Fox; Heather Trott; Julie Perkins; Janine Malloy; Edward Bishop; Shirley Carter; Phil Mitchell</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b01177px</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b01177px</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5604298384384246058.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>08/05/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Roxy is left reeling when her attempts to help Ronnie are thrown back in her face, while Michael finds himself out of his depth as Jack continues to spiral out of control.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Roxy is left reeling when her attempts to help Ronnie are thrown back in her face, while Michael finds himself out of his depth as a volatile Jack continues to spiral out of control. 

	Heather's grief over Kevin leads to a terrible altercation with Denise. Vanessa feels sidelined as Max anxiously awaits Tanya's return from honeymoon and Carol is horrified when Dot has another dangerous near-miss at home. 

	Meanwhile, battle commences over in the Beale household as Jane and Ian declare war.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Jack Branning; Rainie Cross; Max Branning; Vanessa Gold; Carol Jackson; Dot Branning; Ian Beale; Jane Beale; Alfie Moon; Kat Moon; Julie Perkins; Billy Mitchell; Phil Mitchell; Jodie Gold; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Tanya Jessop; Greg Jessop; Abi Branning; Bobby Beale; Janine Malloy; Lydia Simmonds; Pat Evans; Ricky Butcher; Mo Harris; Jean Slater; Denise Fox; Edward Bishop; Heather Trott; Ben Mitchell; Jay Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Darren Miller; Michael Moon; Roxy Mitchell; Ronnie Branning; Christian Clarke; Syed Masood; Zainab Masood; Masood Ahmed; Lauren Branning; Whitney Dean; Ryan Malloy; Grace Olubunmi; Kev</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b011cjcm</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b011cjcm</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5606895980600673684.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>15/05/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Jack lashes out when Max and Carol's decision to help their brother goes wrong. Heather is left devastated by Ben's betrayal and Fat Boy rallies the community to support Mercy. Also in HD.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Jack lashes out when Max and Carol's decision to help their brother goes terribly wrong. Kim accidentally reveals a bit too much about Denise's love life to Masood while Christian and Alfie's attempt to broker peace between Ian and Jane backfires. 

	Heather is left devastated by Ben's betrayal while a disgusted Shirley demands Phil take action to punish his son. 

	Fat Boy rallies the community to support Mercy's immigration appeal.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Ronnie Branning; Roxy Mitchell; Masood Ahmed; Jane Beale; Dr Yusef Khan; Zainab Masood; Denise Fox; Kim Fox; Ian Beale; Phil Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Heather Trott; Ben Mitchell; Jay Mitchell; Abi Branning; Kat Moon; Alfie Moon; Max Branning; Vanessa Gold; Jack Branning; Tanya Jessop; Rainie Cross; Michael Moon; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Darren Miller; Jodie Gold; Afia Masood; Tamwar Masood; Carol Jackson; Dot Branning; Edward Bishop; Christian Clarke; Greg Jessop; Billy Mitchell; Julie Perkins; Imam Ali; Nathan</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b011lj3h</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b011lj3h</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5609497442296058297.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>22/05/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Alfie and Kat receive shocking news from the police. Ronnie's release sends shockwaves across the Square. Ian's underhand tactics lead Jane to make a heartbreaking decision.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Alfie and Kat's happiness at Tommy's christening is under threat when they receive shocking news from the police.

	Ronnie's release sends shockwaves across the Square - how will Jack react to her unexpected return?

	Ian's underhand tactics lead Jane to make a heartbreaking decision, while Masood tries desperately to salvage his relationship with Zainab in the wake of recent revelations.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Ronnie Branning; Jack Branning; Ian Beale; Jane Beale; Bobby Beale; Masood Ahmed; Zainab Masood; Dr Yusef Khan; Afia Masood; Tamwar Masood; Christian Clarke; Syed Masood; Alfie Moon; Kat Moon; Roxy Mitchell; Carol Jackson; Dot Branning; Edward Bishop; Tanya Jessop; Billy Mitchell; Denise Fox; Kim Fox; Phil Mitchell; Michael Moon; Jean Slater; Mo Harris; Jay Mitchell; Abi Branning; Lauren Branning; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Elaine; Vicar; Family Liaison Officer</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b011r46z</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b011r46z</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5612131116237773404.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>29/05/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Dot faces an impossible decision as the reality of being Jim's full-time carer takes it toll, while Rainie deliberately causes mischief between Ronnie and Jack. Also in HD.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Dot faces an impossible decision as the reality of being Jim's full-time carer takes it toll, while Carol and Max are heartbroken to witness their dad's decline. Rainie deliberately causes mischief between Ronnie and Jack when she sees they're back together. 

	Christian makes a momentous decision when Syed's attempts to heal Masood and Zainab's rift leaves him out in the cold, while Mercy faces a wobble ahead of her wedding. Patrick faces a nasty shock on his return home from holiday, and Denise surprises Kim on her birthday.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Syed Masood; Christian Clarke; Masood Ahmed; Zainab Masood; Tamwar Masood; Dr Yusef Khan; Afia Masood; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Lauren Branning; Jodie Gold; Darren Miller; Whitney Dean; Grace Olubunmi; Pat Evans; Ricky Butcher; Lydia Simmonds; Janine Malloy; Denise Fox; Kim Fox; Patrick Trueman; Jim Branning; Jim Branning; Edward Bishop; Carol Jackson; Max Branning; Jack Branning; Ronnie Branning; Michael Moon; Kat Moon; Alfie Moon; Rainie Cross; Tanya Jessop; Greg Jessop; Heather Trott; Billy Mitchell; Mo Harris; Ian Beale; Roxy Mitchell; Mr Lister</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b011w96v</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b011w96v</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5614688769262543432.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>05/06/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Yusef fears for his life when a dramatic showdown with Masood threatens to spiral out of control, while Zainab is horrified when she discovers Syed and Christian's secret. Also in HD.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Yusef fears for his life when a dramatic showdown with Masood threatens to spiral out of control, while Zainab is horrified when she discovers Syed and Christian's secret. 

	Shirley is left reeling when Phil's pent-up anger finally explodes, while Carol lays down the law when Ricky reveals the truth about his recent job interview. 

	Meanwhile, Kat and Alfie are given an unwelcome reminder of recent events, and Roxy gives Michael one last chance to make their relationship work.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Eddie Moon; Alfie Moon; Kat Moon; Michael Moon; Roxy Mitchell; Phil Mitchell; Rainie Cross; Shirley Carter; Masood Ahmed; Zainab Masood; Dr Yusef Khan; Denise Fox; Tamwar Masood; Afia Masood; Whitney Dean; Lauren Branning; Ryan Malloy; Ricky Butcher; Janine Malloy; Kim Fox; Jay Mitchell; Billy Mitchell; Julie Perkins; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Mercy Chubb; Grace Olubunmi; Carol Jackson; Syed Masood; Christian Clarke; Jodie Gold; Darren Miller; Dot Branning; Tiffany Butcher; Morgan Jackson-King; Mr Lister</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b012403p</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b012403p</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5619885250193978504.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>19/06/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Janine and Lydia reach out to one another during a dark night of the soul, before heartbreaking tragedy tears them apart. And tensions between Max and Tanya reach boiling point. Also in HD.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Janine and Lydia reach out to one another during a dark night of the soul, before heartbreaking tragedy tears them apart. Tensions between Max and Tanya reach boiling point at Max and Vanessa's engagement party, while Christian's jealousy causes an explosive argument at his birthday drinks. 

	Zainab and Denise lock horns over wedding plans, while the rivalry between Tam and Afia's camps grows over the mehndi dances. Fat Boy fights for Mercy at the immigration court, and Carol and Eddie come to blows over Liam.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Max Branning; Tanya Jessop; Vanessa Gold; Greg Jessop; Ronnie Branning; Jack Branning; Jodie Gold; Darren Miller; Abi Branning; Jay Mitchell; Lauren Branning; Carol Jackson; Dot Branning; Tamwar Masood; Afia Masood; Masood Ahmed; Zainab Masood; Dr Yusef Khan; Denise Fox; Christian Clarke; Syed Masood; Billy Mitchell; Julie Perkins; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Mercy Chubb; Rainie Cross; Janine Malloy; Pat Evans; Ryan Malloy; Roxy Mitchell; Eddie Moon; Ian Beale; Liam Butcher; Michael Moon; Grace Olubunmi; Kim Fox; Patrick Trueman; Lydia Simmonds; Morgan Jackson-King; Tiffany Butcher; Catherine Kane; Danny</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b012c3lr</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b012c3lr</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5622512481693138548.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>26/06/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Masood's desperate attempt to halt Tam and Afia's wedding is dealt a crushing blow, but a bigger shock lies in store for Zainab when Yusef makes an unexpected confession.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Masood's desperate attempt to halt Tam and Afia's wedding is dealt a crushing blow, but a bigger shock lies in store for Zainab when Yusef makes an unexpected confession. 

	Shirley is incensed to discover Phil and Rainie's secret, while Carol and Eddie's relationship takes a heartwarming turn. A guilty Tanya issues Max with a warning when he causes mischief at a family gathering, and Billy has a surprise announcement for Julie.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Dr Yusef Khan; Zainab Masood; Masood Ahmed; Tamwar Masood; Afia Masood; Syed Masood; Christian Clarke; Denise Fox; Kim Fox; Patrick Trueman; Max Branning; Tanya Jessop; Greg Jessop; Phil Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Rainie Cross; Jay Mitchell; Billy Mitchell; Julie Perkins; Jodie Gold; Darren Miller; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Mercy Chubb; Lauren Branning; Eddie Moon; Carol Jackson; Liam Butcher; Michael Moon; Roxy Mitchell; Alfie Moon; Ian Beale; Bobby Beale; Zulekha Abbasi; Shameem; Tariq</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b0124qmw</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b0124qmw</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5622520212630075710.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>26/06/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Masood's desperate attempt to halt Tam and Afia's wedding is dealt a crushing blow, but a bigger shock lies in store for Zainab when Yusef makes an unexpected confession. Also in HD.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Masood's desperate attempt to halt Tam and Afia's wedding is dealt a crushing blow, but a bigger shock lies in store for Zainab when Yusef makes an unexpected confession. 

	Shirley is incensed to discover Phil and Rainie's secret, while Carol and Eddie's relationship takes a heartwarming turn. A guilty Tanya issues Max with a warning when he causes mischief at a family gathering, and Billy has a surprise announcement for Julie.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Dr Yusef Khan; Zainab Masood; Masood Ahmed; Tamwar Masood; Afia Masood; Syed Masood; Christian Clarke; Denise Fox; Kim Fox; Patrick Trueman; Max Branning; Tanya Jessop; Greg Jessop; Phil Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Rainie Cross; Jay Mitchell; Billy Mitchell; Julie Perkins; Jodie Gold; Darren Miller; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Mercy Chubb; Lauren Branning; Eddie Moon; Carol Jackson; Liam Butcher; Michael Moon; Roxy Mitchell; Alfie Moon; Ian Beale; Bobby Beale; Zulekha Abbasi; Shameem; Tariq</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b012gh70</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b012gh70</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5625094616031493847.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>03/07/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Tyler Moon's surprise arrival in Walford brings chaos to the Vic and has upsetting consequences for Eddie. Carol and Ian are aghast when Shirley lays down the law.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Tyler Moon's surprise arrival in Walford brings chaos to the Vic and has upsetting consequences for Eddie. Carol and Ian are aghast when Shirley lays down the law as the cafe's new owner, while Tam and Afia resolve to legalise their marriage alone, much to Yusef's displeasure. Michael begins to manipulate Jack and Roxy as his obsession with Ronnie reaches new heights, and Kat grows increasingly paranoid ahead of Ronnie's sentencing. Janine receives evidence that she hopes will prove her innocence over Lydia's death. Max and Tanya have a near miss when their passion boils over at the car lot and Lauren finds herself developing an unexpected crush.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Roxy Mitchell; Michael Moon; Ronnie Branning; Jack Branning; Kat Moon; Alfie Moon; Eddie Moon; Carol Jackson; Whitney Dean; Lauren Branning; Ryan Malloy; Janine Malloy; Billy Mitchell; Julie Perkins; Ricky Butcher; Pat Evans; Ian Beale; Mo Harris; Kim Fox; Max Branning; Tanya Jessop; Greg Jessop; Phil Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Rainie Cross; Heather Trott; Jay Mitchell; Darren Miller; Jodie Gold; Poppy Meadow; Tyler Moon; Christian Clarke; Syed Masood; Tamwar Masood; Afia Masood; Masood Ahmed; Zainab Masood; Dr Yusef Khan; Liam Butcher; Tiffany Butcher; Morgan Jackson-King; Catherine Kane</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b012m64b</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b012m64b</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5627669019428687932.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>10/07/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Ronnie is stunned when Michael reveals his true intentions, and Roxy and Jack contemplate their lives without her. Janine struggles with her grief on the day of Lydia's funeral.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Ronnie is stunned when Michael finally reveals his true intentions, and Roxy and Jack are left struggling as they contemplate their lives without her. Janine struggles with her grief on the day of Lydia's funeral, while Pat is thrown by the return of a face from her past.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Janine Malloy; Pat Evans; Ricky Butcher; Ian Beale; Julie Perkins; Billy Mitchell; Phil Mitchell; Alfie Moon; Kat Moon; Michael Moon; Jack Branning; Ronnie Branning; Roxy Mitchell; Max Branning; Tanya Jessop; Lauren Branning; Eddie Moon; Tyler Moon; Mercy Chubb; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Whitney Dean; Jodie Gold; Poppy Meadow; Abi Branning; Jay Mitchell; Ryan Malloy; Vanessa Gold; Greg Jessop; Carol Jackson; Dot Branning; Kim Fox; Shirley Carter; Jean Slater; Judge; Mrs Bartlett; Catherine Kane; Philip Granger QC; Norman Simmonds</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b012kpsp</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b012kpsp</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5627715405071292252.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>10/07/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Michael carries out his final, devastating act of revenge against Ronnie on the day of her sentencing - but can she convince Roxy of her innocence before it is too late? Also in HD.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Michael carries out his final, devastating act of revenge against Ronnie on the day of her sentencing - but can she convince Roxy of her innocence before it is too late? Janine struggles with her grief on the day of Lydia's funeral, while Pat is thrown by the return of a face from her past. Max and Tanya's illicit relationship is exposed by someone unexpected, while Lauren makes an ill-advised attempt to seduce Ryan.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Janine Malloy; Pat Evans; Ricky Butcher; Ian Beale; Julie Perkins; Billy Mitchell; Phil Mitchell; Alfie Moon; Kat Moon; Michael Moon; Jack Branning; Ronnie Branning; Roxy Mitchell; Max Branning; Tanya Jessop; Lauren Branning; Eddie Moon; Tyler Moon; Mercy Chubb; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Whitney Dean; Jodie Gold; Poppy Meadow; Abi Branning; Jay Mitchell; Ryan Malloy; Vanessa Gold; Greg Jessop; Carol Jackson; Dot Branning; Kim Fox; Shirley Carter; Jean Slater; Judge; Mrs Bartlett; Catherine Kane; Philip Granger QC; Norman Simmonds</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b012sqgr</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b012sqgr</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5630291096962899987.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>17/07/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Billy and Julie receive heartbreaking news when they finally pay a visit to their son. A devastated Mercy decides to return to Nigeria in secret.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Billy and Julie receive heartbreaking news when they finally pay a visit to their son. A devastated Mercy decides to return to Nigeria in secret - but can Dot warn Fat Boy before it's too late? Christian forces Zainab into an emotional showdown over his adoption plans, while Syed reaches a momentous decision about their future. Tam and Afia find themselves homeless on their return from honeymoon, while Janine takes pleasure in rubbing her new-found wealth in everyone's faces.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Billy Mitchell; Julie Perkins; Lola Pearce; Syed Masood; Christian Clarke; Roxy Mitchell; Janine Malloy; Pat Evans; Ricky Butcher; Tanya Jessop; Max Branning; Rainie Cross; Greg Jessop; Ian Beale; Bobby Beale; Denise Fox; Zainab Masood; Afia Masood; Tamwar Masood; Masood Ahmed; Dr Yusef Khan; Heather Trott; Phil Mitchell; Jay Mitchell; Abi Branning; Lauren Branning; Ryan Malloy; Kim Fox; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Mercy Chubb; Grace Olubunmi; Dot Branning; Kat Moon; Alfie Moon; Eddie Moon; Jean Slater; Tyler Moon; Jodie Gold; Darren Miller; Poppy Meadow; Liam Butcher; Tiffany Butcher; Morgan Jackson-King; Mr Lister; Paul</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b012y1q5</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b012y1q5</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5632877096771821968.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>24/07/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>There are fireworks aplenty when Janine throws a millionaire's party for the Square's residents with a surprise for Ricky. Greg and Lauren make a shocking discovery about Tanya.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>There are fireworks aplenty when Janine throws a millionaire's party for the Square's residents with a special surprise for Ricky. Greg and Lauren make a shocking discovery about Tanya, while a suspicious Vanessa resolves to deal with her growing doubts about Max. Lola causes mischief during Abi and Jay's romantic evening, Carol rumbles Liam's secret and Eddie receives a worrying call. Dot takes in a new lodger and Ian makes a fool of himself at Bobby's birthday bash.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Tanya Jessop; Vanessa Gold; Max Branning; Lauren Branning; Abi Branning; Greg Jessop; Rainie Cross; Ryan Malloy; Ian Beale; Denise Fox; Kim Fox; Mo Harris; Carol Jackson; Eddie Moon; Tyler Moon; Jodie Gold; Poppy Meadow; Jay Mitchell; Pat Evans; Norman Simmonds; Whitney Dean; Lola Pearce; Ricky Butcher; Janine Malloy; Dot Branning; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Grace Olubunmi; Shirley Carter; Phil Mitchell; Billy Mitchell; Julie Perkins; Bobby Beale; Liam Butcher; Tiffany Butcher</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b0134nct</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b0134nct</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5635446346208291490.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>31/07/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Eddie's happiness at Anthony's arrival in Walford is shortlived when an act of vengeance against the Moons puts their business in jeopardy. Greg is frustrated when Cora moves in.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Eddie's happiness at Anthony's arrival in Walford is shortlived when an act of vengeance against the Moons puts their business in jeopardy. 

	Meanwhile Zainab finds herself unexpectedly defending Masood from Afia's barbs and Roxy is furious when she rumbles Ryan's dodgy dealings. 

	Greg is frustrated when Cora moves in and Lola delights in causing tension between Billy and Julie.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Jean Slater; Eddie Moon; Michael Moon; Tyler Moon; Anthony Moon; Jack Branning; Mo Harris; Billy Mitchell; Julie Perkins; Lola Pearce; Jay Mitchell; Abi Branning; Lauren Branning; Ryan Malloy; Rainie Cross; Tanya Jessop; Max Branning; Greg Jessop; Cora Cross; Zainab Masood; Afia Masood; Phil Mitchell; Roxy Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Dot Branning; Vanessa Gold; Janine Malloy; Liam Butcher; Mr Lister; Annie</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b013dth1</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b013dth1</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5638099347502840287.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>07/08/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Roxy resorts to drastic measures when Phil continues to muscle her out of R&amp;R. Zainab is determined to celebrate Ramadan with the whole family, unaware that Syed has a secret. Also in HD.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>An isolated Roxy resorts to drastic measures when Phil continues to muscle her out of R&amp;R. Meanwhile, Zainab is determined to celebrate Ramadan with the whole family, unaware that Syed has a secret to share. 

	Michael integrates himself further into the Moon family, much to Jack's displeasure, while Ian sinks to a new low. Lola finds herself completely out of her depth when her attempt to teach Phil a lesson backfires with terrible consequences. 

	Meanwhile, Tanya takes an emotional trip down memory lane as she returns to her childhood home.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Julie Perkins; Billy Mitchell; Lola Pearce; Tanya Jessop; Greg Jessop; Cora Cross; Max Branning; Vanessa Gold; Rainie Cross; Phil Mitchell; Jay Mitchell; Alfie Moon; Kat Moon; Jean Slater; Mo Harris; Ian Beale; Janine Malloy; Roxy Mitchell; Jack Branning; Jodie Gold; Darren Miller; Poppy Meadow; Tyler Moon; Anthony Moon; Eddie Moon; Michael Moon; Carol Jackson; Patrick Trueman; Zainab Masood; Masood Ahmed; Dr Yusef Khan; Syed Masood; Christian Clarke; Tamwar Masood; Afia Masood; Tiffany Butcher; Shenice Quinn; Liam Butcher; Bobby Beale; Jude</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b013qyyz</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b013qyyz</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5640673750900064642.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>14/08/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>It is judgement day for Max and Tanya as they finally prepare to come clean with Vanessa and Greg. However, Tanya's life is turned upside down as she receives some news of her own. Also in HD.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>It is judgement day for Max and Tanya as they finally prepare to come clean with Vanessa and Greg. However, Tanya's life is turned upside down as she receives some earth-shattering news of her own. Elsewhere, Jean is on a mission to catch Norman's eye and Darren begins to panic about funding Jodie's elaborate wedding.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Max Branning; Tanya Jessop; Lauren Branning; Abi Branning; Greg Jessop; Vanessa Gold; Cora Cross; Rainie Cross; Jodie Gold; Darren Miller; Poppy Meadow; Tamwar Masood; Dr Yusef Khan; Jean Slater; Kat Moon; Alfie Moon; Mo Harris; Norman Simmonds; Pat Evans; Patrick Trueman; Jack Branning; Eddie Moon; Tyler Moon; Anthony Moon; Michael Moon; Billy Mitchell; Jay Mitchell; Lola Pearce; Ian Beale; Carol Jackson; Annie Farnham; Mr Lister; Shenice Quinn; Tiffany Butcher</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b013yzry</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b013yzry</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5643259750708988359.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>21/08/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Vanessa spirals out of control after the affair is revealed, while Tanya's disappearance throws Abi and Lauren into a panic. Michael makes a momentous discovery. Also in HD.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Vanessa spirals out of control after the affair is revealed, while Tanya's disappearance throws Abi and Lauren into a panic. Michael makes a momentous discovery when he sneaks his way into Eddie's house, and Ian vows to mend his way after his lies about Jane are revealed. 

	A police raid at the Vic has terrible consequences, while Whitney is left distraught. Pat and Jean battle to be crowned Norman's Pearly Queen at the Fete and Fortune Day, while Dot fears the worst as she continues to suffer from crippling headaches.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Rob Grayson; Lee; Whitney Dean; Lauren Branning; Ryan Malloy; Tanya Jessop; Pat Evans; Norman Simmonds; Kat Moon; Alfie Moon; Jean Slater; Mo Harris; Carol Jackson; Eddie Moon; Anthony Moon; Tyler Moon; Michael Moon; Vanessa Gold; Jodie Gold; Darren Miller; Jack Branning; Rainie Cross; Cora Cross; Abi Branning; Janine Malloy; Ian Beale; Patrick Trueman; Zainab Masood; Syed Masood; Christian Clarke; Dr Yusef Khan; Shirley Carter; Heather Trott; Dot Branning; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Bobby Beale; Shenice Quinn; Liam Butcher; Tiffany Butcher; Nurse Roger; Police Officer; Antiques Dealer</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b0146bmq</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b0146bmq</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5645863789384750277.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>28/08/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Whitney is left paralysed with fear when Rob tracks her down wanting forgiveness. Fat Boy's decision to call on Ryan for help has terrible consequences for all concerned.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Whitney is left paralysed with fear when Rob tracks her down wanting forgiveness - will she be able to escape his clutches a second time? Fat Boy's decision to call on Ryan for help has terrible consequences for all concerned. Dot is totally thrown by her sister Rose's lavish lifestyle in Southend but soon learns she has something to hide. Heather finds herself an admirer in Southend, much to Shirley's displeasure. Denise and Patrick reach an upsetting conclusion when Kim arrives home after a night out looking the worse for wear.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Ryan Malloy; Whitney Dean; Rob Grayson; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Dot Branning; Rose; Andrew; Heather Trott; Shirley Carter; Kim Fox; Denise Fox; Patrick Trueman; Lauren Branning; Tilly; Waiter; DC Blake</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b014fnf4</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b014fnf4</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5648443346738532928.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>04/09/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Ian finds himself in a dangerous dilemma when he bumps into a face from his past, Whitney struggles to adjust to life without Ryan, and Kat keeps a secret from Alfie. Also in HD.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Ian finds himself in a dangerous dilemma when he bumps into a face from his past. Dot is aghast when Rose takes the opportunity to meet the locals of Walford in her own unique style while Whitney struggles to adjust to life without Ryan. Darren is forced to take a stand when Harry returns to Jodie's life wanting to pay for their wedding while Vanessa continues to circle Eddie at Michael's behest. Kat keeps a secret from Alfie little knowing that Shenice has stumbled on the truth. While Tanya heads to the hospital alone, Cora has a night in with Patrick, Jay and Abi with unfortunate consequences.

	If you are affected by any of the issues in this episode of EastEnders, please click on the link below for information regarding sources of help, support, and advice: http://www.bbc.co.uk/eastenders/news/news_20081104.shtml.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Kat Moon; Alfie Moon; Tanya Jessop; Cora Cross; Rainie Cross; Lauren Branning; Abi Branning; Jay Mitchell; Patrick Trueman; Eddie Moon; Carol Jackson; Michael Moon; Tyler Moon; Anthony Moon; Phil Mitchell; Janine Malloy; Pat Evans; Norman Simmonds; Jean Slater; Billy Mitchell; Lola Pearce; Ian Beale; Mandy Salter; Vanessa Gold; Jodie Gold; Darren Miller; Poppy Meadow; Jack Branning; Whitney Dean; Rose Cotton; Dot Branning; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Mo Harris; Harry Gold; Shenice Quinn; Bobby Beale; Tiffany Butcher; Morgan Butcher; Paul; Lee</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b01534s5</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b01534s5</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5653298377774130455.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>17/09/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>The Moon family spectacularly implodes as fight night finally comes to pass, and Eddie reveals a staggering secret to Michael which will change the course of their relationship.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>The Moon family spectacularly implodes as fight night finally comes to pass, Eddie reveals a staggering secret to Michael which will change the course of their relationship forever, and Darren and Jodie's wedding plans are tragically shattered, leading a heartbroken Darren to respond with nihilistic abandon. Mercy's sister Faith arrives in Walford, spreading chaos.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Eddie Moon; Michael Moon; Anthony Moon; Tyler Moon; Whitney Dean; Darren Miller; Lauren Branning; Jodie Gold; Poppy Meadow; Vanessa Gold; Jack Branning; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Tamwar Masood; Grace Olubunmi; Carol Jackson; Liam Butcher; Dr Yusef Khan; Mandy Salter; Faith Olubunmi; Heather Trott; Jay Mitchell; Ben Mitchell; Ian Beale; Pat Evans; Janine Malloy; Phil Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Zainab Masood; Rose Cotton; Rainie Cross; Bobby Beale; Sandra Halliday; Artie Stiller; Paramedic</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b015sdrj</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b015sdrj</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5658849193503292805.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>02/10/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Masood comes to a heartbreaking decision about his marriage, while Syed vows to uncover the truth. A panicked Ben attempts to contain the truth about his relationship with Duncan. Also in HD.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>In the wake of Zainab's ordeal, Masood comes to a heartbreaking decision about his marriage, while Syed vows to uncover the truth about what really happened. A panicked Ben attempts to contain the truth about his relationship with Duncan but the situation soon spirals out of control as Phil squares up to Patrick. Eddie comes clean with Anthony and Tyler about Craig while a disgruntled Kat shows Mandy who's boss on a night out on the town. Meanwhile Michael offers Vanessa a wad of cash to leave Walford for good - but will she agree to his demands?</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Eddie Moon; Vanessa Gold; Michael Moon; Tyler Moon; Whitney Dean; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Anthony Moon; Patrick Trueman; Denise Fox; Kim Fox; Phil Mitchell; Ben Mitchell; Christian Clarke; Ian Beale; Mandy Salter; Dot Branning; Masood Ahmed; Heather Trott; Alfie Moon; Kat Moon; Billy Mitchell; Jay Mitchell; Zainab Masood; Dr Yusef Khan; Tamwar Masood; Syed Masood; Tiffany Butcher; Bobby Beale</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b0162pfm</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b0162pfm</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5661437770296784835.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>09/10/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Eddie keeps his suspicions about the nature of Michael and Vanessa's relationship in check during Craig's visit, but a shock revelation changes everything. Who will Eddie believe?</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Eddie keeps his suspicions about the nature of Michael and Vanessa's relationship in check during Craig's visit, but a shock revelation changes everything. With Vanessa and Michael both pleading their innocence, whose story will Eddie believe? Phil and Patrick's feud continues to escalate with huge ramifications for the entire community, leaving Kat and Alfie out on the streets. Fat Boy comforts a devastated Whitney after Tyler reveals his knowledge of her past and Yusef takes drastic action when Zainab starts to recover her former confidence.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Ben Mitchell; Phil Mitchell; Tanya Jessop; Lauren Branning; Rainie Cross; Michael Moon; Janine Malloy; Eddie Moon; Vanessa Gold; Anthony Moon; Tyler Moon; Whitney Dean; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Ian Beale; Mandy Salter; Kat Moon; Alfie Moon; Patrick Trueman; Denise Fox; Kim Fox; Christian Clarke; Jay Mitchell; Abi Branning; Lola Pearce; Dr Yusef Khan; Zainab Masood; Heather Trott; Jodie Gold; Poppy Meadow; Jack Branning; Norman Simmonds; Liam Butcher; Gordon Bags; Kris Jennings; Sophie</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b015scds</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b015scds</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5664059847830970190.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>16/10/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Yusef's meddling pushes Zainab to breaking point. Christian and Syed's lives are turned upside down. Tyler tries to impress Whitney, and Rose harbours a secret from Dot.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Yusef's meddling pushes Zainab to breaking point, resulting in a shocking confrontation. Christian and Syed find their lives turned upside down by the arrival of an unexpected visitor with a life-changing revelation. A smitten Tyler pulls out all the stops to impress Whitney on their first official date, while Rose harbours a secret from Dot. Kat and Alfie's attempt to expose Mandy's true colours to Ian doesn't go according to plan.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Kat Moon; Alfie Moon; Whitney Dean; Tyler Moon; Syed Masood; Christian Clarke; Masood Ahmed; Tamwar Masood; Amira Masood; Zainab Masood; Dr Yusef Khan; Jean Slater; Norman Simmonds; Kim Fox; Patrick Trueman; Ian Beale; Mandy Salter; Dot Branning; Cora Cross; Rose Cotton; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Anthony Moon; Roxy Mitchell; Jack Branning; Lauren Branning; Tanya Jessop; Carol Jackson; Janine Malloy; Michael Moon; Heather Trott; Shirley Carter; Ben Mitchell; Denise Fox; Rainie Cross; Abi Branning; Mark; Sam; Siobhan</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b016k265</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b016k265</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5666648424616076521.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>23/10/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Syed faces a hard choice when his daughter Yasmin visits the Square for the first time, and Kat is horrified when an unwelcome visitor returns, threatening to expose her secret. Also in HD.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Syed faces a difficult choice when his daughter Yasmin visits the Square for the first time; will he stand by Christian, or give in to Amira's demands? 

	Kat is horrified when an unwelcome visitor returns, threatening to expose her secret, while Ian reaches a momentous decision about his life after a heart-to-heart with Alfie. 

	Pat encourages Whitney to face her fears and stand up for herself, but things take an unexpected twist when she takes Pat's advice; and Lauren's plan to support Tanya backfires.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Tyler Moon; Lauren Branning; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Whitney Dean; Ian Beale; Mandy Salter; Tanya Jessop; Greg Jessop; Ben Mitchell; Christian Clarke; Syed Masood; Amira Masood; Masood Ahmed; Tamwar Masood; Pat Evans; Norman Simmonds; Jean Slater; Alfie Moon; Kat Moon; Anthony Moon; Poppy Meadow; Jodie Gold; Carol Jackson; Jack Branning; Roxy Mitchell; Janine Malloy; Kim Fox; Abi Branning; Shenice Quinn; Mark; Sophie</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b017094b</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b017094b</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5669269213664292916.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>30/10/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>A scheming Ben exposes Syed's lies about Amira to an incredulous Christian. Michael helps Janine throw a party to launch her new business. Lola and Ben bond in an unexpected way.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>A scheming Ben exposes Syed's lies about Amira to an incredulous Christian, but will his revelation have the desired effect?

	Michael helps Janine throw a party to launch her new business, much to the displeasure of the locals.

	Pat's faith in Norman is cruelly shattered, while Lola and Ben bond in an unexpected way.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Dr Yusef Khan; Christian Clarke; Syed Masood; Amira Masood; Zainab Masood; Masood Ahmed; Tamwar Masood; Janine Malloy; Michael Moon; Billy Mitchell; Heather Trott; Ben Mitchell; Lola Pearce; Jodie Gold; Poppy Meadow; Ian Beale; Roxy Mitchell; Anthony Moon; Tyler Moon; Dot Branning; Rose Cotton; Pat Evans; Patrick Trueman; Norman Simmonds; Carol Jackson; Rainie Cross; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Whitney Dean; Lauren Branning; Shirley Carter; Reverend Stevens</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b0171w47</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b0171w47</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5671866809880718863.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>06/11/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Yusef's scheming over Yasmin's paternity test continues; Christian offers a distraught Amira a place to stay much to Syed's surprise; and Jack blames Roxy when Amy is hospitalised. Also in HD.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Yusef's scheming over Yasmin's paternity test continues but could a suspicious Masood prove to be his downfall? 

	Christian finds himself offering a distraught Amira a place to stay much to Syed's surprise. 

	A furious Jack blames Roxy when Amy is hospitalised after an accident, while Tanya has a panic attack after receiving some upsetting news. Meanwhile Dot and Rose battle for Reverend Stevens' affections and an unwitting Jodie comes between Anthony and Poppy.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Roxy Mitchell; Jack Branning; Christian Clarke; Ben Mitchell; Phil Mitchell; Jay Mitchell; Masood Ahmed; Dr Yusef Khan; Zainab Masood; Syed Masood; Amira Masood; Qadim Shah; Tamwar Masood; Dot Branning; Rose Cotton; Reverend Stevens; Tanya Jessop; Lauren Branning; Whitney Dean; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Tyler Moon; Anthony Moon; Jodie Gold; Poppy Meadow; Janine Butcher; Michael Moon; Rainie Cross; Patrick Trueman; Denise Fox; Kim Fox; Carol Jackson; Shirley Carter; Heather Trott; Ian Beale; Lola Pearce; Abi Branning; Liam Butcher; Sam; Bev Gregory; Dr Clements</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b017kg8j</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b017kg8j</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5674481156477994816.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>13/11/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Ben's heartbreak rapidly transforms into fury when Christian gently rejects his advances. Amira is horrified to witness the true extent of Yusef's manipulation of Zainab.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Ben's heartbreak rapidly transforms into fury when Christian gently rejects his advances, leading to a shocking allegation. As a raging Phil seeks retribution, will Ben have the courage to admit his deceit before the situation spirals out of control?

	Amira is horrified to witness the true extent of Yusef's manipulation of Zainab, while Jane has a surprising revelation for Ian and Mandy.

	Anthony resolves to end his relationship with Poppy. Janine is thrilled when she stumbles across a discovery that could spell disaster for Shirley.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Dr Yusef Khan; Zainab Masood; Masood Ahmed; Tamwar Masood; Amira Masood; Syed Masood; Christian Clarke; Ben Mitchell; Phil Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Roxy Mitchell; Jay Mitchell; Billy Mitchell; Jodie Gold; Poppy Meadow; Anthony Moon; Tyler Moon; Michael Moon; Alfie Moon; Kat Moon; Mo Harris; Jean Slater; Jane Beale; Ian Beale; Mandy Salter; Bobby Beale; Dot Branning; Rose Cotton; Whitney Dean; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Janine Butcher; Jack Branning; Denise Fox; Heather Trott; Brendan</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b017ltwb</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b017ltwb</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5677062002321969028.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>20/11/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Phil is unnerved to receive another mysterious photograph from an anonymous source, while Alfie's festive cheer is ruined by a terrible confession from Kat. Also in HD.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Phil is unnerved to receive another mysterious photograph from an anonymous source, while Shirley is convinced she knows the identity of his tormentor. Alfie cranks up the Moon charm as he helps Anthony and Tyler shift some Yuletide goods - but his festive cheer is soured by a terrible confession from Kat. 

	Janine is rocked as a traumatised Pat is forced to divulge the truth about a crime from Frank's past, while Tanya feels the pressure as she continues to keep her illness a secret from her family and friends. Poppy helps Jodie reach a life-changing decision about her future, while Yusef has an unexpected admission for Zainab.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Tanya Jessop; Lauren Branning; Abi Branning; Rainie Cross; Jack Branning; Roxy Mitchell; Phil Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Ben Mitchell; Jay Mitchell; Lola Pearce; Kat Moon; Alfie Moon; Shenice Quinn; Anthony Moon; Tyler Moon; Michael Moon; Janine Butcher; Pat Evans; Carol Jackson; Tiffany Butcher; Zainab Masood; Masood Ahmed; Tamwar Masood; Jane Beale; Denise Fox; Kim Fox; Patrick Trueman; Dot Branning; Rose Cotton; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Heather Trott; Jodie Gold; Poppy Meadow; Mr Lister; Reverend Stevens</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b01835ms</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b01835ms</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5679676348919241949.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>27/11/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>As Tanya teeters on the brink of self-destruction, will a desperate Lauren be forced to reveal her darkest secret? Cora and Rainie are left reeling after a terrible revelation.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>As Tanya teeters on the brink of self-destruction, will a desperate Lauren be forced to reveal her darkest secret? Meanwhile, Cora and Rainie are left reeling after a terrible revelation about their family, while Pat is traumatised when Derek Branning makes an unexpected return to Walford. Lola has a bombshell for Billy and Dot is thrown when Rose makes a confession about her past.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Tanya Jessop; Max Branning; Cora Cross; Rainie Cross; Derek Branning; Dot Branning; Carol Jackson; Jack Branning; Lauren Branning; Abi Branning; Jay Mitchell; Ben Mitchell; Phil Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Billy Mitchell; Lola Pearce; Kat Moon; Alfie Moon; Mo Harris; Jean Slater; Rose Cotton; Dr Yusef Khan; Kim Fox; Jane Beale; Mandy Salter; Pat Evans; Tyler Moon; Roxy Mitchell; Tiffany Butcher; Dr Faye Morrison; Sam</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b0186kwl</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b0186kwl</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5682261060233782614.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>04/12/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Roxy makes the decision to dig for dirt on Derek, leading to an unexpected showdown with the Brannings. Lauren finds herself sidelined as Tanya leans on Max for emotional support. Also in HD.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>A desperate Roxy makes the unwise decision to dig for dirt on Derek, leading to an unexpected showdown with the Brannings. Lauren finds herself sidelined as Tanya leans on Max for emotional support, while Billy ropes Abi into a ploy to dupe social services with terrible consequences.

	Yusef faces another obstacle with the arrival of his cousin Tariq, who warns him of the dire consequences of reuniting with Zainab. Will Tariq be able to placate Yusef before his deceit is revealed to Afia?

	Michael is left humiliated when Derek steps up to assist Janine with a problem with her property empire, and Amira is thrilled when Syed reaches a decision about their new business venture.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Afia Masood; Syed Masood; Amira Masood; Tamwar Masood; Janine Butcher; Michael Moon; Derek Branning; Jack Branning; Phil Mitchell; Roxy Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Carol Jackson; Max Branning; Tanya Jessop; Rainie Cross; Cora Cross; Abi Branning; Lauren Branning; Alfie Moon; Kat Moon; Mo Harris; Jean Slater; Denise Fox; Heather Trott; Ian Beale; Tyler Moon; Anthony Moon; Pat Evans; Billy Mitchell; Lola Pearce; Dot Branning; Sam; Dr Faye Morrison; Harpreet</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b018cjzg</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b018cjzg</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5684854790983838452.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>11/12/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>As Yusef and Zainab get ready to move, a secret threatens to ruin their plans. As the police raid Phil's properties, his search for his stalker leads him to a surprising place. Also in HD.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>As Yusef and Zainab get ready to move to Pakistan, a secret of Yusef's threatens to ruin their plans. As the police raid all of Phil's properties, his search for his stalker leads him to a surprising place. Patrick agrees to hide Alfie and Anthony's dodgy fireworks at the B&amp;B. Rose does a tarot card reading for Kim and Jean and suggests love could be on the cards for one of them - but which one?</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Phil Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Ben Mitchell; Billy Mitchell; Lola Pearce; Jay Mitchell; Roxy Mitchell; Masood Ahmed; Syed Masood; Amira Masood; Tamwar Masood; Afia Masood; Tanya Jessop; Cora Cross; Rainie Cross; Max Branning; Derek Branning; Jack Branning; Anthony Moon; Michael Moon; Alfie Moon; Kat Moon; Jean Slater; Carol Jackson; Liam Butcher; Pat Evans; Denise Fox; Patrick Trueman; Rose Cotton; Janine Butcher; DS Kain; Hayley; Nurse Green; Tariq; Troy</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b018scsg</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b018scsg</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5687452387208630622.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>18/12/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Phil and Shirley attempt to discover the identity of their tormentor. Ricky returns from Dubai with some bad news. Yusef's control of Zainab becomes increasingly abusive.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Phil and Shirley's ploy to discover the identity of their tormentor does not go according to plan and they are stunned to realise that it could be someone much closer to home. Jean has an encounter with a mystery man, but is left reeling when he reveals his true intentions. Ricky returns home from Dubai with some bad news, while Ian has a surprise announcement for Mandy. Yusef's control of Zainab becomes increasingly abusive - will Zainab be able to swallow her pride and seek help from an oblivious Masood before it is too late?</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Ian Beale; Mandy Salter; Bobby Beale; Masood Ahmed; Tamwar Masood; Pat Evans; Carol Jackson; Bianca Butcher; Ricky Butcher; Janine Butcher; Liam Butcher; Tiffany Butcher; Whitney Dean; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Branning, Dot; Rose Cotton; Mo Harris; Jean Slater; Kat Moon; Alfie Moon; Anthony Moon; Tyler Moon; Lauren Branning; Jack Branning; Derek Branning; Phil Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Roxy Mitchell; Heather Trott; Billy Mitchell; Denise Fox; Lola Pearce; Tanya Jessop; Cora Cross; Patrick Trueman; Andrew Cotton; Carter</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b018w7nf</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b018w7nf</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5689483047742012437.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>24/12/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Zainab fears for her son when Yusef refuses to tell her where Kamil is. Alfie and Kat clash over Jean, Ian's wedding day approaches, and Ricky receives bad news about Bianca. Also in HD.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Zainab fears for her son when Yusef refuses to tell her where Kamil is. Scared about what Yusef will do, Zainab is forced to go along with his lies. Meanwhile, Masood finally finds out about Zainab's plight and he forces her to tell him exactly what is going on. However, Masood is shocked when he inadvertently sees evidence of Yusef's abuse and he faces a race against time to track down his missing son. 

	Kat is determined to protect Jean when she shows signs of not coping, but when she wanders off with Shenice, Kat panics and sets off in search for them. Realising that something has to change for the safety of his family, Alfie makes a secret phone call. 

	It is the day of Ian and Mandy's wedding and, while Ian is getting everything ready for his big day, Mandy is having doubts about their future. Meanwhile, Ricky receives some bad news about Bianca's release - will Bianca make it home for Christmas?</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Masood Ahmed; Denise Fox; Ricky Butcher; Bianca Butcher; Pat Evans; Carol Jackson; Whitney Dean; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Kat Moon; Jean Slater; Alfie Moon; Michael Moon; Jack Branning; Phil Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Tamwar Masood; Afia Masood; Syed Masood; Amira Masood; Tamwar Masood; Mo Harris; Lauren Branning; Tyler Moon; Anthony Moon; Ian Beale; Mandy Salter; Heather Trott; Andrew Cotton; Max Branning; Liam Butcher; Morgan Butcher; Tiffany Butcher; Shenice Quinn; Bobby Beale; PC Ali Psyk</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b018wdrd</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b018wdrd</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5690789576793428608.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>27/12/2011</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>After Zainab finally stands up to Yusef, he seeks revenge, throwing the entire square in danger. Denise opens a mysterious present revealing a secret about one of the residents. Also in HD.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>As Masood frantically searches for Kamil, Zainab finally stands up to Yusef - but what consequences will this have for her family? 

	As Yusef seeks his revenge on Zainab and Masood, his actions erupt in explosive consequences, throwing the entire square in danger. 

	At Tanya's, everyone tries their best to have an upbeat Christmas but there is a struggle of power between Max and Derek - who will come out on top? 

	Denise opens a mysterious present revealing a shocking secret about one of the residents in Walford. 

	It's Christmas day at the Mitchell's and Shirley is put off her dinner when she finds out some shocking news about Phil's stalker. 

	Alfie overhears Jean and Kat having a heart to heart but will it reveal some shocking home truths?</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Tamwar Masood; Afia Masood; Masood Ahmed; Syed Masood; Amira Masood; Christian Clarke; Denise Fox; Patrick Trueman; Phil Mitchell; Ben Mitchell; Jay Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Roxy Mitchell; Alfie Moon; Kat Moon; Jean Slater; Anthony Moon; Tyler Moon; Whitney Dean; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Pat Evans; Lola Pearce; Billy Mitchell; Jack Branning; Derek Branning; Max Branning; Tanya Jessop; Cora Cross; Lauren Branning; Abi Branning; Heather Trott; Andrew Cotton; Carol Jackson; Bianca Butcher; Ricky Butcher; Janine Butcher; Michael Moon; Shenice Quinn; Tiffanny Butcher; Morgan Butcher; Liam Butcher; Mo Harris</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b019g22g</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b019g22g</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5695231002474224804.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>08/01/2012</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>It is a dark day in Walford, and the whole of Albert Square is in shock as they come to terms with the loss of one of their own. Meanwhile, Denise takes a stand against Phil. Also in HD.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>It is a dark day in Walford, and the whole of Albert Square is in shock as they come to terms with the loss of one of their own. 

	Denise takes a stand against Phil with a very public campaign, but what will Phil say when he finds out? Ricky stumbles across a letter that could have dire consequences for one of the residents of Albert Square, but what will he do with it? 

	Alfie has a surprise in store for Kat that he believes could save their marriage. Syed tries his best to reconcile with Christian, but Amira refuses to go without a fight.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>David Wicks; Derek Branning; Carol Jackson; Amira Masood; Syed Masood; Masood Ahmed; Qadim Shah; Christian Clarke; Roxy Mitchell; Patrick Trueman; Denise Fox; Alfie Moon; Phil Mitchell; Heather Trott; Andrew Cotton; Shirley Carter; Ben Mitchell; Jay Mitchell; Bianca Butcher; Ricky Butcher; Kat Moon; Anthony Moon; Janine Butcher; Michael Moon; Tamwar Masood; Afia Masood; Jean Slater; Ian Beale; Mandy Salter; Norman Simmonds; Mo Harris; Dot Branning; Billy Mitchell; Whitney Dean; Liam Butcher; Tiffany Butcher; Morgan Butcher; DCI Marsden; Gerry; Aaron</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b01b46p7</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b01b46p7</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5697842772086927726.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>15/01/2012</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Pat's family continue to struggle to deal with their loss, but their troubles are far from over. Fatboy and Tyler are there for Whitney as she prepares to meet Morgan's dad. Also in HD.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Pat's family continue to struggle to deal with their loss, but more unexpected news reveals that their troubles are far from over. 

	Bianca's suspicions of Mandy have devastating consequences for her and Ricky while Jack and Max are forced to intervene when Derek decides he wants to get rid of an old enemy once and for all. 

	Fatboy and Tyler are there for Whitney as she prepares to meet Morgan's dad but how will he react to finding out he has a son? 

	Lauren turns to the bottle after feeling neglected by her friends and family, and can Denise and Zainab's friendship recover after the disastrous events of Christmas Day?</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>David Wicks; Carol Jackson; Bianca Butcher; Derek Branning; Jack Branning; Max Branning; Ricky Butcher; Janine Butcher; Michael Moon; Ian Beale; Mandy Salter; Lucy Bywater; Lauren Branning; Tanya Jessop; Abi Branning; Cora Cross; Kat Moon; Alfie Moon; Dot Branning; Patrick Trueman; Denise Fox; Whitney Dean; Tiffanny Butcher; Liam Butcher; Morgan Butcher; Phil Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Roxy Mitchell; Billy Mitchell; Ben Mitchell; Jay Mitchell; Lola Pearce; Jean Slater; Mo Harris; Rose Cotton; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Heather Trott; Masood Ahmed; Tyler Moon; Anthony Moon; Ray Dixon; Reverend Stevens; Sgt Davis; Les Coker</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b01bqq9x</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b01bqq9x</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5703039253018367389.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>29/01/2012</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>The Mitchells are left reeling when Marsden informs them that Phil has been arrested on suspicion of murder, and Derek seizes the opportunity to gain control of Phil's empire. Also in HD.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>The Mitchells are left reeling when Marsden informs them that Phil has been arrested on suspicion of murder, as a new witness has come forward with damning evidence. Witnessing the drama engulfing the Mitchell household, Derek seizes every opportunity he can to take control of Phil's empire. 

	With Jane's move imminent, Ian engineers a plan he hopes will make her realise that Walford is where she should be. 

	Meanwhile, Zainab puts a plan into action in the hope of getting Tamwar to speak, but the family are stunned when he finally does; and Lucy's suspicions about Mandy deepen when she sees her receiving mysterious phone calls,.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Christian Clarke; Tanya Jessop; Ian Beale; Lucy Beale; Mandy Salter; Ben Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Phil Mitchell; Derek Branning; Max Branning; Lauren Branning; Whitney Dean; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Tyler Moon; Heather Trott; Denise Fox; Syed Masood; Masood Ahmed; Jay Mitchell; Janine Butcher; Bianca Butcher; Ray Dixon; Patrick Trueman; Alfie Moon; Tamwar Masood; Afia Masood; Amira Masood; Anthony Moon; Roxy Mitchell; Billy Mitchell; Lola Pearce; Abi Branning; Gethin; Bobby Beale; Morgan Butcher; Sasha Dixon; Shenice Quinn; Tiffany Butcher; DCI Marsden</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
	<episode>
		<episodeId>b01bym28</episodeId>
		<episodeUrl>http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b01bym28</episodeUrl>
		<episodeFile>5705635560752997295.mp4</episodeFile>
		<episodeDate>05/02/2012</episodeDate>
		<episodeDescription>Panic ensues for the Moon brothers when Derek threatens them for the money they owe him. Shirley is taken aback when Ben tells her he is ready to face Phil.</episodeDescription>
		<episodeWebDescription>Panic ensues for the Moon brothers when Derek threatens them for the money they owe him. 

	Fat Boy continues to fume following last night's events but, after words with both Dot and Bianca, he relents and goes to find Whitney... but will she forgive him? 

	Ian tries his best to bond with Lucy but it's clear that Mandy's presence at the Beale house is not making her happy. 

	Shirley is taken aback when Ben tells her he is ready to face Phil.</episodeWebDescription>
		<episodeCharacters>Ben Mitchell; Phil Mitchell; Shirley Carter; Jay Mitchell; Billy Mitchell; Roxy Mitchell; Jack Branning; Derek Branning; Lauren Branning; Anthony Moon; Tyler Moon; Ray Dixon; Patrick Trueman; Heather Trott; Andrew Cotton; Rose Cotton; Cora Cross; Dot Branning; Arthur 'Fat Boy' Chubb; Whitney Dean; Bianca Butcher; Janine Butcher; Michael Moon; Ian Beale; Mandy Salter; Lucy Beale; Amira Masood; Sophie</episodeCharacters>
	</episode>
</eastendersOmnibus>